1
00:02:11,480 --> 00:02:15,280
m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147

2
00:02:11,480 --> 00:02:15,280
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

3
00:02:11,480 --> 00:02:15,280
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:02:11,480 --> 00:02:15,280
ZiMuZu.tv

5
00:00:00,960 --> 00:00:02,840
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...

6
00:00:04,170 --> 00:00:06,640
Please stop crying. I'm begging you.

7
00:00:06,640 --> 00:00:08,800
I don't know what else to do.

8
00:00:08,800 --> 00:00:10,040
My boobs are empty.

9
00:00:10,040 --> 00:00:12,710
Do you want lasagna?

10
00:00:16,280 --> 00:00:19,330
It's okay, it's okay.

11
00:00:26,400 --> 00:00:28,880
What have we done?

12
00:00:34,140 --> 00:00:36,470
What... what's all this?

13
00:00:36,470 --> 00:00:38,650
Well, it sounded like you were having a rough day,

14
00:00:38,650 --> 00:00:41,150
so I wanted you to come home to something nice.

15
00:00:41,150 --> 00:00:43,710
Oh, that is so thoughtful.

16
00:00:43,710 --> 00:00:46,260
Hey, do you remember when we went wine tasting in Santa Barbara

17
00:00:46,260 --> 00:00:48,470
and you said that was the best rose you'd ever had?

18
00:00:48,470 --> 00:00:50,710
Yeah, I remember us driving up there,

19
00:00:50,710 --> 00:00:52,890
going to the winery and...

20
00:00:52,890 --> 00:00:54,910
that's it.

21
00:00:55,500 --> 00:00:57,030
And this wine is why.

22
00:00:58,990 --> 00:01:00,300
Hey, what smells so good?

23
00:01:00,300 --> 00:01:04,320
I made your favorite: pizza bagels!

24
00:01:05,320 --> 00:01:07,220
Pink wine and pizza bagels?

25
00:01:07,220 --> 00:01:10,320
It's like eighth grade all over again.

26
00:01:10,320 --> 00:01:12,340
I am so lucky to have you.

27
00:01:12,340 --> 00:01:13,840
Well, now be careful, these are hot.

28
00:01:13,840 --> 00:01:15,610
I-I could explain the thermodynamics

29
00:01:15,610 --> 00:01:17,980
of why the cheese seems hotter than the crust,

30
00:01:17,980 --> 00:01:20,310
but instead, I'm gonna keep it to myself.

31
00:01:21,050 --> 00:01:24,580
You always know what not to say.

32
00:01:24,620 --> 00:01:27,060
I just, I can't believe you did all this.

33
00:01:27,060 --> 00:01:28,390
Well, you know,

34
00:01:28,390 --> 00:01:30,350
it's easy to take each other for granted and

35
00:01:30,350 --> 00:01:33,900
I never want to do that to you, because

36
00:01:34,340 --> 00:01:35,700
your love,

37
00:01:36,500 --> 00:01:38,820
it's like a river.

38
00:01:38,820 --> 00:01:41,140
It's peaceful and deep.

39
00:01:41,140 --> 00:01:43,680
Your soul is, it's like a secret

40
00:01:43,680 --> 00:01:46,920
that I never could keep.

41
00:01:46,920 --> 00:01:50,110
You did not just quote an NSYNC song.

42
00:01:50,970 --> 00:01:54,430
I quoted your favorite NSYNC song.

43
00:02:05,800 --> 00:02:07,410
Damn. I burped so hard,

44
00:02:07,410 --> 00:02:10,300
I died in my game.

45
00:02:37,780 --> 00:02:39,900
Leonard, I've been meaning to ask you:

46
00:02:39,930 --> 00:02:42,440
what size shoe do you wear?

47
00:02:42,440 --> 00:02:43,420
Why?

48
00:02:43,420 --> 00:02:47,390
I'm trying to take more of an interest in other people's lives.

49
00:02:49,250 --> 00:02:51,490
That's nice. I wear a size eight and a half.

50
00:02:51,490 --> 00:02:53,700
That's small.

51
00:02:55,370 --> 00:02:58,750
So, tell me, do you have any plans for the weekend?

52
00:02:58,750 --> 00:03:00,710
Are you gonna laugh at the answer?

53
00:03:00,710 --> 00:03:04,480
Only if the answer is "Shopping for baby shoes."

54
00:03:05,930 --> 00:03:06,930
If you must know,

55
00:03:06,930 --> 00:03:09,120
Penny won a spa weekend from work

56
00:03:09,120 --> 00:03:10,210
and she's taking me.

57
00:03:10,210 --> 00:03:12,380
Oh, well you know, that is interesting.

58
00:03:12,380 --> 00:03:15,910
I wonder what kind of infection you'll come home with.

59
00:03:16,850 --> 00:03:19,360
My money's on fungal.

60
00:03:21,100 --> 00:03:24,070
They're still having girls' night across the hall.

61
00:03:24,070 --> 00:03:26,980
Oh, so, hang out with me and we'll have boys' night.

62
00:03:26,980 --> 00:03:27,880
At our age,

63
00:03:27,880 --> 00:03:30,520
why don't we call it man's night?

64
00:03:30,880 --> 00:03:34,520
Because we just spent our allowance on comic books.

65
00:03:37,560 --> 00:03:40,300
Penny, is it weird that we're having girls' night here,

66
00:03:40,300 --> 00:03:41,400
but you don't live here anymore,

67
00:03:41,400 --> 00:03:43,460
so it's basically my girls' night?

68
00:03:43,460 --> 00:03:44,760
I hadn't really thought about it.

69
00:03:44,760 --> 00:03:46,450
But now you're thinking about it and it bothers you?

70
00:03:46,450 --> 00:03:48,550
I get that.

71
00:03:51,190 --> 00:03:53,220
Things going well with you and Sheldon living together?

72
00:03:53,220 --> 00:03:54,400
Better than ever.

73
00:03:54,400 --> 00:03:57,430
He asks about my day, takes an interest in my life.

74
00:03:57,430 --> 00:03:58,860
He's like my boyfriend in college,

75
00:03:58,860 --> 00:04:01,980
except he's real, so people can see him.

76
00:04:03,930 --> 00:04:05,210
I've been seeing him for years,

77
00:04:05,210 --> 00:04:08,070
I'm still not convinced he's real.

78
00:04:09,660 --> 00:04:11,000
Hey, can I ask you a question?

79
00:04:11,000 --> 00:04:12,330
You've been married for a while.

80
00:04:12,330 --> 00:04:13,680
Is it normal for the husband

81
00:04:13,680 --> 00:04:17,550
to kind of completely stop giving a crap?

82
00:04:18,100 --> 00:04:19,990
Uh-oh, what's going on?

83
00:04:19,990 --> 00:04:21,640
Well, Leonard used to do all these things,

84
00:04:21,640 --> 00:04:23,250
like bring me flowers

85
00:04:23,250 --> 00:04:25,870
and wear pants.

86
00:04:25,870 --> 00:04:29,030
It's okay, Howie never has on pants.

87
00:04:29,030 --> 00:04:33,240
The Domino's guy brings the pizza like this now.

88
00:04:33,240 --> 00:04:34,960
Well, Sheldon always has his pants on.

89
00:04:34,960 --> 00:04:38,150
I don't think I could pick his knees out of a lineup.

90
00:04:38,520 --> 00:04:40,040
Well, it's not just the pants.

91
00:04:40,040 --> 00:04:41,110
Just, it's like since we got married,

92
00:04:41,110 --> 00:04:43,150
he doesn't really try anymore.

93
00:04:43,150 --> 00:04:44,770
Uh, Penny?

94
00:04:44,770 --> 00:04:45,560
I don't know how to say this,

95
00:04:45,560 --> 00:04:47,630
but this is my first girls' night

96
00:04:47,630 --> 00:04:50,230
and you're kind of bumming everybody out.

97
00:04:54,230 --> 00:04:55,950
All right, got Halley to sleep.

98
00:04:55,950 --> 00:04:57,640
Yeah, I heard you on the baby monitor.

99
00:04:57,890 --> 00:04:59,850
Didn't think you could turn the theme from Walking Dead

100
00:04:59,850 --> 00:05:02,030
into a lullaby.

101
00:05:03,290 --> 00:05:05,190
Yeah, got to get her hooked on TV,

102
00:05:05,190 --> 00:05:08,550
or someday, she'll want me to play outside.

103
00:05:08,810 --> 00:05:11,580
Boy, that floor is so squeaky.

104
00:05:11,580 --> 00:05:14,450
I'm surprised I didn't wake her up walking out of the room.

105
00:05:14,450 --> 00:05:16,530
Have you tried anything to fix it?

106
00:05:16,530 --> 00:05:18,010
Well, I put the rug down.

107
00:05:18,010 --> 00:05:19,030
It didn't help.

108
00:05:19,030 --> 00:05:22,590
I know. Blue shag. What were you thinking?

109
00:05:24,250 --> 00:05:27,210
Did try nailing a couple of the boards down.

110
00:05:27,210 --> 00:05:28,600
Did that do anything?

111
00:05:28,600 --> 00:05:30,110
Yeah, it left little holes in the floor,

112
00:05:30,110 --> 00:05:31,660
that's why I bought the rug.

113
00:05:39,860 --> 00:05:43,790
If you do that, I'll win in eight moves.

114
00:05:50,370 --> 00:05:52,700
I'll win in five moves.

115
00:05:58,510 --> 00:06:00,870
I'll win in one move.

116
00:06:02,770 --> 00:06:05,410
Oh, no. Good game.

117
00:06:09,410 --> 00:06:10,990
Oh, Penny, I'm trying

118
00:06:10,990 --> 00:06:12,950
to take an interest in other people.

119
00:06:12,950 --> 00:06:14,940
Uh, how was your girls' night?

120
00:06:14,940 --> 00:06:16,370
Oh, it was fine.

121
00:06:16,730 --> 00:06:18,320
Did you have anything to eat?

122
00:06:18,320 --> 00:06:20,170
Uh, chips.

123
00:06:20,290 --> 00:06:22,080
Anything to drink?

124
00:06:22,080 --> 00:06:23,860
Some wine.

125
00:06:23,860 --> 00:06:27,380
Well, I'm just playing tennis against the drapes here.

126
00:06:28,340 --> 00:06:29,470
Just ignore him.

127
00:06:29,470 --> 00:06:31,620
At least he took an interest.

128
00:06:31,990 --> 00:06:33,670
What's that supposed to mean?

129
00:06:33,670 --> 00:06:34,740
Nothing.

130
00:06:34,740 --> 00:06:36,390
Hey, what's going on with you?

131
00:06:36,390 --> 00:06:37,780
I don't want to talk about it.

132
00:06:37,780 --> 00:06:40,090
Well, hey, come on, just tell me.

133
00:06:40,600 --> 00:06:41,610
Fine.

134
00:06:42,270 --> 00:06:43,500
Lately, I kind of feel like

135
00:06:43,500 --> 00:06:45,840
you've been taking me for granted.

136
00:06:45,840 --> 00:06:47,770
Wh-what? Where is this coming from?

137
00:06:47,770 --> 00:06:49,010
Leonard. She might be drunk.

138
00:06:49,010 --> 00:06:51,390
All she had was chips.

139
00:06:51,940 --> 00:06:53,910
It's just, since we got married you seem to think

140
00:06:53,910 --> 00:06:56,170
you don't have to try anymore.

141
00:06:56,170 --> 00:06:57,730
That is ridiculous.

142
00:06:57,730 --> 00:06:59,240
This is exactly why I didn't want to talk about it.

143
00:06:59,240 --> 00:07:00,950
No, No, no, no. Let's talk about it.

144
00:07:00,950 --> 00:07:02,520
I'm the one who's made all the effort

145
00:07:02,520 --> 00:07:04,280
in this relationship since day one.

146
00:07:04,280 --> 00:07:06,770
Please tell me what more I could do.

147
00:07:06,770 --> 00:07:08,710
Okay. You know what? Maybe I'll take Amy with me

148
00:07:08,710 --> 00:07:10,800
to the spa this weekend instead.

149
00:07:11,590 --> 00:07:12,740
Fine, go ahead.

150
00:07:17,130 --> 00:07:19,160
Amy is free.

151
00:07:21,410 --> 00:07:23,030
She had a harp lesson on Saturday,

152
00:07:23,030 --> 00:07:24,250
but it got canceled...

153
00:07:24,760 --> 00:07:27,150
Boy, when you take an interest in people,

154
00:07:27,150 --> 00:07:30,630
you really uncork a geyser of nonsense.

155
00:07:34,000 --> 00:07:36,220
Okay. Thanks, Daddy.

156
00:07:36,670 --> 00:07:39,130
He said the only way to really fix an old floor like that

157
00:07:39,130 --> 00:07:41,340
is to tear it up and replace the whole thing.

158
00:07:41,340 --> 00:07:43,460
- That sounds expensive. - Hang on.

159
00:07:43,460 --> 00:07:44,670
No offense to her father,

160
00:07:44,670 --> 00:07:47,040
but he's not an MIT-trained engineer.

161
00:07:47,040 --> 00:07:48,850
Thinking and building is what you do.

162
00:07:48,850 --> 00:07:51,300
MIT's motto is "Mind and hand,"

163
00:07:51,300 --> 00:07:55,330
which just so happens was also my motto as a lonely teenager.

164
00:07:56,420 --> 00:07:59,600
Oh, come on. We just need to be more creative.

165
00:07:59,600 --> 00:08:03,150
What if you didn't step on the floor at all?

166
00:08:03,150 --> 00:08:04,480
Like, what if you...

167
00:08:04,480 --> 00:08:07,900
swung on a rope from the ceiling?

168
00:08:14,620 --> 00:08:15,540
No.

169
00:08:16,520 --> 00:08:18,140
Okay. Um...

170
00:08:18,140 --> 00:08:20,360
Okay. What if you rig up a pulley system

171
00:08:20,360 --> 00:08:23,820
and move yourself across the room in a harness?

172
00:08:35,610 --> 00:08:37,070
No.

173
00:08:38,820 --> 00:08:39,850
I have one.

174
00:08:39,850 --> 00:08:41,560
What if you got a giant slingshot

175
00:08:41,560 --> 00:08:44,000
and flung yourself into the wall?

176
00:08:45,550 --> 00:08:47,540
- Is that supposed to be funny? - Hold on.

177
00:08:54,980 --> 00:08:57,150
Yeah, that's funny.

178
00:08:59,490 --> 00:09:00,930
All right, we're heading out.

179
00:09:02,370 --> 00:09:04,000
I'll call you when we get to the hotel.

180
00:09:04,000 --> 00:09:06,470
And if they have any of those tiny bottles of shampoo?

181
00:09:06,470 --> 00:09:07,840
I will bring them home so you can show me

182
00:09:07,840 --> 00:09:09,960
how Godzilla takes a shower.

183
00:09:11,560 --> 00:09:12,840
- Have fun. - Thanks.

184
00:09:12,840 --> 00:09:13,730
Are you ready?

185
00:09:15,220 --> 00:09:16,640
Bye, Sheldon.

186
00:09:17,070 --> 00:09:18,410
You know what? I feel uncomfortable

187
00:09:18,410 --> 00:09:20,270
engaging in a public display of affection

188
00:09:20,270 --> 00:09:23,070
while their relationship is strained.

189
00:09:23,510 --> 00:09:25,530
Go ahead, it's fine.

190
00:09:25,990 --> 00:09:27,640
- Bye. - Bye.

191
00:09:34,380 --> 00:09:36,450
- Okay! - Let's go!

192
00:09:39,480 --> 00:09:41,290
- Bye. - Bye.

193
00:09:41,700 --> 00:09:42,390
I'll miss you.

194
00:09:42,390 --> 00:09:43,830
Yeah, I'll miss you, too.

195
00:09:43,830 --> 00:09:44,740
I'll miss you more.

196
00:09:44,740 --> 00:09:46,750
Well, if X equals the amount that you'll miss me,

197
00:09:46,750 --> 00:09:49,240
then I'll miss you X plus one.

198
00:09:49,950 --> 00:09:51,780
If you miss me X plus one, I'll miss you

199
00:09:51,780 --> 00:09:54,050
open paren X plus one, close paren to the second...

200
00:09:57,460 --> 00:09:59,000
Thank you.

201
00:10:06,670 --> 00:10:07,580
Here.

202
00:10:08,180 --> 00:10:10,780
You're sad, so I made you tea.

203
00:10:12,030 --> 00:10:12,850
Thanks.

204
00:10:12,850 --> 00:10:14,520
And it's just the way you like it.

205
00:10:14,520 --> 00:10:15,730
- Earl Grey? - Yes.

206
00:10:15,730 --> 00:10:16,690
- Honey? - Yes.

207
00:10:16,690 --> 00:10:17,680
- Unsweetened almond- - Good Lord!

208
00:10:17,680 --> 00:10:19,840
I made you tea. Just drink it!

209
00:10:22,150 --> 00:10:24,160
Sorry, thank you.

210
00:10:25,780 --> 00:10:27,990
Well, what can we do to cheer you up?

211
00:10:27,990 --> 00:10:30,380
I really don't know.

212
00:10:30,380 --> 00:10:31,960
You want to play Jenga?

213
00:10:31,960 --> 00:10:33,550
Or, uh, Ticket to Ride?

214
00:10:33,550 --> 00:10:34,470
Hearthstone?

215
00:10:34,470 --> 00:10:40,220
I-- what would you be the happiest losing at?

216
00:10:41,460 --> 00:10:43,500
I don't want to play a game, Sheldon.

217
00:10:43,500 --> 00:10:47,860
Wow, and I remember when you loved playing games with me.

218
00:10:47,860 --> 00:10:51,300
Maybe Penny isn't the only relationship you're phoning in.

219
00:10:53,080 --> 00:10:55,320
It's not that I'd stopped trying,

220
00:10:55,320 --> 00:10:58,010
it's just how relationships progress.

221
00:10:58,010 --> 00:10:59,670
They start with infatuation,

222
00:10:59,670 --> 00:11:03,140
but over time mellow into something more comfortable.

223
00:11:04,320 --> 00:11:05,720
Yeah, you're right.

224
00:11:05,720 --> 00:11:08,920
It's like when I first encountered the Pythagorean Theorem.

225
00:11:08,920 --> 00:11:12,480
You know, I was blown away that the square of the hypotenuse

226
00:11:12,480 --> 00:11:15,090
was the sum of the squares of the opposite sides.

227
00:11:15,090 --> 00:11:17,460
Yeah, but now I'm just like "Eh."

228
00:11:22,060 --> 00:11:24,910
Okay, this grid represents the room.

229
00:11:24,910 --> 00:11:28,480
All we need to do is plot out where each squeak is

230
00:11:28,480 --> 00:11:31,830
and we can find a quiet path to the crib.

231
00:11:34,460 --> 00:11:37,480
It looks like a map from Dungeons & Dragons.

232
00:11:37,850 --> 00:11:41,850
Except the creature in the crib is a level-nine poop monster.

233
00:11:41,850 --> 00:11:44,080
Okay, uh, you check for squeaks,

234
00:11:44,080 --> 00:11:45,870
and I will mark them down.

235
00:11:45,870 --> 00:11:46,920
Okay.

236
00:11:46,920 --> 00:11:50,040
Space A-3, here we go.

237
00:11:53,750 --> 00:11:55,530
It's squeaking. Mark it.

238
00:11:55,530 --> 00:11:58,290
It's nice to think that you grew up in this room

239
00:11:58,290 --> 00:12:00,630
and now your daughter's going to as well.

240
00:12:00,630 --> 00:12:04,350
I hope she has the same amount of sex in it I did.

241
00:12:04,350 --> 00:12:06,200
None. Next square.

242
00:12:08,520 --> 00:12:11,420
Why do you bounce with your hands in the air like that?

243
00:12:11,810 --> 00:12:13,750
It's a tradition of my people.

244
00:12:13,750 --> 00:12:15,770
If I were a rich man

245
00:12:19,830 --> 00:12:21,700
"Material Girl" needs to be retired.

246
00:12:21,700 --> 00:12:24,790
That is your karaoke song.

247
00:12:27,880 --> 00:12:31,240
Would you like to play a driving game I invented?

248
00:12:31,240 --> 00:12:35,140
Is it about the failing state of my relationship with Penny?

249
00:12:35,500 --> 00:12:36,900
Never mind.

250
00:12:39,040 --> 00:12:41,860
You know, Penny went to this spa to be away from you.

251
00:12:41,860 --> 00:12:43,690
Are you sure you should be going there?

252
00:12:43,690 --> 00:12:46,640
I don't want to wait two days for us to work this out.

253
00:12:47,130 --> 00:12:48,290
Very well.

254
00:12:48,290 --> 00:12:49,910
You got married spur of the moment.

255
00:12:49,910 --> 00:12:53,190
I don't see why your divorce should be any different.

256
00:12:54,040 --> 00:12:55,940
I would pull this car over and kick you out,

257
00:12:55,940 --> 00:12:59,950
but... if Penny dumps me, you're all I got.

258
00:13:03,810 --> 00:13:06,110
When was the last time you got a massage?

259
00:13:06,110 --> 00:13:07,950
Sheldon walked on my back two weeks ago,

260
00:13:07,950 --> 00:13:09,990
but that was just 'cause there was a spider on his pillow

261
00:13:09,990 --> 00:13:12,180
and he was trying to get away.

262
00:13:13,110 --> 00:13:14,630
Leonard stood on me once, too,

263
00:13:14,630 --> 00:13:18,110
but he was just trying to see the Rose Parade.

264
00:13:19,400 --> 00:13:20,550
I don't know the protocol,

265
00:13:20,550 --> 00:13:22,750
are you gonna be naked for your massage?

266
00:13:22,750 --> 00:13:23,920
Well. Yeah.

267
00:13:24,040 --> 00:13:26,840
Then this is probably too many clothes.

268
00:13:30,160 --> 00:13:31,950
What are you doing here?

269
00:13:31,950 --> 00:13:33,330
I came here to apologize.

270
00:13:33,330 --> 00:13:34,860
Okay. Leonard, I really appreciate that,

271
00:13:34,860 --> 00:13:37,180
but I need a little time to myself.

272
00:13:37,740 --> 00:13:38,770
Okay. I don't get it.

273
00:13:38,770 --> 00:13:40,320
You said make an effort.

274
00:13:40,320 --> 00:13:42,380
Here I am, making an effort.

275
00:13:42,380 --> 00:13:44,700
Hello, Amy. It's nice to see you.

276
00:13:45,410 --> 00:13:47,760
Nice to see you, too.

277
00:13:48,060 --> 00:13:51,540
And that's how you make effort look effortless.

278
00:13:51,840 --> 00:13:52,770
All right. Can you please just go

279
00:13:52,770 --> 00:13:53,810
and we'll talk about this tomorrow?

280
00:13:53,810 --> 00:13:54,950
I don't understand what you want!

281
00:13:54,950 --> 00:13:56,470
I'm trying to figure it out!

282
00:13:56,470 --> 00:13:57,780
You know what? If you'd like,

283
00:13:57,780 --> 00:14:01,370
I could whip up a quick Relationship Agreement.

284
00:14:01,900 --> 00:14:02,890
Well, I'm at a spa,

285
00:14:02,890 --> 00:14:05,420
might as well do something relaxing.

286
00:14:05,880 --> 00:14:08,450
Sheldon, why don't we give them some privacy?

287
00:14:08,450 --> 00:14:09,970
Very well.

288
00:14:09,970 --> 00:14:11,430
Hey. Later, we'll check out the minibar?

289
00:14:11,430 --> 00:14:13,850
I'll show you how Godzilla gets drunk.

290
00:14:17,350 --> 00:14:20,660
So what we did was map out the entire room

291
00:14:20,660 --> 00:14:23,610
to identify every squeak.

292
00:14:23,610 --> 00:14:26,080
Watch. It's easy, once you get the hang of it.

293
00:14:28,460 --> 00:14:29,130
Step.

294
00:14:31,050 --> 00:14:32,150
Step.

295
00:14:34,130 --> 00:14:35,600
Hop onto ottoman.

296
00:14:36,900 --> 00:14:40,070
Don't do that in socks, I almost broke my neck.

297
00:14:40,910 --> 00:14:42,580
Then simply sit,

298
00:14:42,580 --> 00:14:44,860
spin, stand,

299
00:14:45,160 --> 00:14:47,610
stretch...

300
00:14:50,940 --> 00:14:53,070
Maybe unloosen your pants.

301
00:14:54,310 --> 00:14:56,630
And... step,

302
00:14:56,630 --> 00:14:58,310
grab, tiny pivot,

303
00:14:58,310 --> 00:15:00,590
pull, and you're there.

304
00:15:01,640 --> 00:15:03,500
Easy, peasy, mac and...

305
00:15:03,910 --> 00:15:05,680
You get the idea.

306
00:15:06,750 --> 00:15:08,280
You actually expect me to do this

307
00:15:08,280 --> 00:15:10,670
while holding a baby in the dark?

308
00:15:10,670 --> 00:15:12,540
Hold on...

309
00:15:19,310 --> 00:15:20,690
I don't think she was impressed.

310
00:15:20,690 --> 00:15:22,110
Bigger problems.

311
00:15:22,110 --> 00:15:24,010
I felt something pop.

312
00:15:27,650 --> 00:15:30,500
There's a cucumber in my water.

313
00:15:33,660 --> 00:15:34,890
Do they know it's there?

314
00:15:34,890 --> 00:15:36,900
Um, sh-should I tell somebody?

315
00:15:37,700 --> 00:15:38,710
It's there on purpose.

316
00:15:38,710 --> 00:15:41,060
It's refreshing.

317
00:15:45,510 --> 00:15:46,880
Interesting.

318
00:15:46,880 --> 00:15:48,450
The world's most boring liquid

319
00:15:48,450 --> 00:15:50,200
and the world's most boring vegetable.

320
00:15:50,200 --> 00:15:52,710
But you put 'em together, and bleh.

321
00:15:56,230 --> 00:15:58,240
Oh! Good, you're here. Are you still fighting?

322
00:15:58,240 --> 00:16:01,150
If you get divorced, do I get two Christmases?

323
00:16:01,720 --> 00:16:03,420
We're not getting divorced.

324
00:16:03,420 --> 00:16:06,250
Listen, we realized, that, uh...

325
00:16:06,250 --> 00:16:09,260
we're facing some new challenges as a married couple.

326
00:16:09,260 --> 00:16:10,480
Yeah. And there are a few things

327
00:16:10,480 --> 00:16:11,780
we need to stay on top of.

328
00:16:11,780 --> 00:16:13,690
So we thought it would useful--

329
00:16:14,140 --> 00:16:16,490
and I can't believe I am about to say this--

330
00:16:17,860 --> 00:16:20,980
Would you please help us make a Relationship Agreement?

331
00:16:23,480 --> 00:16:25,400
But one that's tailored to us.

332
00:16:25,400 --> 00:16:27,320
Okay? We don't need a bathroom schedule.

333
00:16:27,320 --> 00:16:29,870
Although a rule about him texting me from in there

334
00:16:29,870 --> 00:16:32,680
might help with the romance.

335
00:16:34,150 --> 00:16:35,610
What do you say?

336
00:16:35,610 --> 00:16:37,210
I get to write a contract?

337
00:16:37,210 --> 00:16:40,650
I say, let's get this party of the first part started!

338
00:16:47,210 --> 00:16:48,350
Do you really think that's funny?

339
00:16:48,350 --> 00:16:50,850
It's in our agreement. I have to laugh.

340
00:16:56,210 --> 00:16:58,260
If you find this draft acceptable,

341
00:16:58,260 --> 00:17:01,230
then I believe your new Relationship Agreement

342
00:17:01,230 --> 00:17:03,080
is ready to be signed.

343
00:17:03,080 --> 00:17:04,980
Article 8, subsection B:

344
00:17:04,980 --> 00:17:07,350
Leonard will restrict video-gaming in underpants

345
00:17:07,350 --> 00:17:09,010
to hours Penny is not home.

346
00:17:09,010 --> 00:17:11,670
This includes boxers, briefs, thongs, G-strings

347
00:17:11,670 --> 00:17:13,330
or anything else that calls attention

348
00:17:13,330 --> 00:17:16,030
to his pasty little thighs.

349
00:17:19,550 --> 00:17:20,760
Does it really need to say that?

350
00:17:20,760 --> 00:17:24,500
I did this for free, let me get a little something.

351
00:17:25,770 --> 00:17:27,990
Article 10, subsection C:

352
00:17:27,990 --> 00:17:29,850
If questioned, Penny may not say

353
00:17:29,850 --> 00:17:32,030
that everything is fine if it isn't.

354
00:17:32,030 --> 00:17:34,920
Other unacceptable responses include: "It's nothing,"

355
00:17:34,920 --> 00:17:37,210
"Don't worry about it," And "I said it's nothing,

356
00:17:37,210 --> 00:17:39,330
don't worry about it."

357
00:17:40,460 --> 00:17:42,490
I think this all looks good.

358
00:17:42,490 --> 00:17:43,310
Me, too.

359
00:17:43,310 --> 00:17:44,870
Oh, well. Great, then. Here.

360
00:17:44,870 --> 00:17:48,050
You sign here, date here.

361
00:17:48,050 --> 00:17:50,370
And, Penny, if you could initial here to indicate

362
00:17:50,370 --> 00:17:53,950
that you're accepting Leonard in "as is" condition.

363
00:18:01,120 --> 00:18:03,740
I remember signing our first Relationship Agreement.

364
00:18:03,740 --> 00:18:06,110
You seem to be forgetting the "No nostalgia" clause.

365
00:18:06,110 --> 00:18:08,000
Right, right. Got it.

