1
00:18:08,570 --> 00:18:16,570
m 390 300 b 390 311 390 320 390 330 400 330 410 330 419 330 419 320 419 310 419 300 409 300 400 300 390 300 m 428 338 b 413 338 397 338 382 338 382 323 382 308 382 292 397 292 412 292 428 292 428 307 428 322 428 338 m 178 513 b 178 523 178 533 178 542 188 542 197 542 207 542 207 532 207 522 207 513 197 513 188 513 178 513 m 216 505 b 216 520 216 535 216 551 200 551 185 551 169 551 169 536 169 520 169 505 184 505 200 505 216 505 m 207 330 b 207 320 207 310 207 301 197 301 188 301 178 301 178 311 178 320 178 330 188 330 197 330 207 330 m 169 292 b 185 292 200 292 215 292 215 307 215 323 215 338 200 338 185 338 169 338 169 323 169 308 169 292 m 302 367 b 300 367 297 367 295 367 295 365 295 362 295 360 297 360 299 360 302 360 302 362 302 365 302 367 m 312 512 b 309 512 307 512 304 512 304 510 304 507 304 505 307 505 309 505 312 505 312 507 312 509 312 512 m 217 388 b 220 388 222 388 225 388 225 391 225 393 225 396 223 396 221 396 217 396 217 394 217 392 217 388 m 351 367 b 348 367 346 367 343 367 343 365 343 362 343 360 345 360 348 360 351 360 351 362 351 365 351 367 m 331 311 b 331 314 331 316 331 319 329 319 326 319 324 319 324 317 324 314 324 311 326 311 329 311 331 311 m 322 387 b 319 387 317 387 314 387 314 384 314 382 314 379 316 379 319 379 322 379 322 381 322 384 322 387 m 314 464 b 314 461 314 459 314 456 316 456 319 456 322 456 322 459 322 461 322 464 319 464 317 464 314 464 m 312 427 b 312 430 312 432 312 435 310 435 307 435 304 435 302 427 304 425 312 427 m 225 427 b 225 430 225 432 225 435 223 435 220 435 218 435 215 427 216 426 225 427 m 304 377 b 304 374 304 372 304 369 307 369 309 369 312 369 312 372 312 374 312 377 310 377 307 377 304 377 m 254 348 b 251 348 249 348 246 348 245 340 246 339 254 340 254 343 254 346 254 348 m 293 311 b 293 314 293 316 293 319 290 319 288 319 285 319 285 316 285 314 285 311 288 311 290 311 293 311 m 391 543 b 394 543 396 543 399 543 399 545 399 548 399 551 396 551 394 551 391 551 391 548 391 546 391 543 m 341 456 b 341 459 341 461 341 464 338 464 336 464 333 464 333 461 333 459 333 456 336 456 338 456 341 456 m 353 456 b 355 456 358 456 360 456 360 462 360 468 360 474 358 474 355 474 353 474 353 468 353 462 353 456 m 285 466 b 291 466 296 466 302 466 302 471 302 477 302 483 300 483 297 483 295 483 294 480 294 478 294 474 291 474 288 474 285 474 285 471 285 469 285 466 m 216 407 b 219 407 222 407 225 407 225 410 225 413 225 416 219 416 214 416 208 416 208 410 208 404 208 398 210 398 213 398 216 398 216 401 216 404 216 407 m 389 456 b 389 462 389 468 389 474 383 474 378 474 372 474 372 471 372 468 372 465 375 465 378 465 381 465 381 462 381 459 382 456 384 456 386 456 389 456 m 179 418 b 182 418 184 418 187 418 187 421 187 423 187 427 194 427 200 427 206 427 206 430 206 432 206 435 197 435 188 435 179 435 179 429 179 424 179 418 m 381 445 b 381 439 381 433 381 427 384 427 386 427 389 427 389 430 390 433 390 436 393 436 396 436 399 436 399 443 399 448 399 454 396 454 394 454 391 454 391 451 391 449 390 445 387 445 385 445 381 445 m 362 426 b 358 426 356 426 353 426 353 423 353 420 353 418 355 417 358 417 361 417 362 414 362 411 362 408 365 408 367 408 370 408 370 411 371 414 371 417 374 417 377 417 380 417 380 420 380 423 380 425 377 425 374 425 371 425 371 432 371 438 371 444 362 446 362 446 362 438 362 434 362 430 362 426 m 323 377 b 323 374 323 371 323 368 320 368 317 368 314 367 314 362 314 356 314 350 317 350 320 350 323 350 323 346 323 343 324 340 326 340 328 340 331 340 332 343 332 346 332 349 335 349 338 349 341 349 341 352 341 355 341 358 338 358 335 358 332 359 332 365 332 371 332 377 329 377 326 377 323 377 m 371 504 b 374 504 377 504 381 504 381 500 381 497 381 494 377 494 374 494 371 494 371 497 371 500 371 504 m 389 512 b 380 512 371 512 362 512 362 504 362 495 362 487 362 486 363 485 364 485 372 484 381 485 389 485 389 494 389 503 389 512 m 371 369 b 371 372 371 375 371 378 377 378 383 378 389 378 389 384 389 390 389 396 387 396 384 396 381 396 381 393 381 391 381 388 378 388 374 388 371 388 371 390 371 393 371 396 368 396 365 396 362 396 362 394 362 391 361 388 359 387 356 387 353 387 353 381 353 375 353 369 358 369 364 369 371 369 m 303 523 b 306 523 309 523 312 523 312 526 312 529 312 532 309 532 306 532 303 532 303 536 303 539 303 542 306 542 309 542 312 542 312 545 312 548 312 551 303 551 294 551 285 551 285 542 285 533 285 524 288 523 291 523 294 523 294 520 294 517 295 514 297 514 299 514 302 514 303 517 303 520 303 523 m 324 417 b 327 417 329 417 332 417 332 410 332 404 332 397 330 397 327 397 324 397 324 394 324 391 324 389 333 389 342 389 351 389 351 394 351 400 351 406 348 406 345 406 342 406 342 416 342 426 342 436 345 436 348 436 350 436 352 445 352 445 344 445 341 445 338 445 334 445 334 445 333 445 332 445 332 448 332 451 332 454 329 454 326 454 324 454 324 442 324 430 324 417 m 429 552 b 429 555 429 558 429 562 432 562 435 562 439 562 439 558 439 555 439 552 435 552 432 552 429 552 m 352 281 b 352 285 352 288 352 291 355 291 358 291 361 291 361 288 361 284 361 281 358 281 355 281 352 281 m 168 388 b 168 384 168 381 168 378 165 378 162 378 158 378 158 381 158 384 158 388 162 388 165 388 168 388 m 246 484 b 242 484 239 484 236 484 236 488 236 491 236 494 239 494 242 494 246 494 246 491 246 487 246 484 m 158 474 b 158 478 158 481 158 484 165 484 172 484 178 484 178 481 178 478 178 474 172 474 165 474 158 474 m 361 320 b 361 313 361 307 361 301 358 301 355 301 351 301 351 307 351 314 351 320 355 320 358 320 361 320 m 255 484 b 255 487 255 491 255 495 258 495 261 495 264 495 264 498 264 501 265 504 268 504 271 504 274 504 274 500 274 497 274 493 271 493 268 493 266 493 265 490 265 487 265 484 262 484 259 484 255 484 m 255 311 b 255 307 255 304 255 300 252 300 249 300 246 300 246 297 246 294 246 292 253 292 258 292 264 292 264 295 264 298 265 301 268 301 271 301 275 301 275 294 275 288 275 281 261 281 249 281 236 281 236 288 236 294 236 301 239 301 242 301 245 301 245 305 245 308 245 311 249 311 252 311 255 311 m 371 281 b 371 304 371 326 371 349 394 349 416 349 439 349 439 326 439 304 439 281 416 281 393 281 371 281 m 226 562 b 226 539 226 516 226 494 203 494 181 494 158 494 158 516 158 539 158 562 181 562 203 562 226 562 m 226 349 b 226 326 226 304 226 281 203 281 181 281 158 281 158 304 158 327 158 349 181 349 203 349 226 349 m 401 456 b 410 456 419 456 429 456 429 459 429 462 429 465 432 465 435 465 439 465 439 455 439 445 439 436 435 436 432 436 429 436 428 439 428 442 428 445 422 445 416 445 410 445 410 442 410 439 410 436 407 435 404 435 401 435 401 432 401 430 401 427 404 427 407 427 410 427 410 423 410 421 410 418 416 418 422 418 429 418 429 421 429 424 429 426 432 426 435 426 439 426 439 416 439 407 439 397 435 397 432 397 429 397 429 400 428 403 428 406 422 406 416 406 409 406 409 410 409 413 409 416 403 416 398 416 394 416 393 416 391 415 391 414 391 409 391 403 391 398 394 398 397 398 400 397 400 394 401 391 401 388 407 388 413 388 419 388 420 385 420 382 420 379 423 379 426 379 429 379 429 382 429 385 429 388 432 388 435 388 439 388 439 378 439 368 439 359 432 359 425 359 418 359 418 365 418 371 418 377 409 377 400 377 391 377 391 374 391 372 391 369 394 369 397 369 400 368 400 365 400 362 400 358 389 358 378 358 368 358 363 359 361 357 362 352 362 345 362 337 362 330 358 330 355 330 351 330 351 336 351 342 351 348 348 348 345 348 342 348 342 335 342 323 342 310 339 310 336 310 333 310 333 307 333 304 333 301 336 301 339 301 342 301 342 294 342 288 342 281 339 281 335 281 331 281 331 285 331 287 331 291 328 291 325 291 322 291 322 294 322 297 322 300 319 300 316 300 313 301 313 307 313 314 313 321 316 321 319 321 322 321 322 323 323 327 322 328 319 329 316 329 312 330 312 336 312 342 312 348 309 348 307 348 304 348 304 345 304 342 303 339 300 339 297 339 293 339 293 346 293 352 293 359 283 359 274 359 265 359 265 362 265 365 265 368 268 369 271 369 273 369 273 375 273 381 273 387 270 387 268 387 266 387 265 384 265 381 265 377 259 377 252 377 246 377 245 370 245 370 256 368 256 362 256 356 256 350 259 349 262 349 265 349 265 343 265 337 265 331 268 331 271 331 274 331 274 337 274 343 274 349 278 349 281 349 285 349 285 343 285 337 285 330 291 330 297 330 304 330 304 323 304 317 304 310 300 310 298 310 295 310 295 303 295 298 295 291 298 291 301 291 303 291 303 288 303 285 303 281 297 281 290 281 283 281 283 291 283 300 283 310 277 310 271 310 264 310 264 317 264 323 264 329 258 329 252 329 246 329 246 326 246 323 246 320 242 320 239 320 236 320 236 339 236 359 236 379 239 379 242 379 245 379 245 382 245 385 245 388 248 388 251 388 254 388 254 391 254 394 254 396 251 397 248 397 245 397 245 401 245 404 245 407 248 407 251 408 254 408 254 411 255 414 255 417 258 417 261 417 264 417 264 421 264 424 265 426 268 426 271 426 274 426 274 423 274 420 274 416 271 416 269 416 266 416 266 410 266 404 266 398 272 398 278 398 285 398 285 388 285 379 285 369 288 369 290 369 293 369 293 372 293 375 294 378 297 378 300 379 302 379 303 382 303 385 303 388 306 388 309 388 312 388 312 395 312 400 312 406 309 406 307 406 304 406 304 403 304 400 304 397 300 397 297 397 294 397 293 400 293 403 293 406 290 406 287 406 284 406 284 413 284 420 284 426 287 427 291 426 292 428 294 429 293 433 294 436 297 436 299 436 302 436 302 439 302 442 302 445 296 445 291 445 285 445 285 442 284 439 284 436 278 436 271 436 265 436 265 439 265 442 265 446 268 446 270 446 273 446 273 452 273 458 273 464 271 464 268 464 266 464 265 461 265 458 265 454 259 454 252 454 246 454 246 451 246 449 246 446 249 446 252 446 255 446 255 439 255 432 255 426 251 426 248 426 244 426 244 429 244 432 244 435 242 435 239 435 236 435 236 419 236 403 236 387 233 387 230 387 227 387 227 384 226 381 226 377 223 377 220 377 217 377 217 374 216 371 217 370 220 369 223 369 226 368 226 365 226 362 226 358 219 358 213 358 207 358 206 362 206 364 206 367 200 367 194 367 188 367 188 364 188 361 188 359 178 359 168 359 158 359 158 362 158 365 158 369 165 369 171 369 177 369 177 376 177 382 177 388 184 388 190 388 196 388 196 398 196 407 196 416 193 416 191 416 188 416 188 413 188 410 188 407 184 407 181 407 178 407 177 410 177 413 177 416 174 416 172 416 169 416 169 413 169 410 168 407 165 407 162 407 158 407 158 410 158 414 158 417 162 417 165 417 167 417 167 420 167 423 167 426 164 426 161 426 158 426 158 433 158 439 158 446 162 446 165 446 168 446 168 443 169 440 169 437 172 437 174 437 177 437 177 443 177 448 177 455 171 455 165 455 158 455 158 458 158 462 158 466 174 466 190 466 206 466 206 469 206 471 206 474 200 474 194 474 187 474 187 478 187 481 187 484 194 484 201 484 207 484 207 481 207 478 208 476 211 476 213 476 216 476 216 479 216 481 216 484 220 484 223 484 226 484 226 481 226 478 226 474 223 474 220 474 217 474 217 471 217 468 217 466 220 465 223 465 226 465 226 462 226 458 226 455 223 455 220 455 216 455 216 458 216 461 216 464 213 464 210 464 207 464 207 461 207 458 207 454 201 454 195 454 188 454 188 452 188 449 188 446 201 446 214 446 226 446 226 443 227 440 227 437 230 437 232 437 235 437 235 443 235 449 235 455 239 456 242 456 245 456 245 459 245 462 245 466 252 466 258 466 264 466 264 469 264 472 264 475 271 475 277 475 284 475 284 485 284 494 284 504 287 504 290 504 293 504 293 507 293 510 293 512 280 512 268 512 256 512 256 509 255 506 255 503 248 503 242 503 236 503 236 507 236 510 236 513 239 513 242 514 244 514 244 520 244 526 244 532 241 532 239 532 236 532 236 542 236 552 236 561 239 561 242 561 246 561 246 555 246 549 246 543 250 543 252 542 256 542 256 539 256 536 256 533 259 533 262 533 265 533 265 529 265 527 266 524 268 524 271 524 273 524 273 530 273 535 273 541 270 541 268 542 265 542 265 545 265 549 265 553 268 553 271 553 274 553 274 556 274 559 274 562 287 562 300 562 313 562 313 558 314 556 314 553 317 553 319 553 322 553 322 556 322 559 322 561 326 561 329 561 333 561 333 558 333 555 333 553 336 553 339 553 342 553 342 556 342 559 342 562 349 562 355 562 361 562 361 555 361 548 361 542 358 542 355 542 351 542 351 545 351 548 351 551 348 551 345 551 342 551 342 548 342 545 342 542 339 542 335 542 331 542 331 545 331 548 331 551 328 551 326 551 324 551 324 545 324 539 324 533 327 533 330 533 332 533 332 529 332 526 332 522 329 522 326 522 324 522 324 516 324 510 324 504 327 504 330 504 332 504 332 500 332 497 332 494 329 494 326 494 322 494 322 497 322 500 322 503 319 503 316 503 314 503 314 493 314 484 314 475 317 475 320 475 324 475 324 471 324 469 324 466 326 466 329 466 332 466 332 469 332 472 332 475 335 475 338 475 342 475 342 479 342 481 342 484 345 484 348 485 351 485 351 488 351 491 351 494 351 503 351 503 343 503 342 503 342 504 342 504 342 510 342 517 342 524 345 524 348 524 351 524 351 527 351 530 351 533 358 533 365 533 372 533 372 529 372 527 372 524 378 524 383 524 389 524 389 530 389 535 389 542 386 542 383 542 380 542 380 545 380 548 380 551 376 551 374 551 371 552 371 555 371 558 371 562 374 562 377 562 381 562 381 558 381 556 381 553 384 553 387 553 390 553 390 556 390 559 390 562 397 562 403 562 410 562 410 555 410 548 410 542 407 542 404 541 401 541 401 538 401 536 401 533 404 533 407 533 410 533 410 529 410 526 410 522 406 522 404 522 401 522 401 519 401 516 401 513 404 513 407 513 410 513 410 510 410 507 410 503 407 503 404 503 401 503 401 500 401 497 401 494 407 494 413 494 420 494 420 491 420 488 420 485 423 485 425 485 428 485 428 491 428 497 428 503 425 503 422 503 419 503 419 510 419 516 419 524 422 524 425 524 428 524 428 527 428 529 428 532 425 532 422 532 419 532 419 536 419 539 419 542 426 542 432 542 439 542 439 535 439 529 439 523 436 522 433 522 430 522 430 519 430 517 430 513 433 513 436 513 439 513 439 503 439 494 439 484 435 484 433 483 429 483 429 480 429 477 429 474 426 474 422 474 418 474 418 478 418 480 418 483 415 483 413 483 410 483 410 480 410 477 410 474 407 474 404 474 401 474 401 468 401 462 401 456 m 449 571 b 349 571 249 571 149 571 149 471 149 371 149 271 249 271 349 271 449 271 449 371 449 471 449 571

2
00:00:02,790 --> 00:00:05,620
- Hey, have you ever heard of the Van Nuys Comic-Con? - Yeah.

3
00:00:05,620 --> 00:00:08,680
It's a dinky little convention where they sell collectibles

4
00:00:08,680 --> 00:00:11,260
and get sad D-list celebrities to appear. Why?

5
00:00:11,260 --> 00:00:13,540
I got asked to sign autographs there.

6
00:00:13,540 --> 00:00:15,840
That's awesome!

7
00:00:16,730 --> 00:00:18,320
Is this for Serial Ape-ist?

8
00:00:18,320 --> 00:00:19,870
Well, it could be for the monkey movie.

9
00:00:19,870 --> 00:00:21,470
It could be my hemorrhoid commercial.

10
00:00:21,470 --> 00:00:23,660
The list does not go on.

11
00:00:24,150 --> 00:00:25,140
- When is it? - It doesn't matter.

12
00:00:25,140 --> 00:00:26,970
- I'm not doing it. - What? Why not?

13
00:00:26,970 --> 00:00:28,630
You just said yourself, it's sad.

14
00:00:28,630 --> 00:00:29,890
Yeah, but it's not pathetic.

15
00:00:29,890 --> 00:00:32,100
That's where I draw the line.

16
00:00:32,790 --> 00:00:34,170
Come on! We'll have fun.

17
00:00:34,170 --> 00:00:35,310
I don't know.

18
00:00:35,310 --> 00:00:37,740
You'll have nerds fawning all over you.

19
00:00:37,740 --> 00:00:40,550
If you don't love that, this marriage is in trouble.

20
00:00:40,970 --> 00:00:42,800
I guess it wouldn't hurt to meet some fans

21
00:00:42,800 --> 00:00:43,970
and make a little extra money.

22
00:00:43,970 --> 00:00:45,250
Yeah.

23
00:00:45,550 --> 00:00:48,640
Wow! An appearance by George Lucas...

24
00:00:48,640 --> 00:00:50,920
...'s dermatologist.

25
00:00:52,130 --> 00:00:54,100
- Oh, I want that autograph. - Oh, yeah.

26
00:01:20,270 --> 00:01:21,740
You know, with us living together,

27
00:01:21,740 --> 00:01:24,660
maybe we could think about having people over.

28
00:01:24,660 --> 00:01:26,750
We have people over all the time.

29
00:01:26,750 --> 00:01:30,180
We have the maintenance people, the pizza delivery man...

30
00:01:30,180 --> 00:01:32,450
...that UPS driver who feels the need to ask

31
00:01:32,450 --> 00:01:34,310
how parts of me are hanging.

32
00:01:36,010 --> 00:01:37,620
You know what I meant.

33
00:01:37,800 --> 00:01:38,990
All right, fine.

34
00:01:38,990 --> 00:01:41,330
Let's say that we were to entertain people.

35
00:01:41,330 --> 00:01:43,230
What type of gathering did you have in mind?

36
00:01:43,230 --> 00:01:44,340
Huh? A meal? Lunch?

37
00:01:44,340 --> 00:01:45,250
Brunch? Dinner?

38
00:01:45,250 --> 00:01:47,270
Afternoon tea? A formal tea? Hmm?

39
00:01:47,270 --> 00:01:48,350
Is it a party?

40
00:01:48,350 --> 00:01:49,720
And if so, what kind of party?

41
00:01:49,720 --> 00:01:50,690
A cocktail party?

42
00:01:50,690 --> 00:01:52,440
A Tupperware party?

43
00:01:52,440 --> 00:01:55,920
Ooh, yeah-- is it a surprise party?

44
00:01:55,920 --> 00:01:57,720
Oh, I hope it's not a West Coast party,

45
00:01:57,720 --> 00:01:58,950
'cause according to the man on the radio,

46
00:01:58,950 --> 00:02:01,540
a West Coast party don't stop.

47
00:02:02,290 --> 00:02:03,550
I'm sorry I mentioned it.

48
00:02:03,550 --> 00:02:05,630
Oh, don't be. You get your hopes up,

49
00:02:05,630 --> 00:02:08,610
I knock them down. That's called teamwork.

50
00:02:17,720 --> 00:02:19,270
That's a kick.

51
00:02:19,270 --> 00:02:21,450
That's an actual kick.

52
00:02:26,150 --> 00:02:28,360
What are you doing?

53
00:02:28,970 --> 00:02:30,660
I felt a kick.

54
00:02:30,660 --> 00:02:33,010
There's a baby in there.

55
00:02:33,900 --> 00:02:36,820
Oh, yeah, that's where I put it.

56
00:02:37,490 --> 00:02:40,110
Oh, I mean, I know you're pregnant.

57
00:02:40,110 --> 00:02:41,080
I just...

58
00:02:41,230 --> 00:02:44,650
never connected the idea of pregnancy

59
00:02:44,650 --> 00:02:48,180
and you actually having a baby.

60
00:02:48,670 --> 00:02:51,560
Which MIT did you go to?

61
00:02:54,970 --> 00:02:58,440
Oh, God, we are not ready to have an infant in this house!

62
00:02:58,440 --> 00:03:00,880
We don't have a crib, we don't have diapers.

63
00:03:00,880 --> 00:03:02,170
We're not baby-proofed.

64
00:03:02,170 --> 00:03:05,900
Anyone can just walk in off the street and lift our toilet lids!

65
00:03:06,520 --> 00:03:08,840
Howie, we have time to do all that stuff.

66
00:03:08,840 --> 00:03:09,730
Do we?

67
00:03:09,730 --> 00:03:10,540
Look at you.

68
00:03:10,540 --> 00:03:13,690
Willy Wonka would roll you to the juicing room.

69
00:03:15,870 --> 00:03:18,390
The next person kicking you will be me.

70
00:03:18,390 --> 00:03:19,710
Good night.

71
00:03:26,830 --> 00:03:27,810
Are we even in a good school...?

72
00:03:30,840 --> 00:03:33,770
I warned you, and I did it.

73
00:03:37,700 --> 00:03:38,680
What's all this?

74
00:03:38,680 --> 00:03:41,380
Oh, everything we need for your autograph session--

75
00:03:41,380 --> 00:03:43,030
- head shots, markers. - Okay.

76
00:03:43,030 --> 00:03:44,740
Leonard, it's sweet you're excited about this,

77
00:03:44,740 --> 00:03:47,510
but it'll be a miracle if one person asks for my autograph.

78
00:03:47,510 --> 00:03:48,500
Are you kidding?

79
00:03:48,500 --> 00:03:51,490
I once paid $20 for Theo Sassler's signature.

80
00:03:51,490 --> 00:03:52,810
- Who's that? Oh, I don't even know.

81
00:03:52,810 --> 00:03:55,400
I just liked his name. Theo Sassler!

82
00:03:56,290 --> 00:03:57,230
Oh, and look at this.

83
00:03:57,230 --> 00:04:00,200
I even got a change maker.

84
00:04:04,130 --> 00:04:06,530
How much change you want, little lady?

85
00:04:07,730 --> 00:04:10,670
Oh, there's so much I want to change.

86
00:04:11,540 --> 00:04:14,970
Yeah, well, if it's a dollar, you're in luck.

87
00:04:19,910 --> 00:04:21,670
What's going on here?

88
00:04:21,670 --> 00:04:24,520
You expressed an interest in having people over,

89
00:04:24,520 --> 00:04:26,810
and I feel I dismissed it too quickly.

90
00:04:26,810 --> 00:04:29,190
So, I took matters into my own hands,

91
00:04:29,190 --> 00:04:31,360
and I arranged a brunch.

92
00:04:31,360 --> 00:04:33,120
Well, that's so nice.

93
00:04:33,120 --> 00:04:34,660
Who's coming?

94
00:04:34,660 --> 00:04:37,780
Oh, uh, Stuart, Bert from the geology lab,

95
00:04:37,780 --> 00:04:39,690
and Mrs. Petrescu from downstairs.

96
00:04:39,690 --> 00:04:41,800
You mean the Romanian lady on the second floor?

97
00:04:41,800 --> 00:04:42,590
Yes.

98
00:04:42,590 --> 00:04:43,550
Oh, fun story:

99
00:04:43,550 --> 00:04:46,300
she grew up with ten siblings.

100
00:04:46,300 --> 00:04:49,730
Or possibly penguins. Her English is atrocious.

101
00:04:50,330 --> 00:04:52,300
That's an odd mix of people.

102
00:04:52,300 --> 00:04:53,970
Well, for our first time hosting,

103
00:04:53,970 --> 00:04:56,610
I thought it would be wise to conduct a trial run.

104
00:04:56,610 --> 00:04:59,330
You know, like how I practiced for that Halloween haunted house

105
00:04:59,330 --> 00:05:02,420
by going into the bathroom at the bus station.

106
00:05:02,930 --> 00:05:04,710
You never went into that haunted house.

107
00:05:04,760 --> 00:05:08,500
You never saw what jumped out at me at the bus station.

108
00:05:09,000 --> 00:05:10,370
Well, thank you, Sheldon.

109
00:05:10,370 --> 00:05:12,070
This is a fun surprise.

110
00:05:12,660 --> 00:05:14,210
Well, the real surprise is

111
00:05:14,210 --> 00:05:17,050
how surprised you are that I'm great at surprises.

112
00:05:17,050 --> 00:05:19,050
Well, that's not a surprise at all.

113
00:05:19,050 --> 00:05:20,740
I mean, if I knew you were good at surprises,

114
00:05:20,740 --> 00:05:22,300
I would have expected the surprise,

115
00:05:22,300 --> 00:05:23,480
and therefore not have been surprised.

116
00:05:23,480 --> 00:05:24,600
But as it is, I didn't know,

117
00:05:24,600 --> 00:05:27,810
and therefore my surprise should be unsurprising.

118
00:05:28,900 --> 00:05:32,470
Don't get me all randy. Guests are on the way.

119
00:05:35,970 --> 00:05:36,790
Hi.

120
00:05:36,790 --> 00:05:37,820
Hey, where you been?

121
00:05:37,820 --> 00:05:40,390
Oh, we went and did a little shopping for the baby.

122
00:05:40,390 --> 00:05:43,050
Wait till you see the crib we found.

123
00:05:43,050 --> 00:05:44,790
You bought a crib without me?

124
00:05:44,790 --> 00:05:46,010
- You're gonna love it. - Yeah.

125
00:05:46,010 --> 00:05:47,580
It's the highest rated one on the market.

126
00:05:47,580 --> 00:05:49,070
I wouldn't even call it a crib.

127
00:05:49,070 --> 00:05:52,840
I'd call it a Fortress of Solitude for babies.

128
00:05:54,380 --> 00:05:55,550
Sounds expensive.

129
00:05:55,550 --> 00:05:57,170
Okay, well, I may have gone a bit overboard,

130
00:05:57,170 --> 00:05:59,790
but you can't put a price on safety.

131
00:05:59,790 --> 00:06:03,480
Though if you did, it's more zeroes than you're expecting.

132
00:06:04,120 --> 00:06:05,800
But it's the safest crib you can buy.

133
00:06:05,800 --> 00:06:08,260
And if you don't like it, we can return it.

134
00:06:08,260 --> 00:06:09,710
- Fine. - In our new minivan.

135
00:06:09,710 --> 00:06:11,290
Hey, what's for lunch?

136
00:06:12,240 --> 00:06:13,840
You bought a minivan?!

137
00:06:13,840 --> 00:06:15,960
It's for the baby, and I didn't buy it.

138
00:06:15,960 --> 00:06:18,860
The dealer loaned it to me for a 24-hour test drive.

139
00:06:18,860 --> 00:06:21,080
Though we did ding up the back pretty good with the crib,

140
00:06:21,080 --> 00:06:23,560
so you might have bought a minivan.

141
00:06:24,770 --> 00:06:27,360
I don't want to drive that. It's such a mom car.

142
00:06:27,360 --> 00:06:29,260
The guy at the dealership said

143
00:06:29,260 --> 00:06:31,450
they're not just for moms anymore.

144
00:06:31,450 --> 00:06:34,540
Then again, he did think you were my husband.

145
00:06:37,530 --> 00:06:38,930
They thought it at the ultrasound.

146
00:06:38,930 --> 00:06:41,360
Why not at the car dealership?

147
00:06:46,680 --> 00:06:49,420
Never been on this side of the table before.

148
00:06:49,420 --> 00:06:51,530
I feel powerful.

149
00:06:52,010 --> 00:06:52,880
Really?

150
00:06:52,880 --> 00:06:56,830
I feel like I'm selling candy so our team can get new uniforms.

151
00:06:57,150 --> 00:06:59,830
Okay, so it's $4.75 for a signed black-and-white

152
00:06:59,830 --> 00:07:01,190
and $9.95 for a color.

153
00:07:01,190 --> 00:07:03,130
Right. Why not five and ten bucks?

154
00:07:03,130 --> 00:07:06,850
Well, I brought my moneymaker. Let me shake it.

155
00:07:07,760 --> 00:07:09,340
Hey, that guy's looking over here.

156
00:07:09,340 --> 00:07:11,650
You think he's your first autograph?

157
00:07:11,650 --> 00:07:13,550
I don't know. Be cool. He's coming. He's coming.

158
00:07:15,460 --> 00:07:16,580
I love your movie.

159
00:07:16,580 --> 00:07:17,590
Well, thanks.

160
00:07:17,590 --> 00:07:18,840
It has got to be one of the worst things

161
00:07:18,840 --> 00:07:21,210
I've ever seen in my life.

162
00:07:22,140 --> 00:07:25,110
Your love confuses me.

163
00:07:26,180 --> 00:07:27,890
- Would you like an autograph? - Sure.

164
00:07:27,890 --> 00:07:29,750
- Okay. Who do I make it out to? - Daniel.

165
00:07:29,750 --> 00:07:31,500
- Okay. - I have to ask.

166
00:07:31,500 --> 00:07:33,240
Were you trying to be that bad,

167
00:07:33,240 --> 00:07:36,010
or are you just a terrible actress?

168
00:07:36,510 --> 00:07:39,050
That did not clear things up.

169
00:07:42,220 --> 00:07:44,090
That'll be $4.75.

170
00:07:44,090 --> 00:07:44,990
Keep the change.

171
00:07:44,990 --> 00:07:47,010
But I...

172
00:07:54,650 --> 00:07:56,320
Nothing about that was good.

173
00:07:59,000 --> 00:08:01,720
There's nothing to be afraid of, Sheldon.

174
00:08:03,690 --> 00:08:07,150
The average cork speed is 25 miles per hour.

175
00:08:07,150 --> 00:08:08,720
If that is too fast around a school,

176
00:08:08,720 --> 00:08:11,080
it is certainly too fast around a kitchen.

177
00:08:14,000 --> 00:08:15,430
Been 15 minutes. Just sayin'.

178
00:08:15,430 --> 00:08:17,660
Okay. I can do this.

179
00:08:17,660 --> 00:08:19,120
Just give me a moment...

180
00:08:22,090 --> 00:08:24,230
Mimosas coming up.

181
00:08:24,380 --> 00:08:26,500
I once left orange juice in my fridge so long,

182
00:08:26,500 --> 00:08:29,070
it tasted like a mimosa.

183
00:08:29,750 --> 00:08:31,210
How old was it?

184
00:08:31,210 --> 00:08:32,520
It's hard to say.

185
00:08:32,520 --> 00:08:35,640
I don't remember much after I drank it.

186
00:08:36,640 --> 00:08:38,720
Would you like one, Mrs. Petrescu?

187
00:08:38,720 --> 00:08:39,420
Yes.

188
00:08:39,420 --> 00:08:42,690
Drink is fun and good friends-- Applebee's.

189
00:08:45,610 --> 00:08:48,020
She's learning English from TV.

190
00:08:48,020 --> 00:08:51,330
TV, good. Now back to you.

191
00:08:53,380 --> 00:08:54,220
Hey, guys.

192
00:08:54,220 --> 00:08:55,060
Hi, Stuart.

193
00:08:55,060 --> 00:08:56,020
These are for you.

194
00:08:56,020 --> 00:08:57,920
Oh, they're pretty. Thank you.

195
00:08:57,920 --> 00:09:01,050
Stuart, this is Bert from the Caltech geology lab,

196
00:09:01,050 --> 00:09:03,290
and this is Mrs. Petrescu from downstairs.

197
00:09:03,290 --> 00:09:04,140
Nice to meet you.

198
00:09:04,140 --> 00:09:05,410
- Hello. - Hey.

199
00:09:05,410 --> 00:09:06,900
So, what did I miss?

200
00:09:06,900 --> 00:09:11,130
Eh, we watched Sheldon try to open a bottle for 15 minutes.

201
00:09:12,110 --> 00:09:17,480
15 minutes can save you 15% or more on car insurance.

202
00:09:20,870 --> 00:09:22,890
Anybody else coming to this thing?

203
00:09:28,210 --> 00:09:29,110
What's your name?

204
00:09:29,110 --> 00:09:30,630
- Jeff. - Okay.

205
00:09:30,630 --> 00:09:33,060
My favorite part is your shower scene.

206
00:09:33,060 --> 00:09:35,030
Been hearing that a lot today.

207
00:09:35,590 --> 00:09:37,990
I even have a screen grab on my phone.

208
00:09:37,990 --> 00:09:40,420
Yep, there they are.

209
00:09:41,610 --> 00:09:42,960
Okay, let's keep it moving.

210
00:09:42,960 --> 00:09:43,990
Here you go.

211
00:09:45,860 --> 00:09:47,380
Should've punched that guy.

212
00:09:47,380 --> 00:09:49,260
Well, go ahead. He's right over there.

213
00:09:49,260 --> 00:09:52,450
Why do you do that? Can't you let me have my moment?

214
00:09:53,740 --> 00:09:55,230
- Hello. - Hi.

215
00:09:55,230 --> 00:09:56,390
I like your movies.

216
00:09:56,390 --> 00:09:58,460
- Thank you! - I saw both of them.

217
00:09:58,460 --> 00:09:59,860
I assume we're still talking about the movies,

218
00:09:59,860 --> 00:10:02,100
but after today, who knows.

219
00:10:03,080 --> 00:10:04,710
You think I could get a picture of us?

220
00:10:04,710 --> 00:10:05,650
Oh, sure.

221
00:10:05,650 --> 00:10:07,450
And, uh, could you be giving me a kiss?

222
00:10:07,450 --> 00:10:08,410
No. She cannot kiss...

223
00:10:08,410 --> 00:10:10,500
What is wrong with you people?!

224
00:10:10,500 --> 00:10:12,510
- Leonard... - No, no, no. It's not okay.

225
00:10:12,510 --> 00:10:15,160
- Who are you? - I'm her husband.

226
00:10:15,720 --> 00:10:17,720
No, you're not.

227
00:10:19,700 --> 00:10:20,630
I am.

228
00:10:20,630 --> 00:10:22,700
Yeah, he really is.

229
00:10:24,740 --> 00:10:26,540
No.

230
00:10:29,000 --> 00:10:32,330
It's got a rearview camera, there's a DVD player--

231
00:10:32,330 --> 00:10:33,980
oh, and check this out.

232
00:10:35,820 --> 00:10:38,190
It's like we're living in the future!

233
00:10:39,060 --> 00:10:41,560
Hey, show her the trunk! Show her the trunk!

234
00:10:41,560 --> 00:10:45,930
Imagine this: you've got the baby in one hand,

235
00:10:45,930 --> 00:10:48,640
groceries in the other, and you're thinking,

236
00:10:49,040 --> 00:10:51,630
"How am I gonna open this trunk?"

237
00:10:52,030 --> 00:10:53,850
I'm probably thinking, "Where's my husband,

238
00:10:53,850 --> 00:10:56,170
and why isn't he helping me?"

239
00:10:57,030 --> 00:10:59,650
You don't need my help when you can open the trunk

240
00:10:59,650 --> 00:11:01,920
with a simple kick of the foot.

241
00:11:07,890 --> 00:11:10,170
No, it's a gentle kick; you're doing it wrong.

242
00:11:10,170 --> 00:11:11,730
Here. Give me those.

243
00:11:18,840 --> 00:11:21,030
Uh, maybe it was more of a circle?

244
00:11:24,170 --> 00:11:27,020
It's weird that guy thought you were a couple.

245
00:11:28,080 --> 00:11:28,980
- Yes! - Yes!

246
00:11:29,520 --> 00:11:30,360
See?

247
00:11:30,360 --> 00:11:31,490
Easy.

248
00:11:31,490 --> 00:11:33,360
And look at all this cargo space.

249
00:11:33,360 --> 00:11:34,600
You know, we'll get the crib out

250
00:11:34,600 --> 00:11:36,070
and you can take it for a test-drive.

251
00:11:36,070 --> 00:11:39,510
I'm telling you, this van is gonna be...

252
00:11:42,000 --> 00:11:43,160
Oh, is it your back?

253
00:11:43,160 --> 00:11:44,590
Uh... yeah.

254
00:11:46,310 --> 00:11:49,260
Anyway, let's just get in and see if the GPS

255
00:11:49,260 --> 00:11:52,160
can take us to the nearest emergency room.

256
00:11:54,420 --> 00:11:57,060
So until Amy's apartment is fixed,

257
00:11:57,060 --> 00:11:59,280
she and I are living here together.

258
00:11:59,280 --> 00:12:01,230
I lived with my old girlfriend.

259
00:12:01,230 --> 00:12:03,280
She was a geologist, too.

260
00:12:03,280 --> 00:12:04,790
Things didn't work out?

261
00:12:04,790 --> 00:12:08,340
I came home from work one day and she had taken everything.

262
00:12:08,340 --> 00:12:09,580
I'm warning you,

263
00:12:09,580 --> 00:12:11,960
hide your good rocks.

264
00:12:13,620 --> 00:12:16,060
My sister's husband took all her things, too.

265
00:12:16,060 --> 00:12:18,000
Story at 11:00.

266
00:12:20,720 --> 00:12:22,980
Really, no one else is coming?

267
00:12:24,100 --> 00:12:25,190
Oh, this is it.

268
00:12:25,190 --> 00:12:27,240
You are the practice round.

269
00:12:27,240 --> 00:12:29,490
Practice round? For-for what?

270
00:12:29,490 --> 00:12:31,250
Uh, no. He-he just means that

271
00:12:31,250 --> 00:12:33,160
you were the first people we thought of.

272
00:12:33,160 --> 00:12:34,090
You know, exactly.

273
00:12:34,090 --> 00:12:35,580
We've never thrown a brunch before,

274
00:12:35,580 --> 00:12:38,240
and I wanted to work out all the kinks.

275
00:12:38,630 --> 00:12:41,140
So, I'm like a lab rat

276
00:12:41,140 --> 00:12:43,440
before your real friends come over?

277
00:12:47,450 --> 00:12:48,950
You see, your words sound reasonable,

278
00:12:48,950 --> 00:12:51,440
but your face looks angry.

279
00:12:52,700 --> 00:12:55,100
Help me out here. This is not where I shine.

280
00:12:55,560 --> 00:12:58,280
Stuart, you know you're one of our favorite people.

281
00:12:58,280 --> 00:12:59,750
Okay, now, see, you look sincere,

282
00:12:59,750 --> 00:13:02,210
but your words are completely false.

283
00:13:03,020 --> 00:13:04,270
I'm glad we did this test run.

284
00:13:04,270 --> 00:13:06,480
These brunches are wild!

285
00:13:09,040 --> 00:13:11,480
But how did you get her to go out with you?

286
00:13:11,480 --> 00:13:13,430
Well, she moved in across the hall.

287
00:13:13,430 --> 00:13:16,370
And he started to slowly wear me down.

288
00:13:16,980 --> 00:13:19,760
Like a river carves a canyon.

289
00:13:19,830 --> 00:13:23,690
Yeah, except the river kept showing me his Pokemon cards.

290
00:13:24,910 --> 00:13:26,000
Ready to go?

291
00:13:26,000 --> 00:13:26,950
Hang on. This guy's telling me

292
00:13:26,950 --> 00:13:29,590
how he got the Serial Ape-ist girl to marry him.

293
00:13:29,870 --> 00:13:31,270
This guy?

294
00:13:31,900 --> 00:13:34,610
But he's wearing a change maker.

295
00:13:35,570 --> 00:13:37,590
I think it's hot.

296
00:13:39,300 --> 00:13:40,420
That's right.

297
00:13:40,420 --> 00:13:43,140
I'm her change daddy.

298
00:13:48,730 --> 00:13:50,520
What was I thinking?

299
00:13:50,520 --> 00:13:52,880
Wolowitzes are not a lifting people!

300
00:13:52,880 --> 00:13:55,190
We tip the lifting people!

301
00:13:56,990 --> 00:13:59,720
Do we really have to sit for hours in the emergency room?

302
00:13:59,720 --> 00:14:02,240
They're just gonna give you ice and Advil like last time.

303
00:14:02,660 --> 00:14:05,760
You're gonna feel terrible when I'm in a wheelchair.

304
00:14:07,130 --> 00:14:09,110
Which, by the way, would fit easily in the back

305
00:14:09,110 --> 00:14:11,350
of this award-winning minivan.

306
00:14:11,970 --> 00:14:13,420
Fine, we'll go to the E.R.

307
00:14:13,420 --> 00:14:15,220
Just stop selling me on the van.

308
00:14:15,220 --> 00:14:18,160
You're right. It sells itself.

309
00:14:19,240 --> 00:14:21,180
You have to admit, it's a pretty smooth ride.

310
00:14:21,180 --> 00:14:23,220
I was hoping it'd be quieter.

311
00:14:24,040 --> 00:14:25,660
If childbirth is half this bad,

312
00:14:25,660 --> 00:14:28,020
you are so screwed!

313
00:14:29,350 --> 00:14:31,350
- Are we there yet?! - Soon.

314
00:14:31,350 --> 00:14:33,400
Why is it taking so long?!

315
00:14:33,400 --> 00:14:35,070
H-Howard, Howard, look at the DVD screen.

316
00:14:35,070 --> 00:14:37,740
I put on Batman: The Animated Series. Your favorite!

317
00:14:37,740 --> 00:14:40,430
I'm in too much pain to watch cartoo...

318
00:14:40,430 --> 00:14:42,920
Oh! This is a good one.

319
00:14:43,810 --> 00:14:47,070
I've been babysitting him way longer than you have.

320
00:14:47,950 --> 00:14:51,530
Fine. I'll buy the stupid van.

321
00:14:53,970 --> 00:14:56,320
This is the best blintz I've ever had.

322
00:14:56,320 --> 00:14:58,060
Oh. Thank you.

323
00:14:58,060 --> 00:15:00,430
It almost makes up for the incredibly awkward turn

324
00:15:00,430 --> 00:15:02,400
things took earlier.

325
00:15:03,730 --> 00:15:05,820
You know what, I-I think I'm just gonna go.

326
00:15:05,820 --> 00:15:07,320
No, Stuart, don't.

327
00:15:07,320 --> 00:15:11,120
No, I-I consider you and Sheldon like my family,

328
00:15:11,120 --> 00:15:13,390
and I'm not even sure you think of me as a friend.

329
00:15:13,390 --> 00:15:15,790
You have any idea how that feels?

330
00:15:15,790 --> 00:15:17,420
We're so sorry.

331
00:15:17,420 --> 00:15:20,040
I'm always the last one anybody thinks of.

332
00:15:20,040 --> 00:15:21,690
Well, no, that's not true.

333
00:15:21,690 --> 00:15:24,300
I mean, sometimes it's Koothrappali.

334
00:15:25,030 --> 00:15:26,140
But we're not supposed to say that

335
00:15:26,140 --> 00:15:28,160
'cause he's a minority.

336
00:15:29,420 --> 00:15:30,430
Bye.

337
00:15:30,430 --> 00:15:32,560
Stuart, wait.

338
00:15:33,910 --> 00:15:36,850
I do know what it feels like to be left out.

339
00:15:36,850 --> 00:15:38,200
I know how it feels, too.

340
00:15:38,200 --> 00:15:41,480
All right, this is about me and him; you're not part of it.

341
00:15:42,970 --> 00:15:46,730
Stuart, perhaps we do take you for granted,

342
00:15:46,730 --> 00:15:48,440
and that is not acceptable.

343
00:15:48,440 --> 00:15:51,400
Please know that you truly are a valuable member

344
00:15:51,400 --> 00:15:53,170
of our social group.

345
00:15:53,170 --> 00:15:54,160
Thank you.

346
00:15:54,160 --> 00:15:57,960
You know, in fact, I'd like to propose a toast.

347
00:16:00,950 --> 00:16:02,490
To Stuart.

348
00:16:02,940 --> 00:16:04,610
A fine man,

349
00:16:04,610 --> 00:16:08,320
a good friend and a wonderful guest.

350
00:16:08,320 --> 00:16:09,700
- Hear, hear. - Cheers.

351
00:16:09,700 --> 00:16:13,600
Cheers. Filmed before a live studio audience.

352
00:16:17,520 --> 00:16:21,000
And that is how a short asthmatic scientist

353
00:16:21,000 --> 00:16:23,390
landed a stone cold fox.

354
00:16:27,180 --> 00:16:29,220
I didn't know you can propose to the same person

355
00:16:29,220 --> 00:16:31,240
so many times.

356
00:16:32,200 --> 00:16:34,060
The third time, I did it in skywriting,

357
00:16:34,060 --> 00:16:35,930
but she never looked up.

358
00:16:36,580 --> 00:16:38,200
You know, once, I proposed to him.

359
00:16:38,200 --> 00:16:39,950
Yeah. I said no.

360
00:16:40,710 --> 00:16:41,480
Why?

361
00:16:41,480 --> 00:16:43,700
I just wanted to make her work for it.

362
00:16:44,730 --> 00:16:46,990
Yeah, that's gonna cost you later.

363
00:16:48,090 --> 00:16:50,550
Hang on. Is she just with you because you're rich?

364
00:16:50,550 --> 00:16:52,620
She makes more money than I do!

365
00:16:52,620 --> 00:16:56,230
What?! Who are you?!

366
00:17:00,220 --> 00:17:02,900
Do you know what else I love about you?

367
00:17:03,420 --> 00:17:06,990
Y-Your handwriting is impeccable!

368
00:17:07,650 --> 00:17:08,800
Thank you for noticing!

369
00:17:08,800 --> 00:17:09,620
No, I mean it. I mean it.

370
00:17:09,620 --> 00:17:13,780
It's like you have the soul of a label maker.

371
00:17:14,630 --> 00:17:17,050
You know what I love about you? Hmm?

372
00:17:17,050 --> 00:17:20,180
You never leave the house without a paper clip!

373
00:17:20,650 --> 00:17:22,600
You never know when two pieces of paper

374
00:17:22,600 --> 00:17:26,450
might temporarily need fastening in the top left corner.

375
00:17:29,560 --> 00:17:32,910
I also love how you never use swear words.

376
00:17:32,910 --> 00:17:34,260
You know, it turns out,

377
00:17:34,260 --> 00:17:38,190
you can hurt people just as well without 'em.

378
00:17:40,550 --> 00:17:43,140
Maybe I can get a little help putting some of this stuff away.

379
00:17:43,140 --> 00:17:45,390
Oh, calm down.

380
00:17:45,390 --> 00:17:48,480
I already put away five of these!

381
00:17:49,490 --> 00:17:50,100
You see?

382
00:17:50,100 --> 00:17:53,940
No muss, no fuss, not a single cuss.

