1
00:01:00,660 --> 00:01:05,660
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:01:00,660 --> 00:01:05,660
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:01:00,660 --> 00:01:05,660
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:01:01,160 --> 00:01:05,660
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

5
00:01:01,160 --> 00:01:05,660
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

6
00:01:01,160 --> 00:01:05,660
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

7
00:01:01,160 --> 00:01:05,660
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

8
00:01:04,780 --> 00:01:09,400
V

9
00:01:09,400 --> 00:01:13,600
V                                                                      V

10
00:01:13,600 --> 00:01:17,560
V

11
00:00:02,970 --> 00:00:05,090
You know, downward-facing dog

12
00:00:05,090 --> 00:00:09,420
comes from the Sanskrit phrase adho mukha shvanasana.

13
00:00:09,420 --> 00:00:11,750
Oh, that's beautiful. What does it mean?

14
00:00:11,750 --> 00:00:14,570
"Downward-facing dog."

15
00:00:15,040 --> 00:00:16,480
Yeah, I guess they don't have Sanskrit

16
00:00:16,480 --> 00:00:19,290
for "Butts up and heads down."

17
00:00:19,290 --> 00:00:20,900
Hey, we wrote the Kama Sutra.

18
00:00:20,900 --> 00:00:24,680
If it involves butts, there's a word for it.

19
00:00:24,680 --> 00:00:26,760
I thought we were getting breakfast before work.

20
00:00:26,760 --> 00:00:28,240
Oh, right, sorry.

21
00:00:28,240 --> 00:00:30,470
It's my fault. I asked Penny to do yoga with me.

22
00:00:30,470 --> 00:00:32,330
If you want, I can get ready in five minutes.

23
00:00:32,330 --> 00:00:34,920
It's cute that you think that.

24
00:00:35,560 --> 00:00:36,570
Don't worry about it.

25
00:00:36,570 --> 00:00:37,600
Hey, can I ask you a favor?

26
00:00:37,600 --> 00:00:39,200
Would you mind taking Cinnamon for a walk?

27
00:00:39,200 --> 00:00:41,010
Sure. You're living here for free.

28
00:00:41,010 --> 00:00:43,060
I guess I owe you.

29
00:00:44,090 --> 00:00:46,180
Bye, Cinnamon. Be a good girl.

30
00:00:46,180 --> 00:00:47,650
- Yeah, bye, sweetie! - Bye!

31
00:00:47,650 --> 00:00:49,860
Yeah, yeah, bye, Leonard.

32
00:00:51,280 --> 00:00:55,680
Okay, and tree pose.

33
00:00:56,700 --> 00:00:59,340
Well, she's done.

34
00:01:26,400 --> 00:01:28,180
Things have been going really well

35
00:01:28,180 --> 00:01:30,510
with the infinite resistance gyroscope.

36
00:01:30,510 --> 00:01:32,450
That's great. How so?

37
00:01:32,450 --> 00:01:33,880
Oh, the project is classified.

38
00:01:33,880 --> 00:01:35,660
I can't tell you.

39
00:01:35,660 --> 00:01:39,420
Oh, I suppose I could redact the classified parts.

40
00:01:39,420 --> 00:01:43,730
All right, um, I came up with an elegant solution to the...

41
00:01:46,400 --> 00:01:48,010
I used the...

42
00:01:49,910 --> 00:01:51,470
And then I...

43
00:01:56,180 --> 00:01:58,130
And that did it.

44
00:02:00,180 --> 00:02:03,230
Wow, I wonder what they're redacting.

45
00:02:04,060 --> 00:02:06,330
Why don't you ask me what I'm working on?

46
00:02:06,330 --> 00:02:08,790
Oh, very well. What have you been working on?

47
00:02:08,790 --> 00:02:11,990
And feel free to honk during the boring parts.

48
00:02:12,300 --> 00:02:14,150
I'm doing some experiments to show

49
00:02:14,150 --> 00:02:16,000
that the signal to move a muscle occurs

50
00:02:16,000 --> 00:02:18,450
before you know you even decided to move it.

51
00:02:18,450 --> 00:02:20,620
W... So you're attempting to pinpoint

52
00:02:20,620 --> 00:02:23,140
where consciousness resides in the brain.

53
00:02:23,140 --> 00:02:25,540
Yes, I'm trying to figure out the nanometer

54
00:02:25,540 --> 00:02:27,930
and the attosecond, precisely where and when

55
00:02:27,930 --> 00:02:30,500
an event of awareness takes place.

56
00:02:30,500 --> 00:02:32,110
Well, what do you know?

57
00:02:32,110 --> 00:02:34,660
Here I was, waiting to be bored with biology,

58
00:02:34,660 --> 00:02:37,440
and instead you tickle my intellectual fancy.

59
00:02:37,440 --> 00:02:41,260
Which, unlike my body, is an okay place to tickle.

60
00:02:42,900 --> 00:02:44,000
You know, when I was six,

61
00:02:44,000 --> 00:02:47,530
I wanted to marry the gorilla from Good Night, Gorilla.

62
00:02:47,930 --> 00:02:50,420
Maybe I was onto something.

63
00:02:52,670 --> 00:02:55,110
Gentlemen, the most interesting thing

64
00:02:55,110 --> 00:02:56,950
just happened with this spoon.

65
00:02:56,950 --> 00:03:00,660
Unless it was singing "Be Our Guest," I doubt it.

66
00:03:01,510 --> 00:03:03,900
Yeah, I picked it up without thinking about it.

67
00:03:03,900 --> 00:03:06,160
Which raises a neuroscientific question,

68
00:03:06,160 --> 00:03:08,320
when did I decide to pick it up?

69
00:03:08,320 --> 00:03:10,610
The bigger question is, what are you gonna eat with that spoon?

70
00:03:10,610 --> 00:03:13,050
You didn't get any food.

71
00:03:14,030 --> 00:03:16,150
He does raise an interesting point.

72
00:03:16,150 --> 00:03:19,540
Amy is studying the time lag between intent and awareness,

73
00:03:19,540 --> 00:03:20,990
and I realized that applies

74
00:03:20,990 --> 00:03:23,330
to the measurement problem in quantum mechanics.

75
00:03:23,330 --> 00:03:25,690
Now, I recognize there will be a time lag

76
00:03:25,690 --> 00:03:27,880
between me saying that and you Googling what it means,

77
00:03:27,880 --> 00:03:29,530
so I'll wait.

78
00:03:30,750 --> 00:03:32,020
I understand it, Sheldon.

79
00:03:32,020 --> 00:03:33,540
Yeah, me, too.

80
00:03:33,540 --> 00:03:34,710
I'm sorry, I spaced.

81
00:03:34,710 --> 00:03:37,610
Are we still talking about the spoon?

82
00:03:37,610 --> 00:03:41,130
It's nice to see you taking an interest in Amy's work.

83
00:03:41,130 --> 00:03:42,180
Well, don't get me wrong.

84
00:03:42,180 --> 00:03:44,260
Neurobiology's nothing more than the science

85
00:03:44,260 --> 00:03:45,680
of gray squishy stuff.

86
00:03:45,680 --> 00:03:47,420
But, you know, when it connects to physics,

87
00:03:47,420 --> 00:03:51,250
gas up the Ford, Martha, we're going for a drive.

88
00:03:53,950 --> 00:03:55,690
So did you confront Jennifer?

89
00:03:55,690 --> 00:03:57,380
I was going to, but she called in sick.

90
00:03:57,380 --> 00:03:59,030
And guess who else called in sick.

91
00:03:59,030 --> 00:04:00,920
- Paul. - Paul.

92
00:04:00,920 --> 00:04:02,080
Who's Paul?

93
00:04:02,080 --> 00:04:03,620
Oh, you met him at the office Christmas party.

94
00:04:03,620 --> 00:04:04,940
He's married to Nancy.

95
00:04:04,940 --> 00:04:07,890
Oh, sure. Wait, Nancy?

96
00:04:07,890 --> 00:04:09,410
I bet Jennifer gets a promotion out of this,

97
00:04:09,410 --> 00:04:12,040
which is so unfair because I work twice as hard as she does.

98
00:04:12,040 --> 00:04:13,710
Don't worry, Jerry won't be fooled

99
00:04:13,710 --> 00:04:16,040
by that type of behavior.

100
00:04:19,540 --> 00:04:21,350
Jerry?

101
00:04:21,350 --> 00:04:24,640
It didn't work for Randy, it didn't work for Tina,

102
00:04:24,640 --> 00:04:26,770
it sure as hell isn't gonna work for Jennifer.

103
00:04:26,770 --> 00:04:28,250
Well, I hope not.

104
00:04:28,250 --> 00:04:31,410
I just hate when people play those kinds of games.

105
00:04:31,410 --> 00:04:33,640
Tina?

106
00:04:33,640 --> 00:04:37,590
With your sales record, you have nothing to worry about.

107
00:04:38,360 --> 00:04:41,400
I went to your office Christmas party?

108
00:04:44,370 --> 00:04:47,160
You know, I like harp lessons,

109
00:04:47,160 --> 00:04:51,130
but I'm thinking of switching to elevator repair lessons.

110
00:04:52,320 --> 00:04:53,810
What are you working on?

111
00:04:54,260 --> 00:04:56,130
I was thinking about your experiment

112
00:04:56,130 --> 00:04:58,040
on the neuroscience of decision making,

113
00:04:58,040 --> 00:04:59,180
and I realized,

114
00:04:59,180 --> 00:05:02,460
if we connect it to the measurement problem in quantum mechanics,

115
00:05:02,460 --> 00:05:04,800
we have a chance to disprove the role of consciousness

116
00:05:04,800 --> 00:05:07,530
in the Copenhagen Interpretation.

117
00:05:07,530 --> 00:05:10,270
Wait, are you saying if we combine my experiment

118
00:05:10,270 --> 00:05:11,460
with your calculations,

119
00:05:11,460 --> 00:05:13,520
we can determine the precise moment in time

120
00:05:13,520 --> 00:05:15,310
when the wave function collapses?

121
00:05:15,310 --> 00:05:17,180
It could be the most inspired combination

122
00:05:17,180 --> 00:05:20,740
since I mixed red Icee into my blue Icee.

123
00:05:22,400 --> 00:05:25,880
It was like drinking 2/7 of the rainbow.

124
00:05:26,040 --> 00:05:27,710
Sheldon, this is really interesting.

125
00:05:27,710 --> 00:05:31,300
Yeah, and this one won't stain my teeth purple.

126
00:05:31,300 --> 00:05:34,190
You know, we've never collaborated professionally before.

127
00:05:34,190 --> 00:05:36,570
Are you worried it might affect our relationship?

128
00:05:36,570 --> 00:05:38,300
That is a valid point.

129
00:05:38,300 --> 00:05:41,190
Perhaps we should establish some ground rules.

130
00:05:41,190 --> 00:05:42,560
Well, that would make me feel better.

131
00:05:42,560 --> 00:05:43,520
All right, let's start right now.

132
00:05:43,520 --> 00:05:45,040
Uh, rule number one,

133
00:05:45,040 --> 00:05:48,370
no using sexuality to get your way.

134
00:05:49,390 --> 00:05:50,860
That's a ridiculous rule.

135
00:05:50,860 --> 00:05:52,590
Is it?

136
00:05:59,600 --> 00:06:02,870
Okay, how is that?

137
00:06:07,400 --> 00:06:09,280
I can actually feel the toxins

138
00:06:09,280 --> 00:06:12,490
being pulled out of my skin.

139
00:06:12,490 --> 00:06:14,900
Well, this is a moisturizing mask.

140
00:06:14,900 --> 00:06:16,960
Oh, well, then I can actually feel

141
00:06:16,960 --> 00:06:20,610
the moisture going into my skin.

142
00:06:20,610 --> 00:06:21,410
Hey, I hope you don't mind,

143
00:06:21,410 --> 00:06:23,610
I used a little of your eye cream last night.

144
00:06:23,610 --> 00:06:27,330
I thought someone looked brighter and tighter.

145
00:06:32,110 --> 00:06:34,840
I'd still like to know who Jerry is.

146
00:06:34,840 --> 00:06:36,290
Don't worry about it. Hey, after this,

147
00:06:36,290 --> 00:06:38,310
how about we all go out and do something together?

148
00:06:38,310 --> 00:06:40,730
That would be great. Thank you.

149
00:06:40,730 --> 00:06:41,570
You want to go shopping?

150
00:06:41,570 --> 00:06:43,380
Ooh, yes. Fun.

151
00:06:43,380 --> 00:06:45,720
Or we could do something we'll all enjoy,

152
00:06:45,720 --> 00:06:48,650
like play a board game.

153
00:06:51,280 --> 00:06:55,120
♪ Imagine me and you, I do ♪

154
00:06:55,120 --> 00:06:57,140
♪ I think about you day and night ♪

155
00:06:57,140 --> 00:07:01,210
♪ It's only right to think about the one you love ♪

156
00:07:01,210 --> 00:07:02,520
♪ And hold her tight ♪

157
00:07:02,520 --> 00:07:06,830
♪ So happy together ♪

158
00:07:07,610 --> 00:07:12,460
♪ I can't see me lovin' nobody but you ♪

159
00:07:12,460 --> 00:07:15,510
♪ For all my life ♪

160
00:07:15,510 --> 00:07:18,110
♪ When you're with me ♪

161
00:07:18,110 --> 00:07:20,380
♪ Baby, the skies will be blue ♪

162
00:07:20,380 --> 00:07:23,720
♪ For all my life.♪

163
00:07:24,530 --> 00:07:27,480
I believe I've made some progress on our ground rules.

164
00:07:27,480 --> 00:07:29,430
Oh, good. What are they?

165
00:07:29,430 --> 00:07:30,690
Okay, uh, number one:

166
00:07:30,690 --> 00:07:32,000
in matters of physics,

167
00:07:32,000 --> 00:07:33,620
I have the final say.

168
00:07:33,620 --> 00:07:36,670
In matters of neuroscience, you have the final say.

169
00:07:36,670 --> 00:07:38,580
Unless I disagree.

170
00:07:39,260 --> 00:07:40,240
Oh, here.

171
00:07:40,240 --> 00:07:43,250
Number two: when we publish, my name goes first.

172
00:07:43,250 --> 00:07:46,220
Oh, subsequently, if we win any awards, I speak first.

173
00:07:46,220 --> 00:07:49,360
I don't want to be talking when the orchestra plays us off.

174
00:07:50,170 --> 00:07:51,410
Can I see that?

175
00:07:51,410 --> 00:07:53,420
Oh, of course.

176
00:07:58,480 --> 00:08:00,870
I'll get that back.

177
00:08:00,870 --> 00:08:02,500
Like all my underwear, that notebook says

178
00:08:02,500 --> 00:08:05,220
"Property of Sheldon Cooper."

179
00:08:05,720 --> 00:08:07,410
Sheldon, if we're gonna have ground rules,

180
00:08:07,410 --> 00:08:08,740
I'll tell you the first ground rule--

181
00:08:08,740 --> 00:08:10,950
I make the ground rules.

182
00:08:10,950 --> 00:08:14,210
I'd write that down, but I can't now, can I?

183
00:08:17,180 --> 00:08:18,970
I mean, they didn't say anything,

184
00:08:18,970 --> 00:08:20,340
but I just kind of felt like I was being

185
00:08:20,340 --> 00:08:22,600
a weird third wheel.

186
00:08:22,600 --> 00:08:25,420
Huh, so you can tell what that feels like.

187
00:08:25,420 --> 00:08:27,220
Interesting.

188
00:08:27,760 --> 00:08:30,730
Anyway, I figured I can hang out with my friends

189
00:08:30,730 --> 00:08:32,300
and have fun, too.

190
00:08:32,300 --> 00:08:34,600
Well, if your idea of fun is riding in a minivan

191
00:08:34,600 --> 00:08:35,880
to Target for diapers,

192
00:08:35,880 --> 00:08:39,010
things are about to get nuts.

193
00:08:39,010 --> 00:08:41,050
Oh, it's just nice to be with people

194
00:08:41,050 --> 00:08:42,750
who are happy to have me around.

195
00:08:42,750 --> 00:08:44,570
Isn't that right, Halley?

196
00:08:48,300 --> 00:08:51,110
Well, at least someone had the courage to say it.

197
00:08:53,050 --> 00:08:55,900
Thank you, you are a good citizen.

198
00:08:55,900 --> 00:08:57,900
Told you.

199
00:08:57,900 --> 00:08:59,580
Go ahead, throw my underwear out the window.

200
00:08:59,580 --> 00:09:01,480
Same thing's gonna happen.

201
00:09:02,460 --> 00:09:03,430
Terrific.

202
00:09:03,430 --> 00:09:05,290
Do you want to hear our new set of ground rules?

203
00:09:05,290 --> 00:09:06,880
Fire away.

204
00:09:06,880 --> 00:09:09,230
Number one: we're on the same team,

205
00:09:09,230 --> 00:09:10,800
we're not in competition.

206
00:09:10,800 --> 00:09:15,060
That's smart, because Sheldon 1, Amy 0.

207
00:09:15,780 --> 00:09:18,590
Number two: disagreements can happen politely.

208
00:09:18,590 --> 00:09:20,940
There's no need to call an idea stupid.

209
00:09:20,940 --> 00:09:24,780
Aw, someone drew a penis in it.

210
00:09:26,850 --> 00:09:27,800
Are you listening?

211
00:09:27,800 --> 00:09:29,330
I'm sorry, go ahead.

212
00:09:29,330 --> 00:09:30,540
Number three.

213
00:09:30,540 --> 00:09:33,040
To avoid getting frustrated, we take built-in breaks

214
00:09:33,040 --> 00:09:35,610
and reward our successes with a small treat.

215
00:09:35,610 --> 00:09:37,220
Ooh, that sounds fun.

216
00:09:37,220 --> 00:09:39,080
Now, we're talking about real treats, right?

217
00:09:39,080 --> 00:09:42,510
Not Bible verses like my mother used to give me.

218
00:09:43,080 --> 00:09:44,740
Whatever you want.

219
00:09:44,740 --> 00:09:47,070
So, shall we get to work?

220
00:09:47,070 --> 00:09:49,350
Biology and physics coming together--

221
00:09:49,350 --> 00:09:52,570
this is like the peanut butter cup of the mind.

222
00:09:52,570 --> 00:09:55,270
Oh, I know what I want my treat to be!

223
00:09:56,720 --> 00:09:59,850
♪ Imagine me and you, I do ♪

224
00:09:59,850 --> 00:10:02,550
♪ I think about you day and night ♪

225
00:10:02,550 --> 00:10:04,210
♪ It's only right ♪

226
00:10:04,210 --> 00:10:06,540
♪ To think about the girl you love ♪

227
00:10:06,540 --> 00:10:07,850
♪ And hold her tight ♪

228
00:10:07,850 --> 00:10:12,590
♪ So happy together ♪

229
00:10:12,590 --> 00:10:15,870
♪ If I should call you up, invest a dime ♪

230
00:10:15,870 --> 00:10:18,110
♪ And you say you belong to me ♪

231
00:10:18,110 --> 00:10:19,880
♪ And ease my mind ♪

232
00:10:19,880 --> 00:10:23,810
♪ Imagine how the world could be, so very fine ♪

233
00:10:23,810 --> 00:10:28,280
♪ So happy together ♪

234
00:10:28,810 --> 00:10:30,800
♪ I can't see me ♪

235
00:10:30,800 --> 00:10:33,680
♪ Lovin' nobody but you ♪

236
00:10:33,680 --> 00:10:37,630
♪ For all my life... ♪

237
00:10:38,960 --> 00:10:41,110
Wow, look at that.

238
00:10:41,110 --> 00:10:44,030
Yes, this is remarkable.

239
00:10:44,030 --> 00:10:47,420
So we're agreed: it's complete garbage.

240
00:10:49,540 --> 00:10:52,110
By the way, your name can go first.

241
00:10:57,970 --> 00:10:59,600
I mean, I'm glad they're getting along,

242
00:10:59,600 --> 00:11:01,630
but it's starting to make me uncomfortable.

243
00:11:01,630 --> 00:11:04,110
Well, are you worried he's like another man in her life?

244
00:11:04,110 --> 00:11:07,570
A little, until I saw them in matching tops, so...

245
00:11:08,450 --> 00:11:11,270
Nice. 174 diapers.

246
00:11:11,270 --> 00:11:14,160
That ought to get us to Wednesday.

247
00:11:15,160 --> 00:11:16,800
Well, have you talked to them about it?

248
00:11:16,800 --> 00:11:18,140
Well, what am I supposed to say--

249
00:11:18,140 --> 00:11:20,190
"Stop having fun without me"?

250
00:11:20,190 --> 00:11:22,970
This one says that every time I go out.

251
00:11:22,970 --> 00:11:25,610
See? I listen to you.

252
00:11:27,960 --> 00:11:29,990
Look, Raj just gets along with women.

253
00:11:29,990 --> 00:11:30,790
I-I know,

254
00:11:30,790 --> 00:11:32,360
but he was my friend first.

255
00:11:32,360 --> 00:11:33,770
It's like she's stealing him

256
00:11:33,770 --> 00:11:35,620
and they're just having the best time

257
00:11:35,620 --> 00:11:38,450
doing all their dumb girly stuff together.

258
00:11:38,450 --> 00:11:39,360
You sure you don't fit in?

259
00:11:39,360 --> 00:11:42,080
You sound like a catty bitch to me.

260
00:11:47,790 --> 00:11:49,330
I don't know where we went wrong.

261
00:11:49,330 --> 00:11:51,560
Yeah, the math is so inelegant.

262
00:11:51,560 --> 00:11:54,920
I'm not even sure it makes sense.

263
00:11:54,920 --> 00:11:57,830
Well, don't give up. Maybe we can fix it.

264
00:12:03,540 --> 00:12:05,570
Can you stop breathing so loud?

265
00:12:05,570 --> 00:12:08,100
I can hear your nose whistling.

266
00:12:08,670 --> 00:12:11,910
I can hear your face talking, so we're even.

267
00:12:17,410 --> 00:12:19,370
All right, either blow your nose

268
00:12:19,370 --> 00:12:21,740
or teach it to play "Camptown Races."

269
00:12:22,940 --> 00:12:25,260
Fine. Fine. You want me to blow my nose?

270
00:12:25,260 --> 00:12:26,910
Here, I'll blow it.

271
00:12:32,150 --> 00:12:33,290
Better?

272
00:12:33,290 --> 00:12:35,460
No, I can still hear it.

273
00:12:35,910 --> 00:12:38,710
Oh, wait, that's me. Never mind, it's fine.

274
00:12:38,710 --> 00:12:39,890
You know, you're exhausting.

275
00:12:39,890 --> 00:12:41,820
I knew working together was a bad idea.

276
00:12:41,820 --> 00:12:42,990
Hold on.

277
00:12:42,990 --> 00:12:44,770
I see what's wrong here.

278
00:12:44,770 --> 00:12:47,050
We did the propagation only to the occipital lobe,

279
00:12:47,050 --> 00:12:49,690
not to the prefrontal cortex.

280
00:12:49,690 --> 00:12:52,380
That would mean that this delayed parameter

281
00:12:52,380 --> 00:12:55,550
should be increased 250 milliseconds.

282
00:12:55,550 --> 00:12:58,480
Oh, that is much better.

283
00:12:58,480 --> 00:13:00,540
Yeah, boy, if good ideas came out of your brain the way

284
00:13:00,540 --> 00:13:03,860
mucus comes out of your nose, we'd be in good shape.

285
00:13:07,570 --> 00:13:09,890
Now, take a sip,

286
00:13:09,890 --> 00:13:11,590
swirl it around your mouth,

287
00:13:11,590 --> 00:13:13,720
and try to notice the flavors,

288
00:13:13,720 --> 00:13:17,330
the tannins, the textures.

289
00:13:19,890 --> 00:13:21,100
Well?

290
00:13:21,100 --> 00:13:24,880
I probably should have spit out my gum first.

291
00:13:28,870 --> 00:13:30,790
Yeah. You know,

292
00:13:30,790 --> 00:13:32,960
the last couple of weeks have been pretty rough,

293
00:13:32,960 --> 00:13:34,400
but, uh, staying here with you guys

294
00:13:34,400 --> 00:13:36,060
has really helped take my mind off of it.

295
00:13:36,060 --> 00:13:37,950
Well, we've loved having you around.

296
00:13:37,950 --> 00:13:40,320
Right, sweetie?

297
00:13:42,370 --> 00:13:43,430
Leonard?

298
00:13:43,430 --> 00:13:44,650
Yeah, when did he leave?

299
00:13:44,650 --> 00:13:47,210
Yeah, that's rude.

300
00:13:49,780 --> 00:13:51,540
You know, it's nice to spend time with people

301
00:13:51,540 --> 00:13:55,110
who don't talk about work like it's some kind of soap opera.

302
00:13:55,110 --> 00:13:58,450
Jennifer still trying to sleep her way to the top?

303
00:13:59,970 --> 00:14:02,080
Yeah.

304
00:14:02,580 --> 00:14:05,210
You should be happy someone wants to do the stuff with Penny

305
00:14:05,210 --> 00:14:06,560
you don't want to.

306
00:14:06,560 --> 00:14:08,410
Yeah, I wish I had that with Howard.

307
00:14:08,410 --> 00:14:09,350
Wait.

308
00:14:09,350 --> 00:14:11,490
What? What do I make you do?

309
00:14:11,490 --> 00:14:13,260
Let's see, the magic store,

310
00:14:13,260 --> 00:14:15,150
the Doctor Who convention,

311
00:14:15,150 --> 00:14:18,790
the National Belt Buckle Collector's meet and greet.

312
00:14:19,610 --> 00:14:20,980
It said right there on the invitation,

313
00:14:20,980 --> 00:14:22,150
"Buckle up for fun."

314
00:14:22,150 --> 00:14:24,580
It's not my fault you didn't listen.

315
00:14:26,120 --> 00:14:28,010
I'm sure I'm overreacting.

316
00:14:28,010 --> 00:14:29,910
You're entitled to feel how you feel.

317
00:14:29,910 --> 00:14:32,210
If you don't like it, you should just talk to her.

318
00:14:32,210 --> 00:14:34,510
I don't want to sound like a jealous baby.

319
00:14:34,510 --> 00:14:38,070
Oh, then maybe you shouldn't talk to her.

320
00:14:39,750 --> 00:14:40,530
You know, I had a feeling

321
00:14:40,530 --> 00:14:42,240
you were using the wrong computational model,

322
00:14:42,240 --> 00:14:44,860
but I didn't say anything 'cause you're so sensitive.

323
00:14:44,860 --> 00:14:46,340
Just because I am easily bothered

324
00:14:46,340 --> 00:14:48,610
by light, heat, sound, smell and the way birds look at me

325
00:14:48,610 --> 00:14:50,930
does not mean I'm sensitive!

326
00:14:53,700 --> 00:14:56,120
I wonder what kind of success we'd have

327
00:14:56,120 --> 00:14:59,490
if we defined measurement as the first moment

328
00:14:59,490 --> 00:15:02,780
that an action potential is seen by the visual cortex.

329
00:15:02,780 --> 00:15:06,230
That is a daring and insightful solution.

330
00:15:06,230 --> 00:15:07,560
We're finally making progress.

331
00:15:07,560 --> 00:15:10,010
I wish we could do it without fighting.

332
00:15:10,540 --> 00:15:14,310
What if the fighting is the reason we're making progress?

333
00:15:14,900 --> 00:15:16,640
I suppose it's conceivable that

334
00:15:16,640 --> 00:15:19,280
the hormones associated with our fight-or-flight response

335
00:15:19,280 --> 00:15:22,470
could be sharpening our cognitive processes.

336
00:15:22,470 --> 00:15:24,030
Well, if that's the case,

337
00:15:24,030 --> 00:15:28,020
then your grandparents mumble and have bad posture.

338
00:15:29,620 --> 00:15:31,610
How dare you speak that way about my Grammy--

339
00:15:31,610 --> 00:15:34,110
Hey, wait a second. Wait.

340
00:15:36,830 --> 00:15:41,150
Delta "T" could equal alpha sub-zero.

341
00:15:42,420 --> 00:15:45,340
It seems we have a choice to make.

342
00:15:45,340 --> 00:15:48,560
Abandon all ground rules in the name of science,

343
00:15:48,560 --> 00:15:53,390
or... give up collaborating for the sake of our relationship.

344
00:15:54,070 --> 00:15:55,990
There's only one clear choice.

345
00:15:55,990 --> 00:15:58,610
- Science it is. - No, you bonehead!

346
00:15:59,780 --> 00:16:01,300
Name-calling, that is perfect.

347
00:16:01,300 --> 00:16:02,890
Now, when I get to this equation here,

348
00:16:02,890 --> 00:16:04,170
really let me have it. You know?

349
00:16:04,170 --> 00:16:06,920
I-If it helps, I'm not the sharpest dresser.

350
00:16:10,060 --> 00:16:13,430
Anyway, I know it's silly, but since Raj moved in,

351
00:16:13,430 --> 00:16:16,660
I've been feeling a little left out.

352
00:16:18,750 --> 00:16:21,790
Well, sweetie, that's crazy.

353
00:16:21,790 --> 00:16:23,950
No, no, Penny, don't dismiss his feelings.

354
00:16:23,950 --> 00:16:24,850
Thank you. I just feel...

355
00:16:24,850 --> 00:16:26,370
Hang on, I'm not saying

356
00:16:26,370 --> 00:16:28,770
that his feelings aren't crazy.

357
00:16:28,770 --> 00:16:29,890
I just don't want him to think that

358
00:16:29,890 --> 00:16:31,870
this isn't a safe place.

359
00:16:31,870 --> 00:16:32,570
Well, to be truthful...

360
00:16:32,570 --> 00:16:33,960
Well, why wouldn't this be a safe place? I mean,

361
00:16:33,960 --> 00:16:36,430
he's surrounded by his wife and one of his best friends.

362
00:16:36,430 --> 00:16:37,630
I don't want to speak for Leonard.

363
00:16:37,630 --> 00:16:38,380
Thank you. I...

364
00:16:38,380 --> 00:16:40,370
But when you're insecure,

365
00:16:40,370 --> 00:16:42,020
no amount of external validation

366
00:16:42,020 --> 00:16:43,470
can ever make you feel safe.

367
00:16:43,470 --> 00:16:44,610
Yeah, you're right.

368
00:16:44,610 --> 00:16:47,170
You know, you're really sensitive about this kind of stuff.

369
00:16:47,170 --> 00:16:49,510
- I'm a good listener. - Yeah.

370
00:16:49,510 --> 00:16:51,940
Hey, Olsen twins...

371
00:16:53,680 --> 00:16:54,540
What?

372
00:16:54,540 --> 00:16:56,820
Well, I-I mean, I'm sitting right here.

373
00:16:56,820 --> 00:16:58,230
You're talking about my feelings

374
00:16:58,230 --> 00:17:00,670
and somehow leaving me out of the conversation.

375
00:17:00,670 --> 00:17:03,470
I'm sorry. What did you want to say?

376
00:17:03,470 --> 00:17:06,200
I don't know, you pretty much covered it.

377
00:17:13,080 --> 00:17:15,150
Can you read them back?

378
00:17:15,150 --> 00:17:17,180
"Revised ground rule number one:

379
00:17:17,180 --> 00:17:21,020
We are on the same team, but it is a competition."

380
00:17:22,620 --> 00:17:24,000
Excellent. Excellent.

381
00:17:24,000 --> 00:17:27,320
And on a related point, you're going down, punk.

382
00:17:28,310 --> 00:17:30,270
"Revised ground rule number two:

383
00:17:30,270 --> 00:17:32,890
There are definitely stupid questions.

384
00:17:32,890 --> 00:17:34,610
And those who ask them can be told so

385
00:17:34,610 --> 00:17:37,800
right to their stupid face."

386
00:17:38,750 --> 00:17:40,610
I love that one.

387
00:17:42,350 --> 00:17:44,660
Thanks, babe.

388
00:17:44,660 --> 00:17:45,940
"Number three:

389
00:17:45,940 --> 00:17:48,050
Fair topics for insult include

390
00:17:48,050 --> 00:17:50,690
Educational pedigree, scientific field,

391
00:17:50,690 --> 00:17:54,910
intellectual prowess, and mamas."

392
00:17:55,680 --> 00:17:58,210
Yeah, that list is strong.

393
00:17:58,210 --> 00:18:02,490
Like your mother's urge to be promiscuous with sailors.

