1
00:00:01,390 --> 00:00:02,510
Previously on The Big Bang Theory.

2
00:00:02,630 --> 00:00:04,820
Cohabitation with my girlfriend?

3
00:00:04,820 --> 00:00:07,140
That's a great deal to process.

4
00:00:07,140 --> 00:00:08,390
It's only for five weeks.

5
00:00:08,390 --> 00:00:10,480
Let me appeal to the scientist in you.

6
00:00:10,480 --> 00:00:12,190
Given the five-week end date,

7
00:00:12,190 --> 00:00:15,320
isn't it the perfect opportunity to consider this an experiment

8
00:00:15,320 --> 00:00:17,440
and collect data on our compatibility?

9
00:00:17,440 --> 00:00:20,300
Don't try luring me in with sexy talk.

10
00:00:21,280 --> 00:00:22,150
Okay.

11
00:00:22,150 --> 00:00:23,700
Star Trek: The Original Series.

12
00:00:23,700 --> 00:00:26,490
The Enterprise was on a five-year mission to explore new worlds.

13
00:00:26,490 --> 00:00:27,500
Think of this as your

14
00:00:27,500 --> 00:00:30,530
personal five-week mission to do the same.

15
00:00:30,530 --> 00:00:33,670
If you want to lure me in with sexy talk, that's how you do it.

16
00:00:34,350 --> 00:00:36,220
Okay. Why don't you guys stay across the hall,

17
00:00:36,220 --> 00:00:38,320
and we will live here?

18
00:00:39,480 --> 00:00:41,190
Very well. I'm on board.

19
00:00:41,190 --> 00:00:42,460
- Seriously? - Yes.

20
00:00:42,460 --> 00:00:44,210
I accept this five-week mission

21
00:00:44,210 --> 00:00:46,280
to share a living space with my girlfriend.

22
00:00:46,280 --> 00:00:47,610
Oh. This is so exciting.

23
00:00:47,610 --> 00:00:49,740
Well, now, don't be surprised if, like Star Trek,

24
00:00:49,740 --> 00:00:51,870
it's canceled in three.

25
00:00:55,560 --> 00:00:56,570
Okay, I'm confused.

26
00:00:56,570 --> 00:00:58,380
Which one is Mr. Robot?

27
00:00:58,380 --> 00:00:59,890
I'll give you a hint.

28
00:00:59,890 --> 00:01:02,370
We're watching Daredevil.

29
00:01:02,920 --> 00:01:04,980
Will you two please inform Amy

30
00:01:04,980 --> 00:01:07,930
how much you enjoy adhering to a strict bathroom schedule?

31
00:01:07,930 --> 00:01:08,780
- Can't. - Won't.

32
00:01:08,780 --> 00:01:10,500
- Didn't. - Don't.

33
00:01:10,930 --> 00:01:11,690
I told you,

34
00:01:11,690 --> 00:01:13,990
you can't regulate every aspect of our lives.

35
00:01:13,990 --> 00:01:18,090
I can if you'd just roll over and accept your fate.

36
00:01:18,930 --> 00:01:20,590
I'm sorry for bringing this over here.

37
00:01:20,590 --> 00:01:22,360
Believe me, we know what you're going through.

38
00:01:22,360 --> 00:01:25,070
And I-I think the most helpful thing we can tell you is

39
00:01:25,070 --> 00:01:27,230
no backsies.

40
00:01:27,610 --> 00:01:29,400
Sheldon, I understand

41
00:01:29,400 --> 00:01:30,700
that you like things a certain way

42
00:01:30,700 --> 00:01:32,380
and I'm willing to make some concessions,

43
00:01:32,380 --> 00:01:34,780
but you have to be open to compromise.

44
00:01:34,780 --> 00:01:36,290
She's right. That's reasonable.

45
00:01:36,290 --> 00:01:38,320
Oh, look who's in favor of compromise,

46
00:01:38,320 --> 00:01:41,160
the woman who married Leonard Hofstadter.

47
00:01:41,650 --> 00:01:43,780
Hey, she didn't compromise.

48
00:01:43,780 --> 00:01:46,130
She settled. There's a difference.

49
00:01:46,770 --> 00:01:49,310
Yeah. You tell him, babe.

50
00:02:14,760 --> 00:02:16,480
What time do you and Bernadette head out?

51
00:02:16,480 --> 00:02:18,280
As soon as I get home.

52
00:02:18,280 --> 00:02:19,930
We're hoping to make it before dark.

53
00:02:19,930 --> 00:02:21,460
I've never been to Palm Springs.

54
00:02:21,460 --> 00:02:22,300
Oh, you should go.

55
00:02:22,300 --> 00:02:25,160
It's terrific. I-I really thrive anywhere

56
00:02:25,160 --> 00:02:28,160
the women and the temperature are over 90.

57
00:02:29,270 --> 00:02:30,630
I don't know.

58
00:02:30,630 --> 00:02:32,130
If I want to watch old people sweat,

59
00:02:32,130 --> 00:02:35,270
I can just FaceTime my family in India.

60
00:02:36,660 --> 00:02:39,270
It's nice you and Bernadette are getting away.

61
00:02:39,270 --> 00:02:42,020
Well, she wants us to spend more time together

62
00:02:42,020 --> 00:02:43,310
before the baby comes.

63
00:02:43,310 --> 00:02:45,760
So then what are you doing here buying comic books?

64
00:02:45,760 --> 00:02:48,160
Well, he wants us to spend more time together

65
00:02:48,160 --> 00:02:50,250
before the baby comes.

66
00:02:52,530 --> 00:02:54,870
When you live with someone, there's gonna be conflict.

67
00:02:54,870 --> 00:02:57,290
You just have to keep communicating.

68
00:02:57,290 --> 00:02:59,270
I'm open to that.

69
00:02:59,580 --> 00:03:02,240
Okay. Well, for starters,

70
00:03:02,240 --> 00:03:04,240
there's nothing wrong with keeping our toothbrushes

71
00:03:04,240 --> 00:03:06,470
in the same holder.

72
00:03:07,110 --> 00:03:09,290
Sheldon, what do you say to that?

73
00:03:09,290 --> 00:03:11,370
I think we should see other people.

74
00:03:14,320 --> 00:03:15,150
What?!

75
00:03:15,150 --> 00:03:18,300
Well, as a male, I have an evolutionary drive

76
00:03:18,300 --> 00:03:19,990
to perpetuate my DNA.

77
00:03:19,990 --> 00:03:24,150
Restricting myself to a single partner is against my nature.

78
00:03:25,230 --> 00:03:26,940
We sleep together once a year!

79
00:03:26,940 --> 00:03:29,520
You want other partners?

80
00:03:30,000 --> 00:03:32,510
Don't blame me. Blame your pal, biology.

81
00:03:32,510 --> 00:03:35,080
He's the pervert pulling the strings here.

82
00:03:36,060 --> 00:03:38,680
You wanna see other people? Go see other people.

83
00:03:38,680 --> 00:03:42,080
I hope one of those people is a monkey, 'cause this is bananas.

84
00:03:43,490 --> 00:03:45,120
You can make jokes, but if this keeps up,

85
00:03:45,120 --> 00:03:46,740
- he's gonna move back in here. - All right.

86
00:03:46,740 --> 00:03:48,050
Well, let's just get them apart for a while

87
00:03:48,050 --> 00:03:50,110
- so they can cool down. - Good.

88
00:03:50,110 --> 00:03:51,870
Then before we reintroduce them,

89
00:03:51,870 --> 00:03:52,990
we'll give him one of her sweaters

90
00:03:52,990 --> 00:03:55,600
so he can get used to her scent again.

91
00:03:56,890 --> 00:03:58,930
So it's okay for you to joke around?

92
00:03:58,930 --> 00:04:00,900
No, that's actually what we did with him

93
00:04:00,900 --> 00:04:03,080
when Howard came back from space.

94
00:04:05,220 --> 00:04:07,700
Honey, how ya feeling?

95
00:04:11,120 --> 00:04:13,650
The book says at this stage of the pregnancy

96
00:04:13,650 --> 00:04:16,140
morning sickness should be going away.

97
00:04:20,340 --> 00:04:22,620
So that's good news, right?

98
00:04:23,190 --> 00:04:26,880
The only thing I hate more than you right now is that book!

99
00:04:31,330 --> 00:04:33,670
There she is!

100
00:04:35,050 --> 00:04:36,910
Who's ready for a hot,

101
00:04:36,910 --> 00:04:39,640
three-hour car ride to the desert?

102
00:04:40,560 --> 00:04:43,580
Next vomit is gonna be in your lap.

103
00:04:45,310 --> 00:04:46,460
I'm sorry.

104
00:04:46,460 --> 00:04:48,560
We don't have to go.

105
00:04:48,610 --> 00:04:50,450
But it's our last chance to take a vacation

106
00:04:50,450 --> 00:04:53,040
that's just the two of us.

107
00:04:53,230 --> 00:04:54,920
How 'bout we stay here?

108
00:04:54,920 --> 00:04:56,470
We don't even have to tell anyone.

109
00:04:56,470 --> 00:04:59,930
It'll be like a secret vacation at home.

110
00:05:00,760 --> 00:05:02,660
Keeping secrets from our friends--

111
00:05:02,660 --> 00:05:04,100
that does sound kinda fun.

112
00:05:04,100 --> 00:05:05,870
Does it sound...

113
00:05:05,870 --> 00:05:07,560
sexy?

114
00:05:12,890 --> 00:05:15,740
You just heard me throwing up.

115
00:05:16,080 --> 00:05:18,050
You bet I did.

116
00:05:24,580 --> 00:05:27,030
You're so weird.

117
00:05:28,590 --> 00:05:30,170
You know what's weird?

118
00:05:34,370 --> 00:05:36,900
How turned on you are right now.

119
00:05:39,430 --> 00:05:41,170
You know, people are quick to accuse me

120
00:05:41,170 --> 00:05:42,470
of being difficult to live with,

121
00:05:42,470 --> 00:05:45,850
but the truth is, Amy is just as challenging.

122
00:05:46,210 --> 00:05:47,570
Just as challenging.

123
00:05:47,570 --> 00:05:48,740
Yes.

124
00:05:49,330 --> 00:05:50,730
As you.

125
00:05:51,660 --> 00:05:53,190
Yes.

126
00:05:54,360 --> 00:05:56,170
Just as challenging as you.

127
00:05:58,100 --> 00:05:59,210
When we're sleeping,

128
00:05:59,210 --> 00:06:01,120
she breathes on me.

129
00:06:01,120 --> 00:06:03,130
One night, it got so bad I almost grabbed Toto

130
00:06:03,130 --> 00:06:05,640
and headed for the storm cellar.

131
00:06:06,090 --> 00:06:07,480
Leonard breathes on me, too.

132
00:06:07,480 --> 00:06:08,570
It's not a big deal.

133
00:06:08,570 --> 00:06:11,050
She's always complaining about people at work.

134
00:06:11,050 --> 00:06:12,230
Well, so does Leonard.

135
00:06:12,230 --> 00:06:14,370
It's kind of annoying, but it's not the end of the world.

136
00:06:14,370 --> 00:06:15,990
Do you know that when I get out of the shower,

137
00:06:15,990 --> 00:06:19,260
she eyes me up and down like I'm a piece of meat?

138
00:06:19,260 --> 00:06:21,130
You know, so does Leonard.

139
00:06:21,130 --> 00:06:22,460
Can't I just get ready in the morning

140
00:06:22,460 --> 00:06:24,570
without him giving me his goofy thumbs-up?

141
00:06:27,540 --> 00:06:28,280
I know.

142
00:06:28,280 --> 00:06:30,410
Sometimes I would just like to be appreciated for my mind.

143
00:06:30,410 --> 00:06:33,070
Agreed! Thank you!

144
00:06:37,260 --> 00:06:38,840
That feels great.

145
00:06:39,270 --> 00:06:41,590
Well, pulling a quarter out of your ear

146
00:06:41,590 --> 00:06:44,440
isn't the only magic these hands can do.

147
00:06:46,180 --> 00:06:50,060
In fact, wh-what's this between your toes?!

148
00:06:51,090 --> 00:06:52,000
Can you please stop

149
00:06:52,000 --> 00:06:54,450
making money come out of me for two minutes?

150
00:07:01,630 --> 00:07:02,540
Was that the front door?

151
00:07:02,540 --> 00:07:04,420
It sounded like it.

152
00:07:05,140 --> 00:07:07,080
Oh, my God. Someone's in the house.

153
00:07:07,080 --> 00:07:08,830
Lock the door, lock the door!

154
00:07:11,470 --> 00:07:12,590
We should call the police. Uh...

155
00:07:13,380 --> 00:07:15,020
I left my phone downstairs.

156
00:07:15,020 --> 00:07:16,590
Damn, so did I.

157
00:07:16,590 --> 00:07:18,390
Wait, I have my iPad! What are we gonna do?

158
00:07:18,390 --> 00:07:20,260
E-mail 911?

159
00:07:21,250 --> 00:07:22,520
That's not helpful!

160
00:07:22,520 --> 00:07:24,900
You know I rely on humor in times of stress.

161
00:07:24,900 --> 00:07:27,920
Let me know when you start, because that wasn't funny!

162
00:07:31,610 --> 00:07:33,810
Is that the hot tub?

163
00:07:34,920 --> 00:07:37,090
Who would use our hot tub?

164
00:07:38,250 --> 00:07:41,430
Well, the answer is both more and less disturbing

165
00:07:41,430 --> 00:07:42,970
than you think.

166
00:07:42,970 --> 00:07:44,110
Who is it?

167
00:07:44,110 --> 00:07:45,850
Stuart.

168
00:07:48,980 --> 00:07:51,310
He heard me talking about us going away.

169
00:07:51,310 --> 00:07:54,790
I guess he decided to invite himself over?

170
00:07:54,790 --> 00:07:56,700
Should we say something to him?

171
00:07:56,700 --> 00:07:58,700
Maybe. How 'bout,

172
00:07:58,700 --> 00:08:02,390
"Hey, you look like a boiled chicken breast"?

173
00:08:04,330 --> 00:08:06,990
I meant like, "What are you doing here?"

174
00:08:06,990 --> 00:08:09,290
Nah, that's not gonna hurt his feelings.

175
00:08:12,220 --> 00:08:14,030
Why is nothing easy with him?

176
00:08:14,030 --> 00:08:17,850
Look, here's the thing you need to understand about Sheldon:

177
00:08:17,850 --> 00:08:20,070
he's the worst.

178
00:08:21,190 --> 00:08:23,450
I prefer to think of it as high-maintenance.

179
00:08:23,450 --> 00:08:25,290
I prefer to think of myself as five-ten,

180
00:08:25,290 --> 00:08:27,690
but I still need to get all my pants hemmed.

181
00:08:29,340 --> 00:08:31,550
I guess I should have known what I was getting myself into.

182
00:08:31,550 --> 00:08:33,300
Don't beat yourself up.

183
00:08:33,300 --> 00:08:35,110
You've never lived with anyone before.

184
00:08:35,110 --> 00:08:36,720
- That's true. - And you're starting out

185
00:08:36,720 --> 00:08:38,660
with Sheldon Cooper.

186
00:08:39,320 --> 00:08:41,670
That's like getting your first pet and having it be--

187
00:08:41,990 --> 00:08:43,060
I don't know...

188
00:08:43,060 --> 00:08:46,760
What's a kind of pet that ruins your life?

189
00:08:48,060 --> 00:08:49,840
You're not making me feel better.

190
00:08:49,840 --> 00:08:52,320
Look, even when Penny and I started living together,

191
00:08:52,320 --> 00:08:54,460
there was a-a learning curve.

192
00:08:54,460 --> 00:08:56,830
But I promise you, it does get easier.

193
00:08:56,830 --> 00:08:58,500
He put a sign up in the bathroom that says,

194
00:08:58,500 --> 00:09:01,800
"Number of days without Amy's hair on the soap."

195
00:09:04,500 --> 00:09:05,090
Yeah.

196
00:09:05,090 --> 00:09:07,140
My record was six.

197
00:09:10,970 --> 00:09:12,210
Is it me, or is there something fun

198
00:09:12,210 --> 00:09:15,440
about watching him just float there?

199
00:09:17,200 --> 00:09:20,460
Maybe this is why people get fish tanks.

200
00:09:22,110 --> 00:09:23,960
Who just turned the porch lights on?

201
00:09:23,960 --> 00:09:26,080
Is someone else here?

202
00:09:29,420 --> 00:09:30,920
They must have left the tub on.

203
00:09:31,490 --> 00:09:33,100
Good thing I stopped by.

204
00:10:00,930 --> 00:10:03,440
What are you doing here?!

205
00:10:03,950 --> 00:10:05,940
What are you doing here?!

206
00:10:06,730 --> 00:10:09,330
Maybe Howard and Bernadette said I could be here!

207
00:10:09,330 --> 00:10:10,830
Did they?

208
00:10:11,520 --> 00:10:14,090
Answer the question! What are you doing here?!

209
00:10:15,860 --> 00:10:17,940
I had nothing else to do tonight.

210
00:10:18,390 --> 00:10:19,500
The last couple of months,

211
00:10:19,500 --> 00:10:21,550
I come here when I know they're not home.

212
00:10:21,550 --> 00:10:22,490
What?!

213
00:10:22,490 --> 00:10:23,980
They heard me in the bushes once,

214
00:10:23,980 --> 00:10:26,140
but they thought it was a raccoon.

215
00:10:27,580 --> 00:10:30,660
I told you raccoons don't say "Uh-oh."

216
00:10:33,140 --> 00:10:35,480
You know, one night, Leonard's nose whistled so loud,

217
00:10:35,480 --> 00:10:38,310
I swear it was like sleeping on a train track.

218
00:10:39,000 --> 00:10:42,570
- Have you noticed it's always an A-flat? - Is it?

219
00:10:43,510 --> 00:10:46,530
It's like his sinuses are right here in the car.

220
00:10:47,400 --> 00:10:49,730
If we're just going to drive around aimlessly,

221
00:10:49,730 --> 00:10:51,700
the least you could do is take me for ice cream.

222
00:10:51,700 --> 00:10:53,310
Yeah, I'll take you for ice cream.

223
00:10:53,310 --> 00:10:56,330
Well, see, why can't Amy be that subservient?

224
00:10:56,330 --> 00:10:59,820
She has coitus one time, suddenly she's Gloria Steinem.

225
00:11:01,150 --> 00:11:03,100
Anyway, I suppose an ice cream parlor

226
00:11:03,100 --> 00:11:04,830
will be a good place to meet other women.

227
00:11:04,830 --> 00:11:06,480
Oh, please, you're barely interested

228
00:11:06,480 --> 00:11:08,550
in a physical relationship with one person.

229
00:11:08,550 --> 00:11:11,690
Why would you want to confuse and disappoint others?

230
00:11:11,690 --> 00:11:16,220
Being with Amy has awoken the sexual creature within.

231
00:11:16,220 --> 00:11:19,310
When I see a pretty gal walking down the street, I think,

232
00:11:19,310 --> 00:11:22,120
"Hubba hubba" like any other guy.

233
00:11:22,840 --> 00:11:25,350
You kiss your mother with that mouth?

234
00:11:25,350 --> 00:11:26,920
'Cause it's fine.

235
00:11:30,220 --> 00:11:31,410
Here you go.

236
00:11:31,410 --> 00:11:33,000
Thank you.

237
00:11:34,850 --> 00:11:36,860
Shall we toast?

238
00:11:37,380 --> 00:11:39,470
To Howard and Bernadette,

239
00:11:39,470 --> 00:11:42,750
and the house key they never asked me to return.

240
00:11:44,170 --> 00:11:46,120
You said you got it back.

241
00:11:46,120 --> 00:11:49,230
Well, clearly, I lied.

242
00:11:50,970 --> 00:11:52,210
So how's your apartment?

243
00:11:52,210 --> 00:11:54,600
Not great. The electricity's out.

244
00:11:54,600 --> 00:11:55,820
So why don't you get it fixed?

245
00:11:55,820 --> 00:11:59,890
I called, and they're like, "Pay your bill!"

246
00:12:01,100 --> 00:12:03,560
Of you ever need somewhere to crash, there's always my place.

247
00:12:03,560 --> 00:12:06,320
Oh, no. I don't want to be an inconvenience.

248
00:12:06,320 --> 00:12:08,570
You've got all your lady friends, and...

249
00:12:08,570 --> 00:12:11,400
Actually, I'm single now.

250
00:12:11,400 --> 00:12:12,190
What?!

251
00:12:12,190 --> 00:12:13,280
When did that happen?

252
00:12:13,280 --> 00:12:15,080
It's okay. It's by choice.

253
00:12:15,080 --> 00:12:18,660
Well, their choice, and it's not okay.

254
00:12:19,390 --> 00:12:21,510
Oh. Sorry. I didn't know.

255
00:12:21,510 --> 00:12:25,370
Nobody does. I was embarrassed so I didn't say anything.

256
00:12:25,370 --> 00:12:27,220
Why wouldn't he tell us?

257
00:12:27,220 --> 00:12:28,750
Are we bad friends?

258
00:12:28,750 --> 00:12:31,530
He's in our hot tub drinking our wine.

259
00:12:31,530 --> 00:12:34,700
Yeah, he deserves to be alone.

260
00:12:35,350 --> 00:12:38,170
So you're back out on the dating scene now?

261
00:12:38,170 --> 00:12:39,810
Yeah, yeah, a little.

262
00:12:39,810 --> 00:12:41,910
Oh, that must be fun. How's that going?

263
00:12:41,910 --> 00:12:44,700
I'm in a hot tub with you, so pretty bad.

264
00:12:47,670 --> 00:12:50,360
Maybe I should just give in to his stupid bathroom schedule.

265
00:12:50,360 --> 00:12:52,050
No, don't do that.

266
00:12:52,050 --> 00:12:53,850
- But you did! - Exactly!

267
00:12:53,850 --> 00:12:56,770
Learn from my mistakes!

268
00:12:57,350 --> 00:12:59,420
No matter where I am at 7:18 A.M.,

269
00:12:59,420 --> 00:13:01,920
there better be a toilet nearby.

270
00:13:05,250 --> 00:13:07,430
It's just so much easier to give him what he wants.

271
00:13:07,430 --> 00:13:11,100
Oh, true, but think of how much you've accomplished.

272
00:13:11,100 --> 00:13:14,070
Who got him to stop Purelling his pocket change?

273
00:13:15,020 --> 00:13:15,840
Me.

274
00:13:15,840 --> 00:13:17,600
And who got him to put things other than gloves

275
00:13:17,600 --> 00:13:19,310
in the glove compartment?

276
00:13:20,650 --> 00:13:21,740
Me.

277
00:13:21,740 --> 00:13:23,400
It was mittens.

278
00:13:24,450 --> 00:13:26,500
And who got him to try a turkey dog?

279
00:13:26,500 --> 00:13:27,820
That was actually Koothrappali,

280
00:13:27,820 --> 00:13:30,460
but I did let him spit it out in my hand.

281
00:13:31,110 --> 00:13:33,350
Look, how can you stop now?

282
00:13:33,350 --> 00:13:35,210
That's like walking out of Pinocchio

283
00:13:35,210 --> 00:13:37,870
right before he becomes a real boy.

284
00:13:38,720 --> 00:13:39,820
You know, you're right.

285
00:13:39,820 --> 00:13:41,090
I'm in this relationship, too.

286
00:13:41,090 --> 00:13:42,630
I need to stand up for myself.

287
00:13:42,630 --> 00:13:43,570
Of course you do.

288
00:13:43,570 --> 00:13:46,070
And if he doesn't like it, he can move back here.

289
00:13:46,070 --> 00:13:49,350
Oh. He can try. He'd just need a good locksmith.

290
00:13:52,620 --> 00:13:55,220
Well, who you gonna hit on?

291
00:13:55,220 --> 00:13:56,960
The girl in front of us got strawberry.

292
00:13:56,960 --> 00:13:58,960
That's your favorite.

293
00:13:59,820 --> 00:14:01,910
No. No, if we both like it,

294
00:14:01,910 --> 00:14:04,600
I'll spend the rest of my life opening the freezer and going,

295
00:14:04,600 --> 00:14:06,840
"Aw, no strawberry."

296
00:14:08,030 --> 00:14:10,140
What about the girl behind the counter?

297
00:14:10,460 --> 00:14:12,580
Hmm? Well, she spends her whole day scooping.

298
00:14:12,580 --> 00:14:15,090
One arm's probably bigger than the other.

299
00:14:16,350 --> 00:14:19,760
Is it possible you might not actually want to meet someone?

300
00:14:21,000 --> 00:14:23,460
You are truly wise.

301
00:14:24,190 --> 00:14:25,170
Thank you.

302
00:14:25,170 --> 00:14:26,580
I'd say wise beyond your years,

303
00:14:26,580 --> 00:14:28,930
- but you're getting up there. - All right.

304
00:14:30,310 --> 00:14:33,030
Come on. What is really going on with you?

305
00:14:34,670 --> 00:14:37,030
Penny, I am going to tell you a story

306
00:14:37,030 --> 00:14:38,590
that I've never told anyone.

307
00:14:38,590 --> 00:14:39,870
All right.

308
00:14:40,800 --> 00:14:42,610
I was 13 years old,

309
00:14:42,610 --> 00:14:45,810
and on spring break from college.

310
00:14:49,780 --> 00:14:51,880
Not relating. Go on.

311
00:14:52,220 --> 00:14:53,340
I came home early

312
00:14:53,340 --> 00:14:55,690
because they ran out of math to teach me.

313
00:14:55,690 --> 00:14:57,660
Oh, now I'm with ya. Okay.

314
00:14:57,910 --> 00:14:59,790
My mother was at bible study.

315
00:14:59,790 --> 00:15:02,200
I walked in the house expecting to find it empty,

316
00:15:02,200 --> 00:15:06,150
and I heard a sound coming from my parents' bedroom.

317
00:15:06,380 --> 00:15:07,700
When I opened the door,

318
00:15:07,700 --> 00:15:12,240
I saw my father having relations with another woman.

319
00:15:12,240 --> 00:15:14,820
- Oh, that's awful! - I know.

320
00:15:14,820 --> 00:15:16,270
It's also why I never open a door

321
00:15:16,270 --> 00:15:18,520
without knocking three times.

322
00:15:19,170 --> 00:15:20,720
I mean, the first one's traditional,

323
00:15:20,720 --> 00:15:23,710
but two and three are for people to get their pants on.

324
00:15:24,910 --> 00:15:27,240
Well, what happened with your dad?

325
00:15:27,240 --> 00:15:29,780
We locked eyes, I ran to my room,

326
00:15:29,780 --> 00:15:33,130
and we never, ever spoke of it.

327
00:15:33,180 --> 00:15:34,610
You poor thing.

328
00:15:34,620 --> 00:15:37,050
Since Amy and I have been living together,

329
00:15:37,050 --> 00:15:40,130
we've been bickering like my parents used to.

330
00:15:40,130 --> 00:15:42,920
And you're afraid you're gonna do something like your dad did?

331
00:15:42,920 --> 00:15:45,950
Yes. I need to prepare her now

332
00:15:45,950 --> 00:15:49,350
- to save her from pain down the road. - Down the road?

333
00:15:49,350 --> 00:15:51,630
Sheldon, she wanted to share a toothbrush holder with you,

334
00:15:51,630 --> 00:15:55,030
and now you're at an ice cream parlor trying to pick up women!

335
00:15:56,970 --> 00:15:59,970
Well, anything can sound silly when you put it in that tone.

336
00:16:00,490 --> 00:16:02,980
Honey, instead of worrying about pain you might cause in the future,

337
00:16:02,980 --> 00:16:07,160
how about trying to fix the pain you're causing her right now?

338
00:16:08,010 --> 00:16:10,450
I'm sure you're right.

339
00:16:11,020 --> 00:16:13,990
I suppose I should apologize to you, as well.

340
00:16:14,200 --> 00:16:15,310
Okay.

341
00:16:15,310 --> 00:16:18,060
That must have hurt watching me look for other women

342
00:16:18,060 --> 00:16:20,960
without ever even considering you.

343
00:16:25,210 --> 00:16:28,370
Please understand that I think of you

344
00:16:28,370 --> 00:16:31,360
as more of a nanny.

345
00:16:32,940 --> 00:16:35,930
Just finish your ice cream so I can get you home to bed.

346
00:16:41,220 --> 00:16:42,860
I wonder if this is what it feels like

347
00:16:42,860 --> 00:16:45,610
to be Bernadette's baby.

348
00:16:47,090 --> 00:16:49,740
I don't know. Bernadette's baby doesn't have a Jacuzzi jet

349
00:16:49,740 --> 00:16:52,690
hitting just the right spot.

350
00:16:55,160 --> 00:16:58,980
Those jets are for my secret spot, not his!

351
00:16:59,630 --> 00:17:01,600
What do you do in there?!

352
00:17:01,600 --> 00:17:03,190
It's called relaxing,

353
00:17:03,190 --> 00:17:05,520
and that's all you need to know.

354
00:17:07,490 --> 00:17:10,170
Well, it's getting late.

355
00:17:10,170 --> 00:17:12,350
Maybe we should head home.

356
00:17:12,350 --> 00:17:14,750
Yeah, you're probably right.

357
00:17:16,970 --> 00:17:17,960
You coming?

358
00:17:17,960 --> 00:17:19,970
Yeah, just give me a minute.

359
00:17:19,970 --> 00:17:20,890
Why?

360
00:17:21,130 --> 00:17:24,590
Well, you know how you're wearing a bathing suit?

361
00:17:25,750 --> 00:17:26,730
Yeah?

362
00:17:27,100 --> 00:17:29,810
I kind of went the other way.

363
00:17:30,340 --> 00:17:33,330
You jackasses just bought yourselves a hot tub!

364
00:17:42,910 --> 00:17:44,130
What do you think?

365
00:17:44,130 --> 00:17:45,860
It's a nice enough spot.

366
00:17:45,860 --> 00:17:47,570
You know, if I'm going to start standing up for myself,

367
00:17:47,570 --> 00:17:48,970
this is exactly the kind of thing...

368
00:17:48,970 --> 00:17:51,150
- We're back! - Oh, hi! Hi!

369
00:17:54,090 --> 00:17:55,070
Hello.

370
00:17:55,070 --> 00:17:56,020
How you guys doing?

371
00:17:56,020 --> 00:17:56,740
We're doing good.

372
00:17:56,740 --> 00:18:00,170
I think Sheldon has something he would like to say to Amy.

373
00:18:03,750 --> 00:18:08,180
I wanted to apologize for my behavior today. It...

374
00:18:16,160 --> 00:18:18,630
It was unnecessary.

375
00:18:18,630 --> 00:18:20,920
This is warm.

376
00:18:23,660 --> 00:18:29,660
Oh, and also, I am willing to forego the bathroom schedule.

377
00:18:29,660 --> 00:18:30,530
Oh. Really?

378
00:18:30,530 --> 00:18:33,200
Why does she get that?! We never got that!

379
00:18:33,790 --> 00:18:34,890
Do you want him back?

380
00:18:34,890 --> 00:18:37,020
I'm very happy for you.

381
00:18:38,330 --> 00:18:40,290
Amy, you should know

382
00:18:40,290 --> 00:18:43,300
I was never really interested in seeing other women.

383
00:18:43,300 --> 00:18:46,710
And to prove how serious I am about us,

384
00:18:46,710 --> 00:18:50,810
I'm willing to take our relationship to the next level.

385
00:18:51,960 --> 00:18:53,930
Amy Farrah Fowler,

386
00:18:53,930 --> 00:18:57,780
will you share this toothbrush holder with me?

387
00:18:59,590 --> 00:19:01,830
I would love to.

388
00:19:07,380 --> 00:19:10,300
Did we really need to be here for this?

389
00:19:11,690 --> 00:19:14,680
Call me crazy, but I found it moving.

