1
00:01:45,230 --> 00:01:50,230
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:01:45,230 --> 00:01:50,230
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:01:45,230 --> 00:01:50,230
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:01:45,730 --> 00:01:50,230
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

5
00:01:45,730 --> 00:01:50,230
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

6
00:01:45,730 --> 00:01:50,230
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

7
00:01:45,730 --> 00:01:50,230
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

8
00:01:49,350 --> 00:01:53,970
V

9
00:01:53,970 --> 00:01:58,170
V                                                                      V

10
00:01:58,170 --> 00:02:02,130
V

11
00:00:03,010 --> 00:00:05,410
Aw, man, did you see this post from Raj?

12
00:00:05,410 --> 00:00:07,810
What? Is it another video of him and his dog

13
00:00:07,810 --> 00:00:11,520
Lady-and-the-Tramping some spaghetti?

14
00:00:11,530 --> 00:00:13,530
No. He can't afford his apartment,

15
00:00:13,530 --> 00:00:16,570
and he's asking if anyone knows of a cheap place to live.

16
00:00:16,570 --> 00:00:20,110
I want to say "India," but it seems mean.

17
00:00:22,770 --> 00:00:24,170
What's so funny?

18
00:00:24,170 --> 00:00:26,320
Raj is looking for a cheap place to live,

19
00:00:26,320 --> 00:00:28,870
and I wrote "India."

20
00:00:30,060 --> 00:00:32,330
Don't post that; be supportive.

21
00:00:32,330 --> 00:00:37,180
Maybe you should be supportive of my hilarious jokes.

22
00:00:38,010 --> 00:00:39,620
Fine, what should we do?

23
00:00:39,620 --> 00:00:42,020
We're smart. I'm sure we can think of something.

24
00:00:42,020 --> 00:00:43,850
You want to let him live here?

25
00:00:43,850 --> 00:00:46,500
Oh, we're smarter than that.

26
00:00:47,370 --> 00:00:49,520
I know our apartment's small,

27
00:00:49,520 --> 00:00:51,360
but I think we can make room.

28
00:00:51,360 --> 00:00:52,600
No, Sheldon.

29
00:00:52,600 --> 00:00:57,360
We are not getting a life-size Spider-Man statue.

30
00:00:58,010 --> 00:01:00,090
We do have Sheldon's old room.

31
00:01:00,090 --> 00:01:01,420
If he really needs a place to stay,

32
00:01:01,420 --> 00:01:03,250
I guess we should offer it to him.

33
00:01:03,250 --> 00:01:04,960
You're a good friend.

34
00:01:05,460 --> 00:01:07,550
Am I still a good friend if I wait and hope

35
00:01:07,550 --> 00:01:10,250
that Howard offers him a place to live first?

36
00:01:10,250 --> 00:01:13,470
You're an even better husband.

37
00:01:14,180 --> 00:01:16,420
I know if the roles were reversed,

38
00:01:16,420 --> 00:01:18,370
he would do it for me.

39
00:01:18,370 --> 00:01:19,460
Where would he stay?

40
00:01:19,460 --> 00:01:21,340
We already have Stuart.

41
00:01:21,340 --> 00:01:23,590
Well, we can make some space in the garage.

42
00:01:23,590 --> 00:01:25,500
Maybe put a cot out there,

43
00:01:25,500 --> 00:01:28,430
get him a space heater, maybe a hot plate.

44
00:01:28,430 --> 00:01:29,610
That sounds awful.

45
00:01:29,610 --> 00:01:32,470
Let's hope he thinks so, too.

46
00:01:32,470 --> 00:01:34,330
For the last time,

47
00:01:34,330 --> 00:01:38,990
no Hulk, no Batman, no life-size statues.

48
00:01:40,240 --> 00:01:41,540
I'm starting to think you didn't mean it

49
00:01:41,540 --> 00:01:45,320
when you said you wanted to spruce up the place.

50
00:02:14,480 --> 00:02:15,880
Hello.

51
00:02:15,880 --> 00:02:18,640
Hey, uh, so we've been talking,

52
00:02:18,640 --> 00:02:20,920
and if you need a place to stay,

53
00:02:20,920 --> 00:02:23,690
we'd be happy to fix up the garage for you.

54
00:02:23,690 --> 00:02:25,580
That would be amazing!

55
00:02:25,580 --> 00:02:27,820
I was literally just looking at my moving boxes,

56
00:02:27,820 --> 00:02:30,970
trying to pick one to live in.

57
00:02:30,970 --> 00:02:32,450
I know it's not ideal,

58
00:02:32,450 --> 00:02:34,510
but you'd have plenty of space for your furniture,

59
00:02:34,510 --> 00:02:35,930
and there's this cool button

60
00:02:35,930 --> 00:02:39,090
that makes an entire wall go up and down.

61
00:02:39,090 --> 00:02:41,660
I cannot thank you enough.

62
00:02:41,660 --> 00:02:43,220
It is our pleasure.

63
00:02:43,220 --> 00:02:45,110
Hey, can you hold on one sec?

64
00:02:45,710 --> 00:02:46,540
Hello?

65
00:02:46,540 --> 00:02:49,110
Hey, buddy, you still looking for a place to live?

66
00:02:49,110 --> 00:02:50,960
Uh... yeah.

67
00:02:50,960 --> 00:02:52,990
Why do you ask?

68
00:02:52,990 --> 00:02:54,500
You know, we have the extra bedroom,

69
00:02:54,500 --> 00:02:56,510
and if you need it, it's yours.

70
00:02:56,510 --> 00:02:58,650
Oh, my God, that's so generous!

71
00:02:58,650 --> 00:03:00,200
It's the least we can do.

72
00:03:00,200 --> 00:03:02,060
I-I really appreciate it.

73
00:03:02,060 --> 00:03:04,880
Uh, can you hold on one second?

74
00:03:05,330 --> 00:03:09,440
Hey, so, Howard, what's the bathroom situation gonna be?

75
00:03:09,440 --> 00:03:12,200
Well, there's a sink out there--

76
00:03:12,200 --> 00:03:15,420
that takes care of half your problems.

77
00:03:15,420 --> 00:03:17,810
But I can use the downstairs bathroom, right?

78
00:03:17,810 --> 00:03:21,830
Yeah. We barely use it, so it'll be like it's yours.

79
00:03:21,830 --> 00:03:22,780
Cool, cool, yeah.

80
00:03:22,780 --> 00:03:25,210
- Yeah, hold on one second. - Wh...?

81
00:03:25,210 --> 00:03:28,320
Hey, what's it like sharing a bathroom with Penny?

82
00:03:28,320 --> 00:03:29,660
Is there hair everywhere?

83
00:03:29,660 --> 00:03:32,620
Does she use your loofah?

84
00:03:32,950 --> 00:03:34,160
I don't have a loofah.

85
00:03:34,160 --> 00:03:35,840
Okay, well, if I move in, you can't use mine.

86
00:03:35,840 --> 00:03:37,930
Hold on a second.

87
00:03:38,680 --> 00:03:43,020
Hey, Howard, uh, how's the Wi-Fi in the garage?

88
00:03:43,020 --> 00:03:43,860
I don't know.

89
00:03:43,860 --> 00:03:46,290
Why are you asking all these questions?

90
00:03:46,290 --> 00:03:48,500
Well, to be honest, Leonard's on the other line,

91
00:03:48,500 --> 00:03:50,640
and he offered me their spare bedroom.

92
00:03:50,640 --> 00:03:52,520
Great! Go live there.

93
00:03:52,520 --> 00:03:55,490
But you made the garage sound so fun.

94
00:03:55,830 --> 00:03:57,420
I just didn't want you to feel bad about it.

95
00:03:57,420 --> 00:03:59,300
Unless Leonard's apartment also has a raccoon

96
00:03:59,300 --> 00:04:02,670
that chews its way in on cold nights, go there!

97
00:04:03,580 --> 00:04:04,800
One second.

98
00:04:04,800 --> 00:04:07,670
Okay, I think we're close.

99
00:04:07,670 --> 00:04:10,650
How do you feel about a mini-fridge in my room?

100
00:04:10,650 --> 00:04:12,670
Hey, pal, you want to live here or not?

101
00:04:12,670 --> 00:04:15,630
Oh, uh, hi, Penny. Yes, please.

102
00:04:18,440 --> 00:04:21,500
Uh, Penny, this circular is addressed to "Occupant,"

103
00:04:21,500 --> 00:04:23,040
but with our apartment switch,

104
00:04:23,040 --> 00:04:25,040
it's unclear whether it's yours or mine.

105
00:04:25,040 --> 00:04:26,020
What's it for?

106
00:04:26,020 --> 00:04:26,880
Roofing.

107
00:04:26,880 --> 00:04:29,240
Yeah, it's yours.

108
00:04:29,720 --> 00:04:31,490
Okay, thanks.

109
00:04:31,490 --> 00:04:33,890
"Just throw it out."

110
00:04:35,190 --> 00:04:37,870
Speaking of occupants, I'm given to understand

111
00:04:37,870 --> 00:04:40,180
Raj will be moving into my old room.

112
00:04:40,180 --> 00:04:41,610
Yeah, for a little while.

113
00:04:41,610 --> 00:04:42,960
What about his dog?

114
00:04:42,960 --> 00:04:45,270
She'll be in her crate; it's not a big deal.

115
00:04:45,270 --> 00:04:47,010
I suppose that's acceptable.

116
00:04:47,010 --> 00:04:48,620
Well, Sheldon's getting a little better with dogs.

117
00:04:48,620 --> 00:04:52,330
He even took a picture with Pluto at Disneyland.

118
00:04:52,330 --> 00:04:56,750
If real dogs gave me buttons, I'd like them, too.

119
00:04:56,750 --> 00:04:58,900
Well, I think it's very nice

120
00:04:58,900 --> 00:05:00,700
that you're helping out our friend.

121
00:05:00,700 --> 00:05:03,160
I think it's nice that you're taking whatever medication

122
00:05:03,160 --> 00:05:06,150
Amy's clearly giving you.

123
00:05:07,160 --> 00:05:08,800
And what is that supposed to mean?

124
00:05:08,800 --> 00:05:10,570
Well, it's like that science thing.

125
00:05:10,570 --> 00:05:11,370
For every action,

126
00:05:11,370 --> 00:05:15,230
you have a gigantic and annoying reaction.

127
00:05:16,190 --> 00:05:19,110
Just when I thought you couldn't get any hotter.

128
00:05:20,300 --> 00:05:23,040
If you're implying that I'd have some problem

129
00:05:23,040 --> 00:05:25,080
with him moving into my room, you're wrong.

130
00:05:25,080 --> 00:05:27,800
Raj is in a difficult financial situation,

131
00:05:27,800 --> 00:05:30,350
and I'm glad that he's making changes to improve it.

132
00:05:30,350 --> 00:05:33,130
Do not adjust the dosage. You nailed it.

133
00:05:35,760 --> 00:05:37,500
Don't listen to them.

134
00:05:37,500 --> 00:05:41,310
What's weird is that Penny almost got a science fact right.

135
00:05:41,970 --> 00:05:44,600
I mean, it's unfair; people just assume I'm going to be upset

136
00:05:44,600 --> 00:05:46,810
by Raj moving into my old room.

137
00:05:46,810 --> 00:05:48,490
But you are, aren't you?

138
00:05:48,490 --> 00:05:50,680
Oh, I'm outraged.

139
00:05:51,300 --> 00:05:53,460
Talk to me. Tell me what's going on.

140
00:05:53,460 --> 00:05:56,880
Well, that's been my room since before I met Leonard,

141
00:05:56,880 --> 00:05:59,340
and now someone else is going to be living in it.

142
00:05:59,340 --> 00:06:01,130
And that someone else is not me.

143
00:06:01,130 --> 00:06:04,530
And you know how I feel about people who aren't me.

144
00:06:05,370 --> 00:06:08,060
There are a lot of memories wrapped up in that room.

145
00:06:08,060 --> 00:06:09,850
For me, too.

146
00:06:09,850 --> 00:06:12,160
The first time you told me you loved me was in that room.

147
00:06:12,160 --> 00:06:12,670
Wrong.

148
00:06:12,670 --> 00:06:16,230
We were standing outside my room in the hallway.

149
00:06:16,230 --> 00:06:19,380
And there is the love of which I speak.

150
00:06:19,380 --> 00:06:21,100
I realize it's irrational,

151
00:06:21,100 --> 00:06:25,200
but with Raj moving in there, I'm feeling a bit replaced.

152
00:06:25,200 --> 00:06:28,130
Well, this isn't an easy time for him.

153
00:06:28,130 --> 00:06:30,890
He's losing his apartment, he's in debt,

154
00:06:30,890 --> 00:06:32,680
he's probably humiliated.

155
00:06:32,680 --> 00:06:34,730
Yes, probably.

156
00:06:34,730 --> 00:06:38,270
But until we know for sure, how can I feel better?

157
00:06:39,670 --> 00:06:41,580
Can I get anyone anything at all?

158
00:06:41,580 --> 00:06:43,200
Raj, you don't have to serve us.

159
00:06:43,200 --> 00:06:46,350
It's the least I can do for helping me carry my stuff up.

160
00:06:46,350 --> 00:06:48,100
It was really no problem.

161
00:06:48,100 --> 00:06:51,840
Not for you, Box of Towels.

162
00:06:52,580 --> 00:06:53,950
Anyway, thanks again.

163
00:06:53,950 --> 00:06:54,990
Hey, look at that.

164
00:06:54,990 --> 00:06:57,110
You've got a Raj, we've got a Stuart.

165
00:06:57,110 --> 00:06:58,790
Maybe we should take them both to the park

166
00:06:58,790 --> 00:07:01,190
and let them run around together.

167
00:07:02,660 --> 00:07:06,250
I don't know. Yours looks like he has worms.

168
00:07:07,150 --> 00:07:08,210
You ready to go?

169
00:07:08,210 --> 00:07:09,440
All set.

170
00:07:09,440 --> 00:07:10,550
What's that?

171
00:07:10,550 --> 00:07:13,620
A housewarming gift for Raj.

172
00:07:13,620 --> 00:07:15,930
Well, a bunch of fake snakes better not spring out of it,

173
00:07:15,930 --> 00:07:19,240
'cause that was a lousy anniversary present.

174
00:07:19,240 --> 00:07:21,220
It's nothing like that.

175
00:07:21,220 --> 00:07:23,460
I just, I thought about Raj's situation,

176
00:07:23,460 --> 00:07:25,220
and I had a change of heart.

177
00:07:25,220 --> 00:07:26,580
You know, and regarding your gift,

178
00:07:26,580 --> 00:07:30,800
you said "Surprise me," and, boy, did I.

179
00:07:33,390 --> 00:07:34,640
Perfect timing. Food's ready.

180
00:07:34,640 --> 00:07:36,810
Uh, wait-- before we eat, I have a little

181
00:07:36,810 --> 00:07:38,960
"Welcome to the building" gift for Raj.

182
00:07:38,960 --> 00:07:40,110
Wait, is anything gonna jump out...

183
00:07:40,110 --> 00:07:42,510
No. I already asked.

184
00:07:43,080 --> 00:07:44,780
Thank you, Sheldon.

185
00:07:46,850 --> 00:07:48,540
It's a... blank notebook.

186
00:07:48,540 --> 00:07:50,740
Well, I had some of my best ideas in that room,

187
00:07:50,740 --> 00:07:52,270
and I'm sure you will, too.

188
00:07:52,270 --> 00:07:53,930
He also never had sex in that room.

189
00:07:53,930 --> 00:07:56,880
That's something else to look forward to.

190
00:07:58,730 --> 00:07:59,930
This means a lot.

191
00:07:59,930 --> 00:08:02,080
Well, I know this is a difficult time for you.

192
00:08:02,080 --> 00:08:04,610
Y-You're losing your apartment, you're in debt,

193
00:08:04,610 --> 00:08:06,570
and you just-- you must be humiliated.

194
00:08:06,570 --> 00:08:07,360
Sheldon...

195
00:08:07,360 --> 00:08:08,770
Oh, good grief.

196
00:08:08,770 --> 00:08:11,040
She is such a stickler for citing sources.

197
00:08:11,040 --> 00:08:13,630
Those were Amy's words.

198
00:08:13,810 --> 00:08:14,420
Sheldon...

199
00:08:14,420 --> 00:08:15,660
I know, I know!

200
00:08:15,660 --> 00:08:20,020
"Good grief" was originally said by Charlie Brown, geez.

201
00:08:20,020 --> 00:08:22,110
You're right, I am humiliated.

202
00:08:22,110 --> 00:08:23,340
Thanks for pointing it out.

203
00:08:23,340 --> 00:08:25,330
You're such a jerk.

204
00:08:25,330 --> 00:08:26,830
Can you believe this guy?

205
00:08:26,830 --> 00:08:29,090
Yes.

206
00:08:29,790 --> 00:08:32,590
I-I thought that was gonna break the other way.

207
00:08:32,590 --> 00:08:33,460
Come on, Sheldon.

208
00:08:33,460 --> 00:08:35,120
Maybe we should just eat at our place.

209
00:08:35,120 --> 00:08:36,410
Fine.

210
00:08:37,070 --> 00:08:38,210
You took my room.

211
00:08:38,210 --> 00:08:39,520
You turned my friends against me.

212
00:08:39,520 --> 00:08:40,720
I hope you're happy.

213
00:08:40,720 --> 00:08:41,880
What do I have to be happy about?

214
00:08:41,880 --> 00:08:43,750
My life's a wreck.

215
00:08:43,750 --> 00:08:45,200
How come he can say it and I can't?

216
00:08:45,200 --> 00:08:47,060
Just keep walking.

217
00:08:53,040 --> 00:08:54,980
Hello, Sheldon.

218
00:08:54,980 --> 00:08:56,340
What a pleasant surprise.

219
00:08:56,340 --> 00:08:57,710
How are you?

220
00:08:57,710 --> 00:08:59,700
Honestly, I've been better.

221
00:08:59,700 --> 00:09:00,860
Do you have time?

222
00:09:00,860 --> 00:09:03,180
Leonard says you're very busy these days.

223
00:09:03,180 --> 00:09:06,350
Oh, I just say that because he prattles.

224
00:09:07,560 --> 00:09:08,840
What's going on?

225
00:09:08,840 --> 00:09:12,650
Well, our friend Raj moved into my old room,

226
00:09:12,650 --> 00:09:16,670
and it's brought up a lot of negative feelings for me.

227
00:09:16,670 --> 00:09:20,400
Well, what do you think the loss of your room represents?

228
00:09:20,400 --> 00:09:22,810
Beverly, you know I hold you in high esteem.

229
00:09:22,810 --> 00:09:25,200
Can we skip the part where you pretend not to know the answer,

230
00:09:25,200 --> 00:09:28,660
and get to the part where you tell me the answer?

231
00:09:28,970 --> 00:09:31,120
Very well, but, uh, if you don't mind,

232
00:09:31,120 --> 00:09:34,090
I'd still like to pause for effect.

233
00:09:34,560 --> 00:09:36,860
Now...

234
00:09:37,610 --> 00:09:41,390
You've recently moved in with Dr. Fowler, yes?

235
00:09:41,390 --> 00:09:42,910
I have.

236
00:09:42,910 --> 00:09:46,550
Clearly, your old room represents an escape hatch,

237
00:09:46,550 --> 00:09:48,480
and without it, you're forced to confront

238
00:09:48,480 --> 00:09:51,590
the terrifying reality of being trapped

239
00:09:51,590 --> 00:09:54,970
in a relationship with Amy forever.

240
00:09:55,420 --> 00:09:56,790
I hadn't thought about that.

241
00:09:56,790 --> 00:09:59,850
And don't start thinking about it now!

242
00:10:01,170 --> 00:10:02,720
Hello, Amy.

243
00:10:02,720 --> 00:10:05,900
Your defensiveness may indicate similar insecurities

244
00:10:05,900 --> 00:10:07,910
about your relationship with Sheldon.

245
00:10:07,910 --> 00:10:09,200
That's not true!

246
00:10:09,200 --> 00:10:12,030
She said defensively.

247
00:10:13,350 --> 00:10:14,900
This isn't about me and Sheldon.

248
00:10:14,900 --> 00:10:18,340
This is about Rajesh moving in with Leonard and Penny.

249
00:10:18,340 --> 00:10:20,410
Interesting.

250
00:10:20,410 --> 00:10:24,610
They've found a need to take yet another roommate.

251
00:10:24,610 --> 00:10:28,670
Seems they're avoiding some harsh realities themselves.

252
00:10:28,670 --> 00:10:29,970
I had no idea

253
00:10:29,970 --> 00:10:32,700
all our relationships were such a disaster.

254
00:10:32,700 --> 00:10:33,990
Boy, you're good.

255
00:10:33,990 --> 00:10:36,460
That is the word on the street, dear.

256
00:10:39,500 --> 00:10:41,890
Maybe moving in was a bad idea.

257
00:10:41,890 --> 00:10:44,330
I haven't been here one day, I'm already causing problems.

258
00:10:44,330 --> 00:10:46,620
You didn't do anything. It's Sheldon.

259
00:10:46,620 --> 00:10:48,120
"You didn't do anything. It's Sheldon."

260
00:10:48,120 --> 00:10:51,530
That'd make a nice needlepoint pillow.

261
00:10:52,200 --> 00:10:54,310
So, relax. We're happy to have you.

262
00:10:54,310 --> 00:10:55,360
Thank you, but how do I know

263
00:10:55,360 --> 00:10:57,280
you're not saying that just to be nice?

264
00:10:57,280 --> 00:10:58,820
Do you actually pay for that haircut?

265
00:10:58,820 --> 00:11:01,120
That'll do it.

266
00:11:02,130 --> 00:11:04,760
Hey, Raj, I owe you an apology.

267
00:11:04,760 --> 00:11:07,620
Look, could you please put your dog on a leash?

268
00:11:07,620 --> 00:11:09,940
Sheldon, she's fine.

269
00:11:09,940 --> 00:11:11,060
Well, then at least hold her still

270
00:11:11,060 --> 00:11:13,390
so I can pretend she's stuffed.

271
00:11:13,900 --> 00:11:17,270
Raj, I let my emotions get the best of me,

272
00:11:17,270 --> 00:11:19,700
and I unfairly took it out on you.

273
00:11:19,700 --> 00:11:21,370
Thank you. I appreciate that.

274
00:11:21,370 --> 00:11:22,630
No, I can't take all the credit.

275
00:11:22,630 --> 00:11:25,530
I spoke with Leonard's mother, and she made me feel better.

276
00:11:25,530 --> 00:11:28,950
I don't know who you talked to, but that wasn't my mother.

277
00:11:31,210 --> 00:11:34,770
Beverly pointed out that I'm experiencing insecurities

278
00:11:34,770 --> 00:11:36,300
in my relationship with Amy,

279
00:11:36,300 --> 00:11:40,010
in the same way that Leonard and Penny are in their relationship.

280
00:11:40,350 --> 00:11:42,700
What are you talking about? We're fine.

281
00:11:42,700 --> 00:11:44,790
Yes, you're fine as long as you have a buffer

282
00:11:44,790 --> 00:11:47,320
living with you to distract from your marital problems.

283
00:11:47,320 --> 00:11:48,630
It used to be me.

284
00:11:48,630 --> 00:11:52,310
Now it's Raj and his attack Tribble.

285
00:11:53,600 --> 00:11:55,780
Anyway, I'm sorry for everything.

286
00:11:55,780 --> 00:11:58,640
Oh, and FYI-- if you cry while they're fighting,

287
00:11:58,640 --> 00:12:01,010
they'll take you to McDonald's.

288
00:12:07,110 --> 00:12:08,620
Hello, Leonard.

289
00:12:08,620 --> 00:12:10,920
Why are you saying we have marital problems?

290
00:12:10,920 --> 00:12:12,950
We don't have marital problems!

291
00:12:12,950 --> 00:12:17,840
I see. You must be yelling at me out of wedded bliss.

292
00:12:19,730 --> 00:12:22,550
Look, just because we took our friend in does not mean

293
00:12:22,550 --> 00:12:24,820
that Penny and I are afraid to be alone.

294
00:12:24,820 --> 00:12:27,370
Yeah, this is a special circumstance.

295
00:12:27,370 --> 00:12:29,840
Sheldon mentioned you tried to get your brother

296
00:12:29,840 --> 00:12:31,660
to live with you, as well.

297
00:12:31,660 --> 00:12:34,150
Yeah, well, a circumstance can happen twice

298
00:12:34,150 --> 00:12:36,950
and still be special.

299
00:12:36,950 --> 00:12:38,830
Do you agree with that?

300
00:12:38,830 --> 00:12:40,830
Well, now that you point it out...

301
00:12:40,830 --> 00:12:42,450
Are you kidding me?

302
00:12:42,450 --> 00:12:44,810
We do seem to keep finding roommates.

303
00:12:44,810 --> 00:12:46,490
Now you're taking her side?

304
00:12:46,490 --> 00:12:49,680
Dear, I would never come between you and Leonard.

305
00:12:49,680 --> 00:12:54,320
That's for your parade of roommates to do.

306
00:12:56,440 --> 00:12:57,730
Howard?

307
00:12:59,690 --> 00:13:00,650
Howard!

308
00:13:03,000 --> 00:13:05,170
It's me! It's just me!

309
00:13:05,170 --> 00:13:07,550
What are you doing here?!

310
00:13:07,550 --> 00:13:10,290
Well, I texted you, but you didn't respond.

311
00:13:10,290 --> 00:13:11,970
Leonard and Penny were arguing...

312
00:13:11,970 --> 00:13:14,520
Not on my watch!

313
00:13:15,940 --> 00:13:17,790
It's fine. It's just Raj.

314
00:13:17,790 --> 00:13:20,780
You can hit him with the bat, but it's fine.

315
00:13:21,190 --> 00:13:24,040
And if my heart stops, just let me go.

316
00:13:24,040 --> 00:13:25,430
I'm sorry, guys.

317
00:13:25,430 --> 00:13:28,180
Sheldon was upset, Leonard and Penny were fighting.

318
00:13:28,180 --> 00:13:31,640
I just wanted to go someplace where I wasn't causing problems.

319
00:13:31,900 --> 00:13:33,340
I'll say it again.

320
00:13:33,340 --> 00:13:35,680
India.

321
00:13:38,830 --> 00:13:40,910
Can I just stay in the garage?

322
00:13:40,910 --> 00:13:42,510
Don't do that. We'll make up the couch for you

323
00:13:42,510 --> 00:13:44,190
and figure out something in the morning.

324
00:13:44,190 --> 00:13:45,080
Thank you.

325
00:13:45,080 --> 00:13:47,130
Come on, I'll get you some sheets.

326
00:13:47,130 --> 00:13:48,860
Then we'll see if I can beat my high score

327
00:13:48,860 --> 00:13:51,540
on the blood pressure machine.

328
00:13:54,720 --> 00:13:58,630
Never should've had all these kids so close together.

329
00:14:09,610 --> 00:14:10,790
You okay?

330
00:14:11,400 --> 00:14:14,030
I can't sleep.

331
00:14:14,030 --> 00:14:16,340
What's wrong?

332
00:14:16,340 --> 00:14:17,620
Beverly believes

333
00:14:17,620 --> 00:14:21,890
I unconsciously consider my old room an escape hatch.

334
00:14:21,890 --> 00:14:23,790
Is that bothering you?

335
00:14:23,790 --> 00:14:27,020
Yes. I don't care for unconscious thoughts.

336
00:14:27,020 --> 00:14:28,550
My brain and I are best friends.

337
00:14:28,550 --> 00:14:30,840
It should tell me everything.

338
00:14:31,530 --> 00:14:34,130
I mean, how it relates to our relationship,

339
00:14:34,130 --> 00:14:37,920
not the bromance between you and your brain.

340
00:14:38,840 --> 00:14:40,800
What if she's correct?

341
00:14:40,800 --> 00:14:43,860
Doesn't that say something troubling about us?

342
00:14:43,860 --> 00:14:45,090
I don't know.

343
00:14:45,090 --> 00:14:47,010
I just think you're the kind of person

344
00:14:47,010 --> 00:14:50,650
who likes a contingency plan.

345
00:14:50,650 --> 00:14:52,670
That is true.

346
00:14:52,670 --> 00:14:54,440
Did you know I figured out

347
00:14:54,440 --> 00:14:56,610
in which order I would eat all my friends

348
00:14:56,610 --> 00:14:59,790
in the event of an apocalypse?

349
00:15:01,650 --> 00:15:03,660
You need to stop hanging out with your brain so much.

350
00:15:03,660 --> 00:15:06,500
It's not a good influence.

351
00:15:09,390 --> 00:15:10,670
If you're looking for spare change,

352
00:15:10,670 --> 00:15:12,570
I already cleaned it out.

353
00:15:16,530 --> 00:15:19,170
Didn't think this is where my life would be.

354
00:15:19,170 --> 00:15:20,100
Me, either.

355
00:15:20,100 --> 00:15:22,280
I'm in a bedroom and you're on a couch.

356
00:15:22,280 --> 00:15:24,390
I'm actually winning.

357
00:15:25,510 --> 00:15:26,850
You know, we're both down on our luck.

358
00:15:26,850 --> 00:15:29,230
Maybe you and I should try to get a place together.

359
00:15:29,690 --> 00:15:31,480
Okay, listen to me.

360
00:15:35,240 --> 00:15:37,120
There is no reason to leave here.

361
00:15:37,120 --> 00:15:39,260
This is great. Everyone's nice.

362
00:15:39,260 --> 00:15:40,740
It's comfortable.

363
00:15:40,740 --> 00:15:44,080
If all goes according to plan, this is my retirement home.

364
00:15:44,450 --> 00:15:46,070
Wouldn't you feel better about yourself

365
00:15:46,070 --> 00:15:47,400
if you were more independent?

366
00:15:47,400 --> 00:15:49,280
Better than I feel in their steam shower?

367
00:15:49,280 --> 00:15:51,870
I don't think so.

368
00:15:53,100 --> 00:15:56,340
Penny would be the entree.

369
00:15:57,700 --> 00:16:01,060
Then Leonard's basically a cheese course.

370
00:16:01,060 --> 00:16:05,640
And because I love you, you're dessert.

371
00:16:05,640 --> 00:16:07,320
I want to say "Aw,"

372
00:16:07,320 --> 00:16:10,900
but I'm gonna say "Ew."

373
00:16:11,340 --> 00:16:13,020
No, you see, I'm doing this

374
00:16:13,020 --> 00:16:15,610
so I can stop being spoiled and, you know,

375
00:16:15,610 --> 00:16:18,130
grow as a person.

376
00:16:18,130 --> 00:16:19,360
Good for you.

377
00:16:19,360 --> 00:16:23,240
This sandwich has six dollars worth of ham in it.

378
00:16:25,580 --> 00:16:29,320
Don't you even feel a little bad sponging off your friends?

379
00:16:29,320 --> 00:16:31,840
Hey, look, I went to art college,

380
00:16:31,840 --> 00:16:33,900
I tried to make it as a graphic artist,

381
00:16:33,900 --> 00:16:35,170
a comic book artist,

382
00:16:35,170 --> 00:16:36,830
and you know what I got for my efforts?

383
00:16:36,830 --> 00:16:39,890
A visible rib cage.

384
00:16:40,360 --> 00:16:41,060
I'm not kidding.

385
00:16:41,060 --> 00:16:43,460
You could see my heart beating.

386
00:16:43,910 --> 00:16:46,080
Well, no offense, but I didn't go to art school.

387
00:16:46,080 --> 00:16:48,540
I have a PhD in astrophysics.

388
00:16:48,540 --> 00:16:50,820
Oh, great, it'll be easier for you to look up at the stars

389
00:16:50,820 --> 00:16:53,530
without a roof over your head.

390
00:16:56,120 --> 00:16:57,060
Morning.

391
00:16:57,060 --> 00:16:59,220
Did you know Raj moved out last night?

392
00:16:59,220 --> 00:17:00,560
What? Why?

393
00:17:00,560 --> 00:17:03,250
"Leonard and Penny, I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused.

394
00:17:03,250 --> 00:17:04,840
I went to stay at Howard's.

395
00:17:04,840 --> 00:17:06,630
P.S., Cinnamon's with me,

396
00:17:06,630 --> 00:17:08,280
But if you feel like messing with Sheldon,

397
00:17:08,280 --> 00:17:11,390
tell him she's loose in the building."

398
00:17:13,380 --> 00:17:14,970
I feel terrible.

399
00:17:14,970 --> 00:17:16,380
Should we go bring him back?

400
00:17:16,380 --> 00:17:17,540
Well, you're the one worried

401
00:17:17,540 --> 00:17:20,230
having someone live with us is a sign of problems.

402
00:17:20,230 --> 00:17:22,790
Oh, that was just because my mother got in my head.

403
00:17:22,790 --> 00:17:26,050
It's like being possessed, but instead of Satan, it's--

404
00:17:26,050 --> 00:17:29,400
Actually, it's the same thing.

405
00:17:29,990 --> 00:17:32,260
All right, so we'll ask him to come back.

406
00:17:32,260 --> 00:17:33,700
Well, great.

407
00:17:34,260 --> 00:17:35,790
Don't you want to get dressed first?

408
00:17:35,790 --> 00:17:37,820
Just one second.

409
00:17:43,520 --> 00:17:47,400
Help! Cinnamon's loose in the building!

410
00:17:47,700 --> 00:17:51,240
Amy, quick, lock the door!

411
00:17:53,990 --> 00:17:56,260
We're so sorry if we made you feel uncomfortable.

412
00:17:56,260 --> 00:17:57,980
We really weren't fighting about you.

413
00:17:57,980 --> 00:18:00,370
I just never want to be a burden on my friends.

414
00:18:00,370 --> 00:18:02,020
Me, either. Don't want to be a burden.

415
00:18:02,020 --> 00:18:04,380
Hey, is that the baby? I'll go check.

416
00:18:05,460 --> 00:18:07,030
You are not a burden,

417
00:18:07,030 --> 00:18:08,890
and we want you to come back and stay with us.

418
00:18:08,890 --> 00:18:10,320
But I also upset Sheldon,

419
00:18:10,320 --> 00:18:12,750
and he's not gonna want to come over if I'm there.

420
00:18:12,750 --> 00:18:15,270
More reasons for you to stay.

421
00:18:17,490 --> 00:18:18,790
Halley's fine.

422
00:18:18,790 --> 00:18:21,750
You know she's at my parents' house, right?

423
00:18:23,160 --> 00:18:28,000
And she's having the time of her life.

424
00:18:28,000 --> 00:18:29,890
If you ever want to change things up,

425
00:18:29,890 --> 00:18:31,760
you're always welcome here.

426
00:18:31,760 --> 00:18:35,110
Just not in our bedroom, you dumbass.

427
00:18:36,950 --> 00:18:39,730
I appreciate it, but I think

428
00:18:39,730 --> 00:18:42,560
staying with Leonard and Penny makes more sense for everyone.

429
00:18:42,560 --> 00:18:44,420
- Then it's settled. - And just so you know,

430
00:18:44,420 --> 00:18:45,350
it's only temporary.

431
00:18:45,350 --> 00:18:47,230
I'm not gonna get too comfortable.

432
00:18:47,230 --> 00:18:48,300
Good.

433
00:18:48,300 --> 00:18:51,090
Nobody needs a mooch living in their house forever.

434
00:18:51,090 --> 00:18:54,480
Hey, that's no way to talk about your baby.

435
00:19:01,120 --> 00:19:03,470
You know what? I'm proud of us.

436
00:19:03,470 --> 00:19:06,460
Yeah, with Penny and Leonard taking in Raj,

437
00:19:06,460 --> 00:19:08,490
and Stuart living with Howard and Bernadette,

438
00:19:08,490 --> 00:19:10,710
we're the only couple of our social group

439
00:19:10,710 --> 00:19:11,990
who doesn't need to fill the holes

440
00:19:11,990 --> 00:19:14,810
in their relationship with a third party.

441
00:19:14,810 --> 00:19:17,950
Yup, we're killin' it.

