1
00:00:03,430 --> 00:00:05,080
There was water everywhere.

2
00:00:05,080 --> 00:00:06,290
It was such a mess.

3
00:00:06,290 --> 00:00:08,470
That stinks. How long are you out of the apartment?

4
00:00:08,470 --> 00:00:09,660
About five weeks.

5
00:00:09,660 --> 00:00:11,080
Ugh! Did you lose anything valuable?

6
00:00:11,080 --> 00:00:12,540
Well, the pipe was over my closet,

7
00:00:12,540 --> 00:00:13,790
so all my clothes are gone.

8
00:00:13,790 --> 00:00:15,920
Oh, so nothing. Great.

9
00:00:17,110 --> 00:00:18,750
Do they know why the pipe burst?

10
00:00:18,750 --> 00:00:19,950
They didn't say.

11
00:00:19,950 --> 00:00:21,760
Buildings that have a combination

12
00:00:21,760 --> 00:00:23,520
of copper and galvanized steel

13
00:00:23,520 --> 00:00:25,610
are susceptible to pinholes and corrosion

14
00:00:25,610 --> 00:00:28,940
caused by the mobility of ions in the water.

15
00:00:31,950 --> 00:00:34,790
Can't have your head shoved in a toilet as much as I did

16
00:00:34,790 --> 00:00:38,170
and not pick up a few things about plumbing.

17
00:00:38,640 --> 00:00:41,630
Well, if you need a place to crash, you can stay with us.

18
00:00:41,630 --> 00:00:43,480
- Really? - Of course.

19
00:00:43,480 --> 00:00:45,740
You can stay in Leonard's room, and we'll stay at my place.

20
00:00:45,740 --> 00:00:47,370
You're sure that's not an inconvenience?

21
00:00:47,370 --> 00:00:48,640
No, not at all.

22
00:00:48,640 --> 00:00:50,000
And we live with Sheldon,

23
00:00:50,000 --> 00:00:53,470
so the word "inconvenience" has really lost all meaning.

24
00:00:54,940 --> 00:00:58,440
So, technically, I'd be moving in with my boyfriend?

25
00:00:58,440 --> 00:00:59,540
I guess so.

26
00:00:59,540 --> 00:01:02,530
I'd finally get to live alone with my husband.

27
00:01:02,890 --> 00:01:04,790
Oh, my, this is a big step.

28
00:01:05,300 --> 00:01:08,010
For two of us, it's in the right direction.

29
00:01:12,340 --> 00:01:15,180
Why are you all smiling like crazy people?

30
00:01:41,670 --> 00:01:43,860
Cohabitation with my girlfriend?

31
00:01:43,860 --> 00:01:46,110
That's a great deal to process.

32
00:01:46,110 --> 00:01:47,680
It's only for five weeks.

33
00:01:47,680 --> 00:01:49,380
Yeah, and we'll be right across the hall.

34
00:01:49,380 --> 00:01:50,620
What do you think?

35
00:01:50,620 --> 00:01:52,290
I don't know.

36
00:01:52,810 --> 00:01:56,440
What if living together kills the romance?

37
00:01:57,670 --> 00:02:00,060
Okay, you guys had sex one whole time.

38
00:02:00,060 --> 00:02:03,420
Nothing can put out a fire like that.

39
00:02:04,150 --> 00:02:06,770
Yeah, but what happens when we each get a peek behind the curtain?

40
00:02:06,770 --> 00:02:09,970
I mean, she's never even seen me unshaven.

41
00:02:10,610 --> 00:02:11,570
You just shaved yesterday.

42
00:02:11,570 --> 00:02:13,670
You're good for three months.

43
00:02:14,390 --> 00:02:16,380
Sheldon, I understand your apprehension,

44
00:02:16,380 --> 00:02:18,490
but let me appeal to the scientist in you.

45
00:02:18,490 --> 00:02:20,240
Given the five-week end date,

46
00:02:20,240 --> 00:02:23,270
isn't it the perfect opportunity to consider this an experiment

47
00:02:23,270 --> 00:02:25,290
and collect data on our compatibility?

48
00:02:25,290 --> 00:02:28,370
Don't try luring me in with sexy talk.

49
00:02:29,270 --> 00:02:29,980
Okay.

50
00:02:29,980 --> 00:02:31,740
Star Trek: The Original Series.

51
00:02:31,740 --> 00:02:34,420
The Enterprise was on a five-year mission to explore new worlds.

52
00:02:34,420 --> 00:02:35,320
Think of this as your

53
00:02:35,320 --> 00:02:38,530
personal five-week mission to do the same.

54
00:02:38,530 --> 00:02:41,670
If you want to lure me in with sexy talk, that's how you do it.

55
00:02:43,520 --> 00:02:45,790
Don't be proud of that.

56
00:02:47,190 --> 00:02:48,680
So, is that a yes?

57
00:02:48,680 --> 00:02:50,160
Not yet. I...

58
00:02:50,160 --> 00:02:53,380
How will I learn if I'm comfortable living with Amy

59
00:02:53,380 --> 00:02:55,740
or just comfortable because I'm in my own apartment?

60
00:02:55,740 --> 00:02:57,690
Now, if this experiment is going to be valid,

61
00:02:57,690 --> 00:02:59,660
I suggest a neutral environment.

62
00:02:59,660 --> 00:03:00,930
Well, where would you go?

63
00:03:00,930 --> 00:03:02,530
Well, ideally, an enclosed,

64
00:03:02,530 --> 00:03:05,580
self-sustaining biodome in New Mexico.

65
00:03:06,370 --> 00:03:10,080
Where we would eat crops fertilized with our own waste.

66
00:03:11,680 --> 00:03:14,650
And you were worried about the romance.

67
00:03:15,130 --> 00:03:17,040
Wait. Why don't you guys stay across the hall,

68
00:03:17,040 --> 00:03:18,720
and we will live here?

69
00:03:18,920 --> 00:03:20,240
Interesting.

70
00:03:20,240 --> 00:03:23,300
If my official residence were across the hall,

71
00:03:23,300 --> 00:03:26,700
I wonder if I'd need to knock every time I came over here.

72
00:03:27,590 --> 00:03:28,600
That's a good question.

73
00:03:28,600 --> 00:03:30,740
Maybe just don't come over.

74
00:03:32,700 --> 00:03:35,560
Historically, I don't do well with change.

75
00:03:35,560 --> 00:03:36,730
Okay, it won't be that bad.

76
00:03:36,730 --> 00:03:38,920
We wouldn't even sit in your spot while you're gone.

77
00:03:38,920 --> 00:03:40,320
You're darn right, you wouldn't.

78
00:03:40,320 --> 00:03:42,860
No matter where I am, this will always be my spot.

79
00:03:42,860 --> 00:03:44,790
Like an embassy in a foreign country,

80
00:03:44,790 --> 00:03:48,520
this seat is the sovereign soil of my bottom.

81
00:03:49,280 --> 00:03:51,580
Just nod and smile. He's almost gone.

82
00:03:54,020 --> 00:03:55,650
Sheldon, what do you think?

83
00:03:58,160 --> 00:03:59,820
Very well. I'm on board.

84
00:03:59,820 --> 00:04:01,140
- Seriously? - Yes.

85
00:04:01,140 --> 00:04:02,830
I accept this five-week mission

86
00:04:02,830 --> 00:04:04,830
to share a living space with my girlfriend.

87
00:04:04,830 --> 00:04:06,250
Oh. This is so exciting.

88
00:04:06,250 --> 00:04:08,210
Well, now, don't be surprised if, like Star Trek,

89
00:04:08,210 --> 00:04:10,730
it's canceled in three.

90
00:04:13,080 --> 00:04:16,580
I have to say, I am happy with your OBGYN.

91
00:04:18,120 --> 00:04:20,760
Cool. 'Cause she says you're doing a great job as

92
00:04:20,760 --> 00:04:24,300
"Weird friend who doesn't have to be at every appointment."

93
00:04:24,420 --> 00:04:27,130
I'm the son of a gynecologist. I could be helpful.

94
00:04:27,130 --> 00:04:28,550
It would help if you stopped telling me

95
00:04:28,550 --> 00:04:31,660
I have a textbook cervix.

96
00:04:31,670 --> 00:04:34,890
The polite response is, "Thank you for noticing."

97
00:04:38,980 --> 00:04:40,930
Let me see the sonogram again.

98
00:04:40,930 --> 00:04:44,560
Oh, yeah, that's a good-looking baby for a little gray blob.

99
00:04:44,560 --> 00:04:46,490
Yeah, we could name him Blobert.

100
00:04:47,730 --> 00:04:49,240
What if it's a girl?

101
00:04:49,240 --> 00:04:51,000
Bloberta.

102
00:04:51,640 --> 00:04:53,690
Or Blobbi with an "I."

103
00:04:54,360 --> 00:04:56,820
Are we being silly not finding out the sex?

104
00:04:56,820 --> 00:04:59,410
Yeah, I was just thinking the same thing.

105
00:04:59,410 --> 00:05:01,370
If you want, you can find out right now.

106
00:05:02,010 --> 00:05:04,800
The doctor's gone for the day, so it doesn't matter.

107
00:05:04,800 --> 00:05:08,010
Well, somebody else knows because they saw it in the folder.

108
00:05:08,010 --> 00:05:09,460
You looked in our folder?!

109
00:05:09,460 --> 00:05:10,900
It was an accident.

110
00:05:10,900 --> 00:05:12,830
The doctor left the folder out on her desk.

111
00:05:12,830 --> 00:05:14,870
It's not my fault I opened it and looked.

112
00:05:16,620 --> 00:05:20,280
So you know the sex of our baby, and we don't?!

113
00:05:20,690 --> 00:05:23,300
Flip a coin. You got a fifty-fifty shot.

114
00:05:24,620 --> 00:05:26,050
- It's unbelievable. - God, Raj.

115
00:05:26,050 --> 00:05:27,790
What? This is not a problem, okay?

116
00:05:27,790 --> 00:05:29,880
If you don't want to know, I don't have to tell you.

117
00:05:29,880 --> 00:05:31,950
We don't want you to know!

118
00:05:31,950 --> 00:05:34,230
Okay, well, that's a problem.

119
00:05:37,570 --> 00:05:40,030
You know, I'm very proud of you for trying to live with Amy.

120
00:05:40,060 --> 00:05:41,480
Oh. Thank you.

121
00:05:41,480 --> 00:05:44,060
Of course, the ideal way to conduct this experiment

122
00:05:44,060 --> 00:05:47,420
would be with four pairs of identical Sheldons and Amys.

123
00:05:47,420 --> 00:05:50,180
One pair that was neither dating nor living together.

124
00:05:50,180 --> 00:05:52,610
One pair that was dating but not living together.

125
00:05:52,610 --> 00:05:54,340
One pair that was living together but not dating.

126
00:05:54,340 --> 00:05:55,270
And then, of course, one pair

127
00:05:55,270 --> 00:05:57,240
that was living together and dating.

128
00:05:57,240 --> 00:05:58,540
Although, with that many Sheldons,

129
00:05:58,540 --> 00:06:01,990
it'd be such a party, we'd never get anything done.

130
00:06:02,680 --> 00:06:04,050
That was a cute story.

131
00:06:04,050 --> 00:06:04,840
So, um...

132
00:06:06,900 --> 00:06:08,350
What did you want to ask me?

133
00:06:08,350 --> 00:06:11,660
Well, you've lived with your significant other for some time.

134
00:06:11,660 --> 00:06:13,900
I would like this experiment to go well.

135
00:06:14,090 --> 00:06:16,530
Are there any insights you can share?

136
00:06:17,140 --> 00:06:19,950
Well, the biggie is, if she has an insane roommate,

137
00:06:19,950 --> 00:06:22,170
kick him out as soon as possible.

138
00:06:23,480 --> 00:06:27,280
You know, Leonard and I were very happy before you came along.

139
00:06:28,050 --> 00:06:29,860
You've been roommates with Sheldon forever.

140
00:06:29,860 --> 00:06:31,870
Do you have any advice?

141
00:06:33,280 --> 00:06:34,420
I'm trying to think of an answer

142
00:06:34,420 --> 00:06:36,810
that won't stop you from doing this.

143
00:06:37,700 --> 00:06:39,190
I know it sounds like a cliche

144
00:06:39,190 --> 00:06:40,650
but compromise is key.

145
00:06:40,650 --> 00:06:42,560
Never leave a belt on the floor.

146
00:06:42,560 --> 00:06:44,850
At night, they look like snakes.

147
00:06:45,170 --> 00:06:47,830
Do little things, like bring her a cup of coffee in bed.

148
00:06:47,830 --> 00:06:49,320
Keep M&M'S in your pocket

149
00:06:49,320 --> 00:06:51,730
in case you have to wait in a long line.

150
00:06:52,770 --> 00:06:54,480
You're gonna be seeing each other a lot,

151
00:06:54,480 --> 00:06:56,830
so respect each other's personal space.

152
00:06:56,830 --> 00:07:01,560
He startles easily, so, please, no flash photography.

153
00:07:04,990 --> 00:07:08,210
How many pairs of underwear did you pack for the move?

154
00:07:08,470 --> 00:07:10,310
I don't know. I didn't count.

155
00:07:10,820 --> 00:07:13,940
You truly are the Goofus to my Gallant.

156
00:07:15,570 --> 00:07:17,290
That's me.  Listen,

157
00:07:19,640 --> 00:07:22,110
you and I are gonna be sharing a bed.

158
00:07:22,110 --> 00:07:25,000
You know, this is uncharted territory for both of us.

159
00:07:25,000 --> 00:07:27,250
How are you feeling about that?

160
00:07:27,640 --> 00:07:29,760
Oh, excited, concerned,

161
00:07:29,760 --> 00:07:30,900
a little scared.

162
00:07:30,900 --> 00:07:34,500
All the same emotions I feel in line at Space Mountain.

163
00:07:36,540 --> 00:07:39,140
Well, if you're nervous about the sleeping arrangements,

164
00:07:39,140 --> 00:07:41,400
maybe we should talk about it.

165
00:07:41,400 --> 00:07:42,710
Okay.

166
00:07:46,390 --> 00:07:47,410
Talk.

167
00:07:48,480 --> 00:07:50,890
Well, I imagine one of your concerns

168
00:07:50,890 --> 00:07:53,130
might be coital expectations.

169
00:07:53,130 --> 00:07:56,120
Wow, no foreplay or anything, just right to it.

170
00:07:57,130 --> 00:07:58,580
Look, I know this experiment

171
00:07:58,580 --> 00:08:01,280
is a big step outside of your comfort zone.

172
00:08:01,280 --> 00:08:04,830
So why don't we take being physical off the table

173
00:08:04,830 --> 00:08:06,390
and maybe later on,

174
00:08:06,390 --> 00:08:09,920
once we're more settled in, we can revisit it.

175
00:08:10,600 --> 00:08:12,360
You're really okay with that?

176
00:08:12,360 --> 00:08:13,990
I've never lived with someone, either.

177
00:08:13,990 --> 00:08:16,180
This is a lot for me, too.

178
00:08:17,140 --> 00:08:19,060
This is such a relief.

179
00:08:19,060 --> 00:08:20,510
Honestly, if it didn't get you all worked up,

180
00:08:20,510 --> 00:08:22,580
I'd kiss you right now.

181
00:08:25,150 --> 00:08:26,020
Good call.

182
00:08:26,020 --> 00:08:27,490
Seeing your Teen Titans underwear

183
00:08:27,490 --> 00:08:29,580
really got my motor running.

184
00:08:30,330 --> 00:08:33,510
I know. They probably shouldn't sell those to children.

185
00:08:36,350 --> 00:08:37,560
Well, here's your key.

186
00:08:37,560 --> 00:08:38,860
Thank you.

187
00:08:38,860 --> 00:08:41,200
Enjoy having the place to yourselves.

188
00:08:41,200 --> 00:08:42,870
You enjoy your mission to boldly go

189
00:08:42,870 --> 00:08:45,530
where no man has gone before.

190
00:08:47,240 --> 00:08:48,550
It's Penny's bedroom.

191
00:08:48,550 --> 00:08:51,420
Plenty of men have gone before.

192
00:08:53,470 --> 00:08:56,810
Now, now, there's no need to make this emotional.

193
00:08:57,660 --> 00:08:59,350
Shall we?

194
00:09:00,260 --> 00:09:01,940
I guess this is it.

195
00:09:01,940 --> 00:09:03,100
You guys have fun.

196
00:09:03,100 --> 00:09:04,540
You, too.

197
00:09:07,800 --> 00:09:08,790
Oh, don't forget.

198
00:09:08,790 --> 00:09:10,750
Tuesday the air filters need to be changed.

199
00:09:10,750 --> 00:09:12,350
Yeah, you wrote it on my hand.

200
00:09:16,100 --> 00:09:17,110
Oh, and every other day,

201
00:09:17,110 --> 00:09:19,050
check the water level on the avocado pit.

202
00:09:19,050 --> 00:09:19,740
I'm on it.

203
00:09:19,740 --> 00:09:22,770
15 years from now, we'll make guacamole together.

204
00:09:23,310 --> 00:09:25,610
Leonard, please, let me go.

205
00:09:30,510 --> 00:09:32,080
Come on, Sheldon.

206
00:09:33,870 --> 00:09:34,880
Oh. Bye.

207
00:09:34,880 --> 00:09:37,180
- Good night. - Good night.

208
00:09:41,470 --> 00:09:42,260
Well, that's it.

209
00:09:42,260 --> 00:09:45,190
For the next five weeks, we are officially living together.

210
00:09:45,190 --> 00:09:47,780
I guess the experiment begins.

211
00:09:47,780 --> 00:09:50,120
- We did it! - Yeah!

212
00:09:55,790 --> 00:09:58,050
Which side of the bed would you prefer?

213
00:09:58,050 --> 00:09:59,780
Doesn't matter to me. Your choice.

214
00:09:59,780 --> 00:10:02,890
No, no, we're living together now-- everything's equal.

215
00:10:02,890 --> 00:10:04,940
You know? I know that I have a tendency to be controlling,

216
00:10:04,940 --> 00:10:06,830
so I would rather you choose.

217
00:10:06,830 --> 00:10:08,430
Well, Sheldon, I really appreciate that,

218
00:10:08,430 --> 00:10:10,240
but these things mean more to you than they do to me,

219
00:10:10,240 --> 00:10:11,760
so whatever you want.

220
00:10:11,760 --> 00:10:13,650
Well, clearly, it's not whatever I want,

221
00:10:13,650 --> 00:10:15,500
because what I want is for you to make this decision,

222
00:10:15,500 --> 00:10:17,270
and you refuse to do that.

223
00:10:18,170 --> 00:10:19,280
Well, I'm not refusing.

224
00:10:19,280 --> 00:10:20,920
I'm just trying to be considerate.

225
00:10:20,920 --> 00:10:22,460
Like when you let me get those shoes

226
00:10:22,460 --> 00:10:23,400
with the wheels on the bottom,

227
00:10:23,400 --> 00:10:25,740
and then watched me roll right into traffic?

228
00:10:26,150 --> 00:10:28,490
- Sheldon, will you please just pick a side? - Fine.

229
00:10:34,680 --> 00:10:37,170
Okay. Now, on this side,

230
00:10:37,170 --> 00:10:40,750
I am closer to the exit in case of emergency.

231
00:10:41,120 --> 00:10:43,040
Great. That's your side.

232
00:10:43,040 --> 00:10:47,010
No, but I'm also closer to the entrance in case of attack.

233
00:10:48,190 --> 00:10:49,750
Okay, I'll take that side.

234
00:10:49,750 --> 00:10:51,510
Ah, then again, what are the odds of someone attacking me?

235
00:10:51,510 --> 00:10:53,350
Rising rapidly.

236
00:10:56,190 --> 00:10:59,920
Now, this side offers me proximity to the bathroom,

237
00:10:59,920 --> 00:11:01,880
but I am closer to the window

238
00:11:01,880 --> 00:11:04,670
where perverts can watch me sleep.

239
00:11:05,690 --> 00:11:06,480
Okay.

240
00:11:06,480 --> 00:11:09,020
What if we do this?

241
00:11:11,350 --> 00:11:12,870
I suppose that works.

242
00:11:12,870 --> 00:11:13,950
Great.

243
00:11:18,050 --> 00:11:21,230
Although now I'm kind of worried someone's hiding behind those drapes.

244
00:11:24,960 --> 00:11:26,440
This is ridiculous.

245
00:11:26,440 --> 00:11:28,300
The doctor knows what the baby is,

246
00:11:28,300 --> 00:11:30,790
the ultrasound tech knows, Raj knows,

247
00:11:30,790 --> 00:11:35,050
his Grey's Anatomy online fan group probably knows.

248
00:11:36,270 --> 00:11:38,330
Is it weird we don't?

249
00:11:38,330 --> 00:11:39,900
I don't know.

250
00:11:39,900 --> 00:11:42,360
Maybe the surprise will make it more fun.

251
00:11:42,360 --> 00:11:43,960
Like magic tricks.

252
00:11:43,960 --> 00:11:45,730
Remember how disappointed you were

253
00:11:45,730 --> 00:11:47,940
when I explained the never-ending hanky?

254
00:11:47,940 --> 00:11:50,530
I was disappointed to see the man I was engaged to

255
00:11:50,530 --> 00:11:53,590
pulling rainbow scarves out of his fly.

256
00:11:55,670 --> 00:11:58,620
But how delightful was it when I pulled out

257
00:11:58,620 --> 00:12:01,080
a bouquet at the end of those scarves?

258
00:12:02,220 --> 00:12:03,440
It'll be the same thing

259
00:12:03,440 --> 00:12:06,980
when the doctor pulls a beautiful surprise out of you.

260
00:12:08,450 --> 00:12:11,050
Everyone said I could do better.

261
00:12:12,470 --> 00:12:14,960
But you didn't listen, and presto change-o,

262
00:12:14,960 --> 00:12:17,330
my baby's inside you. Ta-da!

263
00:12:27,580 --> 00:12:29,530
Ugh. What is that?

264
00:12:38,230 --> 00:12:39,300
Why'd you switch sides?

265
00:12:39,300 --> 00:12:41,600
Be grateful I'm still in the room.

266
00:12:48,920 --> 00:12:49,910
Comfy?

267
00:12:49,910 --> 00:12:51,810
Oh, I'm just happy I don't know

268
00:12:51,810 --> 00:12:54,160
what this memory foam remembers.

269
00:12:55,050 --> 00:12:56,250
Sheldon?

270
00:12:56,250 --> 00:12:58,410
I know we took coitus off the table,

271
00:12:58,410 --> 00:13:01,560
but I was wondering how you feel about other forms of intimacy,

272
00:13:01,560 --> 00:13:03,210
such as snuggling.

273
00:13:03,210 --> 00:13:04,830
Well, it's funny you should ask,

274
00:13:04,830 --> 00:13:07,320
because I was wondering how you'd feel

275
00:13:07,320 --> 00:13:11,730
about separating the two of us with a pillow wall.

276
00:13:12,390 --> 00:13:16,250
Sheldon, I've made more than enough accommodations for you.

277
00:13:16,250 --> 00:13:17,540
We're both grown adults--

278
00:13:17,540 --> 00:13:19,910
we've been far more intimate than this.

279
00:13:19,910 --> 00:13:21,250
If you don't want to snuggle, fine--

280
00:13:21,250 --> 00:13:22,690
but we're not building a pillow wall.

281
00:13:22,690 --> 00:13:24,350
Okay, well, I am sorry.

282
00:13:24,350 --> 00:13:26,860
I'm just worried that my sensitivity to temperature

283
00:13:26,860 --> 00:13:28,540
could make this a rough night.

284
00:13:28,540 --> 00:13:30,900
And no offense, but your bottom radiates enough heat,

285
00:13:30,900 --> 00:13:33,760
I'm surprised there aren't iguanas lying on it.

286
00:13:37,790 --> 00:13:40,040
That's it. It's Sheldon's bedtime.

287
00:13:40,040 --> 00:13:41,870
He is in for the night.

288
00:13:41,870 --> 00:13:44,940
Wow. I cannot believe we are alone in our own apartment.

289
00:13:44,940 --> 00:13:46,240
It's weird.

290
00:13:46,240 --> 00:13:47,370
This must be how parents feel

291
00:13:47,370 --> 00:13:49,620
when their kid goes off to college.

292
00:13:51,120 --> 00:13:53,620
Unless they feel sad-- then it's different.

293
00:13:54,400 --> 00:13:56,040
So, what do you want to do?

294
00:13:56,530 --> 00:13:59,830
I know exactly what we are gonna do.

295
00:13:59,830 --> 00:14:01,150
Really? You're a genius,

296
00:14:01,150 --> 00:14:03,480
and that's the first thing you come up with?

297
00:14:04,820 --> 00:14:06,410
Hey, Sheldon's not here,

298
00:14:06,410 --> 00:14:08,360
so we are going to put on music

299
00:14:08,360 --> 00:14:10,730
and dance in our underwear.

300
00:14:11,660 --> 00:14:14,440
Ugh. Can we just have sex?

301
00:14:15,840 --> 00:14:17,370
Oh, don't worry.

302
00:14:17,370 --> 00:14:21,120
Once you see my sweet moves, sex is inevitable.

303
00:14:38,910 --> 00:14:41,120
Inevitable, you say?

304
00:14:42,370 --> 00:14:44,250
I'll just let my hips do the talkin'.

305
00:14:51,490 --> 00:14:53,270
Screw it. I'm calling and finding out.

306
00:14:53,270 --> 00:14:54,870
Good. Call him.

307
00:14:58,860 --> 00:15:00,400
Wait, I'm not sure I want to know.

308
00:15:00,400 --> 00:15:01,820
But you just said you wanted to know.

309
00:15:01,820 --> 00:15:04,100
Well, now I don't know if I want to know!

310
00:15:05,460 --> 00:15:06,300
Hello?

311
00:15:06,300 --> 00:15:07,610
Call you back.

312
00:15:09,690 --> 00:15:11,580
No, Dr. Feynman.

313
00:15:11,580 --> 00:15:15,240
If I solve it for you, you'll never learn.

314
00:15:25,700 --> 00:15:27,690
Wow! Where did you learn these moves?

315
00:15:27,690 --> 00:15:30,180
The world may have forgotten about Dance Dance Revolution,

316
00:15:30,180 --> 00:15:33,710
but not this smooth criminal.

317
00:15:35,800 --> 00:15:37,700
Okay, you're positive you want to know?

318
00:15:37,700 --> 00:15:40,640
- Yes. - Okay. Here we go.

319
00:15:41,050 --> 00:15:42,210
It's ringing.

320
00:15:45,850 --> 00:15:46,630
Hello?

321
00:15:46,630 --> 00:15:48,640
- Wait. - Wrong number.

322
00:16:27,820 --> 00:16:30,560
I told you not to do the worm.

323
00:16:31,990 --> 00:16:33,530
You were right.

324
00:16:38,600 --> 00:16:39,540
Hello.

325
00:16:39,540 --> 00:16:42,050
I changed my mind! Hang up! Hang up!

326
00:17:10,510 --> 00:17:13,090
- What are you doing down there? - Hang on.

327
00:17:13,090 --> 00:17:14,680
Who are you calling?

328
00:17:23,760 --> 00:17:24,700
I'm so sore.

329
00:17:24,700 --> 00:17:27,490
I don't think I slept two minutes last night.

330
00:17:32,510 --> 00:17:35,200
Yeah, get it, girl.

331
00:17:37,030 --> 00:17:39,130
It's not what you think.

332
00:17:39,130 --> 00:17:40,720
I feel like I pulled something.

333
00:17:40,720 --> 00:17:43,010
Why didn't you tell me to stop?

334
00:17:44,520 --> 00:17:47,230
Even more not what you think.

335
00:17:48,120 --> 00:17:51,330
I don't know if I can make it through five weeks living with him.

336
00:17:51,330 --> 00:17:53,750
If you ever need a break, the owner of the train store

337
00:17:53,750 --> 00:17:56,770
- will let you leave him there while you get a coffee. - Yeah.

338
00:17:57,580 --> 00:17:59,270
Good morning.

339
00:17:59,270 --> 00:18:01,270
See? I didn't knock, but it's fine.

340
00:18:01,270 --> 00:18:03,520
I didn't knock, but it's fine. I didn't knock, but it's fine.

341
00:18:04,910 --> 00:18:06,650
So, how is everyone?

342
00:18:06,650 --> 00:18:08,590
Miserable and exhausted.

343
00:18:08,590 --> 00:18:11,260
Really? I slept great.

344
00:18:11,470 --> 00:18:13,630
Well, I didn't, and it's your fault.

345
00:18:13,630 --> 00:18:17,160
How? You had the whole floor to yourself.

346
00:18:19,110 --> 00:18:22,670
Sheldon, maybe living together is a bad idea.

347
00:18:22,980 --> 00:18:25,190
Well... Yeah, but what kind of scientists would we be,

348
00:18:25,190 --> 00:18:27,960
drawing a conclusion after only 12 hours of data?

349
00:18:27,960 --> 00:18:31,290
The kind who almost put a pillow over your face last night.

350
00:18:34,310 --> 00:18:36,820
I anticipated we'd have problems,

351
00:18:36,820 --> 00:18:40,150
but I never thought your scientific rigor would be one of them.

352
00:18:40,150 --> 00:18:43,370
I'm sorry, are you questioning my integrity as a scientist?

353
00:18:43,370 --> 00:18:47,510
If the lab room disposable shoe cover fits.

354
00:18:48,420 --> 00:18:49,440
Was that a science diss?

355
00:18:49,440 --> 00:18:50,640
- Yeah. - Was it a good one?

356
00:18:53,000 --> 00:18:54,560
What would a theoretical physicist

357
00:18:54,560 --> 00:18:56,740
understand about an experiment anyway?

358
00:18:56,740 --> 00:18:58,520
I mean, you wouldn't know a confounding variable

359
00:18:58,520 --> 00:19:02,230
if two of them hit you in the face at the same time!

360
00:19:02,990 --> 00:19:04,260
And you don't even get that joke,

361
00:19:04,260 --> 00:19:07,140
'cause you don't even work with confounding variables!

362
00:19:08,310 --> 00:19:09,860
How dare you?

363
00:19:09,860 --> 00:19:10,730
Oh, you heard me.

364
00:19:10,730 --> 00:19:13,230
Your experimental bona fides are laughable.

365
00:19:13,230 --> 00:19:16,110
Whoa, whoa! Now you're making fun of my bona fides?

366
00:19:16,730 --> 00:19:19,770
Can't make fun of something that's a null set.

367
00:19:21,210 --> 00:19:22,920
- I feel like I should say "Damn." - Do it.

368
00:19:22,920 --> 00:19:24,810
Damn!

369
00:19:25,370 --> 00:19:28,470
Well, if you are so protective of the scientific method,

370
00:19:28,470 --> 00:19:30,240
perhaps we should use the next five weeks

371
00:19:30,240 --> 00:19:31,430
to finish what we started.

372
00:19:31,430 --> 00:19:33,440
Well, for science, maybe I will!

373
00:19:33,440 --> 00:19:34,960
For science, maybe you should!

374
00:19:34,960 --> 00:19:35,710
- Fine! - Fine!

375
00:19:35,710 --> 00:19:37,300
- Good. - Great.

376
00:19:38,040 --> 00:19:39,620
Do you want to go to our place and make out?

377
00:19:39,620 --> 00:19:42,350
Does Stephen Hawking roll through the quad?

378
00:19:49,020 --> 00:19:51,520
The new neighbors are weird.

