1
00:00:03,930 --> 00:00:06,760
Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.

2
00:00:06,770 --> 00:00:08,670
And I'm Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler.

3
00:00:08,670 --> 00:00:11,740
And welcome to the first "on location" episode of

4
00:00:11,740 --> 00:00:15,210
Dr. Sheldon Cooper and Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler present:

5
00:00:15,210 --> 00:00:18,420
Dr. Sheldon Cooper's Fun with Flags.

6
00:00:20,280 --> 00:00:21,410
Hit it.

7
00:00:22,450 --> 00:00:24,210
♪ For joy and fun ♪

8
00:00:24,210 --> 00:00:25,900
♪ There's no better manner ♪

9
00:00:25,900 --> 00:00:28,080
♪ Than to fly a pennant ♪

10
00:00:28,080 --> 00:00:29,780
♪ Flag or banner ♪

11
00:00:29,780 --> 00:00:31,090
♪ What fills my heart ♪

12
00:00:31,090 --> 00:00:33,090
♪ And makes my eyes moist ♪

13
00:00:33,090 --> 00:00:34,540
♪ Sending a flag ♪

14
00:00:34,540 --> 00:00:36,590
♪ Up a pole on a hoist ♪

15
00:00:36,590 --> 00:00:38,210
♪ Fun with flags ♪

16
00:00:38,210 --> 00:00:39,510
♪ Fun with flags ♪

17
00:00:39,510 --> 00:00:43,450
♪ Oh! Say can you see ♪

18
00:00:43,450 --> 00:00:45,800
♪ It's fun with flags ♪

19
00:00:45,800 --> 00:00:47,480
♪ Fun with flags. ♪

20
00:00:51,740 --> 00:00:54,710
As you may notice, just one of the changes around here

21
00:00:54,710 --> 00:00:56,790
is our new house band.

22
00:01:00,430 --> 00:01:03,100
Who haven't learned their place yet.

23
00:01:05,190 --> 00:01:08,910
We're also coming to you live from a different apartment.

24
00:01:08,910 --> 00:01:12,340
Dr. Fowler and I began an experiment in living together

25
00:01:12,340 --> 00:01:14,780
after her apartment became water damaged.

26
00:01:14,780 --> 00:01:17,120
This is our friend Penny's place.

27
00:01:17,120 --> 00:01:18,890
You may remember her from our episode

28
00:01:18,890 --> 00:01:22,360
"Flags and the People Who Don't Understand Them."

29
00:01:23,210 --> 00:01:25,550
So, in the spirit of cohabitation,

30
00:01:25,550 --> 00:01:28,710
the theme of today's episode is flags of two regions

31
00:01:28,710 --> 00:01:30,480
coming together as one.

32
00:01:30,480 --> 00:01:34,260
Such as the flag of St. Kitts and Nevis.

33
00:01:34,260 --> 00:01:37,970
So, let's roll up our "Sleevis" and get to know Nevis.

34
00:01:42,220 --> 00:01:45,130
Well, I-I like that, but next time check with me.

35
00:01:46,260 --> 00:01:48,020
Did you know that the flag

36
00:01:48,020 --> 00:01:50,220
was designed by a student named Edrice Lewis...

37
00:01:50,220 --> 00:01:51,060
I can't believe I'm saying this,

38
00:01:51,060 --> 00:01:53,880
but can we watch the news or something?

39
00:01:55,450 --> 00:01:57,510
It's cute, they're having fun living together.

40
00:01:57,510 --> 00:02:00,150
Yeah, I wonder what they're gonna do when her apartment's ready.

41
00:02:00,150 --> 00:02:02,110
Actually, it's been ready for weeks.

42
00:02:02,110 --> 00:02:03,330
What do you mean?

43
00:02:03,330 --> 00:02:04,820
Well, they finished the work early,

44
00:02:04,820 --> 00:02:07,330
but she's been telling Sheldon they're behind schedule.

45
00:02:07,330 --> 00:02:09,460
So, she's just been lying to him?

46
00:02:09,460 --> 00:02:11,110
Well, you've lied to Sheldon.

47
00:02:11,110 --> 00:02:12,660
Yeah, but to make him leave,

48
00:02:12,660 --> 00:02:14,830
not to make him stay.

49
00:02:16,190 --> 00:02:20,880
Buda and Pest united to form Budapest.

50
00:02:20,880 --> 00:02:22,790
And that's why Budapest

51
00:02:22,790 --> 00:02:25,260
is the "Budabest."

52
00:02:27,340 --> 00:02:28,210
Now.

53
00:02:28,210 --> 00:02:28,880
Oh, right.

54
00:02:58,160 --> 00:03:00,290
Thank you for your services, gentlemen.

55
00:03:00,290 --> 00:03:02,450
Now, I'm hoping to broaden our audience

56
00:03:02,450 --> 00:03:05,160
with your youthful rock and roll music.

57
00:03:05,770 --> 00:03:09,340
Aw, you think you have an audience, that's funny.

58
00:03:10,810 --> 00:03:12,720
We don't get paid? Nothing?

59
00:03:12,720 --> 00:03:15,110
Not even a sandwich?

60
00:03:17,270 --> 00:03:19,020
It's almost dinner time.

61
00:03:19,020 --> 00:03:20,830
You in the mood for anything?

62
00:03:20,830 --> 00:03:23,150
Yeah, we could get Thai food near your apartment

63
00:03:23,150 --> 00:03:25,890
and then drop in and check on the progress.

64
00:03:26,980 --> 00:03:30,140
Oh, you don't want do that, it's a construction zone.

65
00:03:30,870 --> 00:03:31,960
So?

66
00:03:31,960 --> 00:03:35,670
Well, what about your fear of stray nails and butt cracks?

67
00:03:36,710 --> 00:03:38,810
I am terrified of stepping on a nail

68
00:03:38,810 --> 00:03:41,130
and falling into a butt crack.

69
00:03:42,390 --> 00:03:44,600
Anyway, how about dinner?

70
00:03:44,600 --> 00:03:45,620
You know, if you'd like,

71
00:03:45,620 --> 00:03:48,420
I could call your landlord and complain.

72
00:03:48,630 --> 00:03:50,370
Thanks, but you don't have to.

73
00:03:50,370 --> 00:03:53,390
Oh, I don't mind, I'm very good at complaining.

74
00:03:53,390 --> 00:03:56,200
If it were an Olympic sport, I'd complain about

75
00:03:56,200 --> 00:03:59,260
what a stupid sport it is and then I'd take home the gold.

76
00:04:01,180 --> 00:04:02,140
Good stuff.

77
00:04:02,140 --> 00:04:05,290
So, uh, what about dinner?

78
00:04:06,150 --> 00:04:07,150
Is it me

79
00:04:07,150 --> 00:04:09,990
or are you purposely changing the subject?

80
00:04:09,990 --> 00:04:11,470
No.

81
00:04:11,470 --> 00:04:13,450
And on the subject of subjects,

82
00:04:13,450 --> 00:04:16,340
is your use of the word "subject" the same or different

83
00:04:16,340 --> 00:04:19,900
as when we speak about the subject of a king?

84
00:04:22,620 --> 00:04:25,350
I have a feeling you're still doing it.

85
00:04:25,350 --> 00:04:27,420
But I find that topic irresistible, so,

86
00:04:27,420 --> 00:04:29,910
now, in ancient Mesopotamia,

87
00:04:29,910 --> 00:04:33,200
the king referred to the people as his property.

88
00:04:35,100 --> 00:04:36,370
I'm serious,

89
00:04:36,370 --> 00:04:38,780
JPL's actually developing a robot arm

90
00:04:38,780 --> 00:04:41,690
that could grab an asteroid before it hits us.

91
00:04:41,690 --> 00:04:44,880
So their plan for saving the Earth from Armageddon

92
00:04:44,880 --> 00:04:48,740
is hoping a bunch of scientists can catch a ball?

93
00:04:48,750 --> 00:04:52,380
If we're all gonna die, why am I eating so much kale?

94
00:04:53,820 --> 00:04:56,130
You're awful quiet, everything okay?

95
00:04:56,130 --> 00:04:58,530
I'm concerned about Amy.

96
00:04:58,530 --> 00:05:01,400
She's acting a bit odd lately.

97
00:05:01,400 --> 00:05:02,940
Oh. Well, j-just out of curiosity,

98
00:05:02,940 --> 00:05:06,670
what registers as odd to you?

99
00:05:10,460 --> 00:05:11,940
Her behavior.

100
00:05:11,940 --> 00:05:15,050
No, I have the feeling that she's hiding something.

101
00:05:15,050 --> 00:05:16,500
I wouldn't worry about it.

102
00:05:16,500 --> 00:05:18,570
She's probably just distracted by work.

103
00:05:18,570 --> 00:05:20,370
Well, whatever it is, it's troubling me.

104
00:05:20,370 --> 00:05:22,270
And I can't eat, I can't sleep.

105
00:05:22,270 --> 00:05:25,850
And don't even ask about the consistency of my bowel movements.

106
00:05:26,970 --> 00:05:29,930
You heard him, guys, don't ask.

107
00:05:30,620 --> 00:05:32,540
Why would she keep something from me, you know?

108
00:05:32,540 --> 00:05:35,110
I shared my body with that woman.

109
00:05:35,110 --> 00:05:37,900
And my Netflix password.

110
00:05:38,420 --> 00:05:42,800
They recommended Stella Got Her Groove Back because of her.

111
00:05:43,590 --> 00:05:44,610
Buddy, buddy, listen,

112
00:05:44,610 --> 00:05:46,280
nothing bad is going on,

113
00:05:46,280 --> 00:05:48,120
she just...

114
00:05:48,120 --> 00:05:50,640
she just didn't want you to know that the work on her apartment

115
00:05:50,640 --> 00:05:53,430
was finished a couple weeks ago.

116
00:05:53,840 --> 00:05:55,330
I don't understand.

117
00:05:55,330 --> 00:05:57,390
She's enjoying living with you

118
00:05:57,390 --> 00:06:00,090
and she didn't want it to end early.

119
00:06:00,090 --> 00:06:02,710
So, she's deceiving me

120
00:06:02,710 --> 00:06:05,130
in order to spend more time with me.

121
00:06:05,130 --> 00:06:06,380
Yes.

122
00:06:07,440 --> 00:06:10,740
Well, I feel both flattered and hurt.

123
00:06:11,070 --> 00:06:11,950
Like when people say I look like

124
00:06:11,950 --> 00:06:15,280
that skeleton from Nightmare Before Christmas.

125
00:06:16,240 --> 00:06:19,060
Oh my God, that's who you look like.

126
00:06:20,380 --> 00:06:22,050
Sheldon, this is not a big deal.

127
00:06:22,050 --> 00:06:23,800
It's a little white lie, everyone does it.

128
00:06:23,800 --> 00:06:24,620
Not me,

129
00:06:24,620 --> 00:06:27,660
I'm a 100% honest in all of my relationships.

130
00:06:27,660 --> 00:06:30,060
And how single are you right now?

131
00:06:30,700 --> 00:06:33,590
Eating-cake-on-the-toilet single.

132
00:06:34,430 --> 00:06:37,350
Well, I won't tolerate deception in my relationship.

133
00:06:37,350 --> 00:06:39,440
I have no choice but to confront her.

134
00:06:39,440 --> 00:06:42,350
Don't do that, you've got gold here.

135
00:06:42,350 --> 00:06:44,370
Hang onto it until you're in trouble

136
00:06:44,370 --> 00:06:47,440
and then... throw it in her face.

137
00:06:48,080 --> 00:06:49,390
What? Why would you tell him that?

138
00:06:49,390 --> 00:06:51,010
That's terrible advice.

139
00:06:51,010 --> 00:06:54,290
So you wouldn't want to have anything on Penny?

140
00:06:54,290 --> 00:06:56,220
Well, of course not.

141
00:06:56,220 --> 00:07:00,110
So, if I actually know something right now...

142
00:07:00,110 --> 00:07:01,820
and I do...

143
00:07:03,130 --> 00:07:04,860
...you don't want me to tell you?

144
00:07:06,570 --> 00:07:08,120
Pfft, no.

145
00:07:08,120 --> 00:07:10,160
I'll take that as a "Yes."

146
00:07:10,950 --> 00:07:14,010
She's secretly been moving your collectibles into storage

147
00:07:14,010 --> 00:07:16,280
a little at a time and you haven't noticed.

148
00:07:16,280 --> 00:07:17,560
Are you kidding me?

149
00:07:17,560 --> 00:07:19,230
See, I've known that for weeks,

150
00:07:19,230 --> 00:07:21,540
but, you know, I waited till the moment

151
00:07:21,540 --> 00:07:24,920
when it would cause him the most pain.

152
00:07:29,980 --> 00:07:32,830
Superman's gone, my stormtrooper's gone.

153
00:07:32,830 --> 00:07:35,980
Your Klingon word-of-the-day calendar's gone.

154
00:07:36,330 --> 00:07:37,550
I'd say "damn it" in Klingon,

155
00:07:37,550 --> 00:07:40,250
but that wasn't until next month.

156
00:07:40,580 --> 00:07:41,440
It's "Khoo-vakh."

157
00:07:41,440 --> 00:07:43,120
Khoo-vakh!

158
00:07:44,220 --> 00:07:46,030
She took my Where's Waldo.

159
00:07:46,030 --> 00:07:47,410
Well, no, no, he's over there.

160
00:07:47,410 --> 00:07:48,740
Oh, yeah, there he is.

161
00:07:51,980 --> 00:07:54,850
So, what's the deal with your apartment?

162
00:07:54,850 --> 00:07:57,130
Why's it taking so long?

163
00:07:57,130 --> 00:08:00,100
Um, it was a drywall problem.

164
00:08:00,100 --> 00:08:02,980
Oh, no, what happened?

165
00:08:03,430 --> 00:08:05,360
Well, the drywall got wet,

166
00:08:05,360 --> 00:08:08,220
and you do not want wet drywall

167
00:08:08,220 --> 00:08:12,200
because when drywall gets wet, it's really more...

168
00:08:12,200 --> 00:08:14,010
Wet wall?

169
00:08:15,360 --> 00:08:17,840
Or damp wall, just as bad. Mm.

170
00:08:19,220 --> 00:08:22,410
So why don't they just get more drywall?

171
00:08:22,410 --> 00:08:25,020
Well, they went to get some,

172
00:08:25,020 --> 00:08:28,240
but the woman at the wall store

173
00:08:28,840 --> 00:08:30,870
said it was going on sale and they should wait

174
00:08:30,870 --> 00:08:33,560
- because the savings... - Okay, are you done?

175
00:08:33,560 --> 00:08:35,660
Bernadette told me your apartment's ready.

176
00:08:35,660 --> 00:08:39,230
I was done at wet wall, but you wouldn't let it go.

177
00:08:40,050 --> 00:08:42,390
But is Sheldon really believing all this crap?

178
00:08:42,390 --> 00:08:44,950
Well, he started to question it, but then I fake sneezed on him

179
00:08:44,950 --> 00:08:46,880
and he ran to take a shower.

180
00:08:48,170 --> 00:08:50,270
Please don't say anything, I feel terrible about this.

181
00:08:50,270 --> 00:08:51,880
Oh, don't worry, I won't.

182
00:08:51,880 --> 00:08:53,520
Thanks.

183
00:08:54,920 --> 00:08:57,630
- "The woman at the wall store?" - Let it go!

184
00:09:00,690 --> 00:09:02,600
Are you going to confront Penny?

185
00:09:02,600 --> 00:09:04,110
Eventually, I guess.

186
00:09:04,110 --> 00:09:06,450
Although, I am kind of curious how long she thinks

187
00:09:06,450 --> 00:09:09,290
she can keep hiding my stuff without me knowing.

188
00:09:10,940 --> 00:09:13,480
You know, perhaps instead of confronting them,

189
00:09:13,480 --> 00:09:17,120
we should see how far they're willing to spin their tangled webs.

190
00:09:17,120 --> 00:09:18,450
Like that Spider-Man action figure

191
00:09:18,450 --> 00:09:20,540
that used to be on your desk.

192
00:09:20,830 --> 00:09:23,050
Oh, my God, I'm going blind.

193
00:09:25,200 --> 00:09:27,490
Hi. Food's here.

194
00:09:28,480 --> 00:09:29,910
Excellent.

195
00:09:29,910 --> 00:09:31,830
I'm very hungry.

196
00:09:31,830 --> 00:09:33,110
Yeah, speaking of which,

197
00:09:33,110 --> 00:09:35,350
what's going on with your apartment?

198
00:09:36,100 --> 00:09:38,650
Oh, uh, they're still working on it.

199
00:09:38,650 --> 00:09:40,120
Interesting.

200
00:09:40,120 --> 00:09:43,220
Very interesting.

201
00:09:43,720 --> 00:09:45,990
Yeah, we swung by her apartment on the way to the restaurant,

202
00:09:45,990 --> 00:09:48,370
and they're gonna be fixing it for a while.

203
00:09:48,370 --> 00:09:51,400
Wait, uh... you saw her apartment?

204
00:09:51,400 --> 00:09:54,310
I did, still a mess.

205
00:09:57,750 --> 00:10:00,290
- Leonard? - Yeah?

206
00:10:14,110 --> 00:10:16,110
W-Why are you speaking Klingon?

207
00:10:16,110 --> 00:10:18,510
Why are you speaking English?

208
00:10:19,500 --> 00:10:20,800
This is ridiculous.

209
00:10:20,800 --> 00:10:23,220
Penny, do you remember when I taught you Ubbi Dubbi?

210
00:10:40,940 --> 00:10:42,050
Oh, wait, stop that.

211
00:10:42,050 --> 00:10:43,420
You stop that.

212
00:10:48,050 --> 00:10:49,670
Okay. That's enough. You know what?

213
00:10:50,930 --> 00:10:52,430
What is going on?

214
00:10:52,430 --> 00:10:55,580
Fine, I told Sheldon that her apartment's been finished,

215
00:10:55,580 --> 00:10:56,740
but then you just said it's not,

216
00:10:56,740 --> 00:10:58,550
so now I'm all confused.

217
00:10:58,780 --> 00:11:00,920
Penny was just covering for me.

218
00:11:00,920 --> 00:11:02,940
My place has been ready for two weeks.

219
00:11:02,940 --> 00:11:04,160
How could you lie to me?

220
00:11:04,160 --> 00:11:05,380
Uh, she's enjoyed living with you.

221
00:11:05,380 --> 00:11:07,220
It's called being in love.

222
00:11:07,220 --> 00:11:09,530
Mm-hmm, and what's it called when you secretly get rid

223
00:11:09,530 --> 00:11:10,990
of all your husband's stuff?

224
00:11:10,990 --> 00:11:13,050
Wha... That is not true!

225
00:11:13,050 --> 00:11:14,900
Bernadette told Howard, Howard told me.

226
00:11:14,900 --> 00:11:17,550
Plus, I can see all my stuff is gone!

227
00:11:17,550 --> 00:11:20,480
Oh, so, you believe your friend, and your friend's wife

228
00:11:20,480 --> 00:11:23,140
and your own eyes over me?

229
00:11:32,560 --> 00:11:35,400
You really didn't think I'd notice my stuff was missing?

230
00:11:35,400 --> 00:11:37,710
Uh, did you notice your key chain?

231
00:11:42,010 --> 00:11:43,960
Where's Batman?!

232
00:11:46,430 --> 00:11:49,030
Why did you tell Howard I was hiding Leonard's things?

233
00:11:49,030 --> 00:11:49,820
One sec.

234
00:11:49,820 --> 00:11:50,660
Why did you tell Leonard

235
00:11:50,660 --> 00:11:53,320
I told you Penny was hiding his things?!

236
00:11:53,600 --> 00:11:54,740
It just came up

237
00:11:54,740 --> 00:11:58,020
because we-we were talking about secrets and...

238
00:11:58,020 --> 00:11:58,680
Wait.

239
00:12:00,010 --> 00:12:01,460
Everybody stop it with that!

240
00:12:03,150 --> 00:12:04,320
I'm not really a part of this,

241
00:12:04,320 --> 00:12:06,530
so I'm just gonna dig in.

242
00:12:07,920 --> 00:12:10,700
And I'd like to know why you blabbed about my apartment.

243
00:12:10,700 --> 00:12:12,230
You're up, blabby.

244
00:12:13,760 --> 00:12:16,840
Amy, I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said anything.

245
00:12:17,390 --> 00:12:19,620
I guess it's okay.

246
00:12:19,840 --> 00:12:21,250
I'm sorry

247
00:12:21,250 --> 00:12:23,700
that I lied about my apartment.

248
00:12:23,700 --> 00:12:25,110
It's all right.

249
00:12:25,110 --> 00:12:26,570
And...

250
00:12:26,570 --> 00:12:27,310
And what?

251
00:12:27,310 --> 00:12:30,350
Your wizard robes are next to go.

252
00:12:31,890 --> 00:12:33,420
Now that everything's out on the table,

253
00:12:33,420 --> 00:12:36,510
you-you think you two will keep living together?

254
00:12:37,240 --> 00:12:39,530
Despite recent events,

255
00:12:39,530 --> 00:12:42,270
I do consider our experiment in cohabitation

256
00:12:42,270 --> 00:12:44,280
to have been positive.

257
00:12:44,280 --> 00:12:47,430
Are you saying you'd like to live with me?

258
00:12:47,430 --> 00:12:50,000
I'm open to the possibility.

259
00:12:53,650 --> 00:12:54,830
Whatever.

260
00:12:57,280 --> 00:12:59,560
You know, if he moves across the hall for good,

261
00:12:59,560 --> 00:13:01,810
Leonard could keep the stuff you don't like in Sheldon's old room.

262
00:13:01,810 --> 00:13:03,560
- Solves everything. - That's a great idea!

263
00:13:03,560 --> 00:13:05,980
Ooh, maybe I could turn it into a gaming den.

264
00:13:05,980 --> 00:13:06,960
That would be amazing.

265
00:13:06,960 --> 00:13:07,940
Wait, wait, hold on, do what?

266
00:13:07,940 --> 00:13:10,500
Excuse me... that's my room.

267
00:13:10,500 --> 00:13:11,710
But you won't be living here.

268
00:13:11,710 --> 00:13:12,950
But that's my room.

269
00:13:12,950 --> 00:13:14,720
- But you won't be living here. - But that's my room.

270
00:13:14,720 --> 00:13:15,780
You guys might want to start eating.

271
00:13:15,780 --> 00:13:17,450
But you won't be living here.

272
00:13:18,600 --> 00:13:19,880
Sweetie, once you stop paying rent,

273
00:13:19,880 --> 00:13:21,570
none of this is really yours.

274
00:13:21,570 --> 00:13:22,650
But that's my room.

275
00:13:22,650 --> 00:13:25,130
But you won't be living here!

276
00:13:27,770 --> 00:13:29,840
Thank you for understanding.

277
00:13:29,840 --> 00:13:31,800
Hey, I get it.

278
00:13:31,800 --> 00:13:34,550
Everybody wants to spend more time with me.

279
00:13:35,570 --> 00:13:38,450
I'm like a man made of sugar in a world of ants.

280
00:13:40,030 --> 00:13:40,770
Good night.

281
00:13:40,770 --> 00:13:41,730
Mm, night.

282
00:13:54,140 --> 00:13:56,780
If we did continue living together,

283
00:13:56,780 --> 00:13:58,640
would it be here?

284
00:13:59,980 --> 00:14:01,070
I don't know.

285
00:14:01,070 --> 00:14:02,720
It-It could be.

286
00:14:03,120 --> 00:14:03,990
Of course there's...

287
00:14:03,990 --> 00:14:06,340
there's always your apartment.

288
00:14:06,810 --> 00:14:09,990
S-Sure, sure, we-we could live in my apartment.

289
00:14:09,990 --> 00:14:12,180
I hate your apartment.

290
00:14:13,470 --> 00:14:15,970
Sorry, you brought it up?

291
00:14:16,630 --> 00:14:19,050
Well, I suppose we could find a whole new place.

292
00:14:19,050 --> 00:14:20,030
You know, and, technically,

293
00:14:20,030 --> 00:14:22,080
we don't even have to stay in Pasadena.

294
00:14:22,080 --> 00:14:24,720
We could, we could move to Altadena...

295
00:14:24,720 --> 00:14:27,950
or a place that doesn't even end in "Dena."

296
00:14:28,350 --> 00:14:29,790
It's kind of exciting.

297
00:14:29,790 --> 00:14:33,430
I mean... we could do whatever we want.

298
00:14:33,430 --> 00:14:36,480
But what if we move and we don't like it?

299
00:14:36,480 --> 00:14:38,740
What if there's a smoker in the building?

300
00:14:38,740 --> 00:14:40,050
Or pets?

301
00:14:40,050 --> 00:14:41,590
Or there could be mold.

302
00:14:41,590 --> 00:14:43,190
There could be traffic noise.

303
00:14:43,190 --> 00:14:46,810
I'm gonna have to learn a whole new bus route.

304
00:14:53,080 --> 00:14:54,650
Are you trying to soothe me

305
00:14:54,650 --> 00:14:57,480
by singing the Star Trek theme as a lullaby?

306
00:14:58,140 --> 00:14:59,360
Yes.

307
00:14:59,360 --> 00:15:02,020
I'm not a child, don't do that.

308
00:15:02,490 --> 00:15:04,040
Sorry.

309
00:15:07,780 --> 00:15:10,740
Do you know 2001: A Space Odyssey?

310
00:15:22,060 --> 00:15:24,130
All right, now that's soothing.

311
00:15:32,820 --> 00:15:35,390
Look, I-I get it, this is still my room;

312
00:15:35,390 --> 00:15:37,190
we haven't really made it yours.

313
00:15:37,190 --> 00:15:38,550
Thank you.

314
00:15:38,550 --> 00:15:42,390
Which is why I got you this Pink Power Ranger.

315
00:15:44,110 --> 00:15:45,870
Put it anywhere you like.

316
00:15:45,870 --> 00:15:49,080
Okay, but you may feel some discomfort.

317
00:15:50,390 --> 00:15:52,910
I'm kidding, I want you to feel at home here.

318
00:15:52,910 --> 00:15:55,570
Decorate it any way that makes you happy.

319
00:15:55,570 --> 00:15:56,530
Do you really mean that?

320
00:15:56,530 --> 00:15:57,700
I really do.

321
00:15:57,700 --> 00:15:58,910
Great, and just so you know,

322
00:15:58,910 --> 00:16:00,440
I'm not getting rid of all your stuff.

323
00:16:00,440 --> 00:16:02,390
Yeah? What are you keeping?

324
00:16:02,390 --> 00:16:04,800
That candle and you.

325
00:16:06,950 --> 00:16:07,800
What about my robot poster?

326
00:16:08,680 --> 00:16:11,270
I can make do with just the candle.

327
00:16:17,910 --> 00:16:19,350
What's going on?

328
00:16:20,100 --> 00:16:23,380
I'm struggling with the thought of leaving my old bedroom.

329
00:16:24,310 --> 00:16:27,260
Can it be more of an internal struggle?

330
00:16:28,620 --> 00:16:30,480
I need to see it.

331
00:16:31,420 --> 00:16:32,780
While I'm gone,

332
00:16:32,780 --> 00:16:35,230
don't breathe on my pillow.

333
00:16:35,830 --> 00:16:37,610
How about if I just don't breathe at all?

334
00:16:37,610 --> 00:16:39,410
That's my girl.

335
00:16:47,000 --> 00:16:49,140
What on earth?

336
00:17:02,390 --> 00:17:04,010
What is going on?!

337
00:17:04,010 --> 00:17:05,850
Oh, hey, Sheldon.

338
00:17:06,830 --> 00:17:09,730
We turned your room into a sex dungeon.

339
00:17:12,480 --> 00:17:13,300
No!

340
00:17:13,300 --> 00:17:15,070
What is happening?!

341
00:17:19,220 --> 00:17:20,660
Okay, last question.

342
00:17:20,660 --> 00:17:24,180
The chaps he was wearing... assless?

343
00:17:24,960 --> 00:17:27,820
Can we just focus on the decision I'm facing?

344
00:17:27,820 --> 00:17:29,600
We can, but for the record,

345
00:17:29,600 --> 00:17:32,130
all chaps are assless.

346
00:17:33,120 --> 00:17:34,940
Gentlemen, please,

347
00:17:34,940 --> 00:17:36,790
this is a significant decision.

348
00:17:36,790 --> 00:17:39,740
Now, do Amy and I continue living together?

349
00:17:39,740 --> 00:17:42,110
Or do I move back in with Leonard?

350
00:17:42,110 --> 00:17:44,950
Over my assless chaps you will.

351
00:17:45,750 --> 00:17:47,990
This isn't complicated.

352
00:17:47,990 --> 00:17:49,100
Do you love Amy?

353
00:17:49,100 --> 00:17:49,980
Yes.

354
00:17:49,980 --> 00:17:51,830
Do you like living with her?

355
00:17:51,830 --> 00:17:52,880
Yes.

356
00:17:52,880 --> 00:17:55,610
Do you know what you need to do now?

357
00:17:56,060 --> 00:17:57,490
Apparently, figure this out on my own

358
00:17:57,490 --> 00:17:59,430
'cause you guys are no help at all.

359
00:18:22,710 --> 00:18:24,250
What are you doing?

360
00:18:25,320 --> 00:18:29,270
I'm just contemplating Buridan's donkey.

361
00:18:29,270 --> 00:18:30,130
I understand.

362
00:18:30,130 --> 00:18:31,950
I'll leave you be.

363
00:18:34,040 --> 00:18:36,410
What, you're familiar with the reference?

364
00:18:36,410 --> 00:18:37,740
Of course.

365
00:18:37,740 --> 00:18:40,300
Jean Buridan proposed a philosophical thesis

366
00:18:40,300 --> 00:18:41,880
stating that a hungry donkey

367
00:18:41,880 --> 00:18:44,420
placed between two equidistant bales of hay

368
00:18:44,420 --> 00:18:46,020
would be paralyzed by indecision

369
00:18:46,020 --> 00:18:47,900
and would starve to death.

370
00:18:52,470 --> 00:18:54,350
Exactly.

371
00:18:55,300 --> 00:18:57,940
Well, I wouldn't want you to starve to death, so...

372
00:18:59,000 --> 00:19:00,510
...here's an eggplant.

373
00:19:03,370 --> 00:19:04,940
Thank you.

374
00:19:05,470 --> 00:19:07,920
You know, some people believe that Buridan

375
00:19:07,920 --> 00:19:10,010
was plagiarizing Aristotle.

376
00:19:10,550 --> 00:19:11,550
Really?

377
00:19:11,550 --> 00:19:13,660
Although, in Aristotle's example,

378
00:19:13,660 --> 00:19:16,170
he proposed an equally hungry and thirsty man

379
00:19:16,170 --> 00:19:18,270
caught between food and drink.

380
00:19:19,330 --> 00:19:20,720
Yeah, I wonder if that's related

381
00:19:20,720 --> 00:19:23,840
to the 12th century Persian philosopher, al-Ghazali

382
00:19:23,840 --> 00:19:27,650
and his story of a man caught between two dates.

383
00:19:27,650 --> 00:19:30,150
Are you suggesting al-Ghazali was Aristotelian?

384
00:19:30,150 --> 00:19:33,700
'Cause if anything, he was anti-Aristotelian.

385
00:19:34,640 --> 00:19:37,920
Al-Ghazali was anti-Aristotelian?

386
00:19:37,920 --> 00:19:40,820
Boy, you think you know a guy.

387
00:19:45,140 --> 00:19:47,680
Okay.  Open your eyes

388
00:19:47,680 --> 00:19:49,910
and see your new room.

389
00:19:56,910 --> 00:19:58,310
I-I know I went a little overboard.

390
00:19:58,310 --> 00:19:59,460
We can always dial it back.

391
00:19:59,460 --> 00:20:00,450
No, no, no, no, no,

392
00:20:00,450 --> 00:20:01,560
it's-it's important to me

393
00:20:01,560 --> 00:20:03,250
that you have the bedroom you want.

394
00:20:03,250 --> 00:20:05,310
Oh, that means so much. I love you.

395
00:20:05,310 --> 00:20:06,850
I love you, too.

396
00:20:09,860 --> 00:20:12,930
Just hiding some stuff in your closet, don't tell Penny.

