1
00:02:50,010 --> 00:02:53,810
m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147

2
00:02:50,010 --> 00:02:53,810
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

3
00:02:50,010 --> 00:02:53,810
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:02:50,010 --> 00:02:53,810
ZiMuZu.tv

5
00:00:02,790 --> 00:00:04,530
What's going on with that woman you're dating?

6
00:00:04,530 --> 00:00:05,710
I broke up with her.

7
00:00:05,710 --> 00:00:06,480
Why?

8
00:00:06,480 --> 00:00:08,140
She said she didn't want to see me anymore

9
00:00:08,140 --> 00:00:10,300
and I found that insulting.

10
00:00:11,510 --> 00:00:13,480
I thought things were going well. What happened?

11
00:00:13,480 --> 00:00:15,940
I don't know, she didn't even give me a reason.

12
00:00:15,940 --> 00:00:17,850
Oh, not a problem, we can figure this out.

13
00:00:17,850 --> 00:00:22,450
What are the reasons women reject Raj?

14
00:00:22,690 --> 00:00:24,830
Can we not play this game?

15
00:00:24,830 --> 00:00:27,360
Doesn't like games. That's one.

16
00:00:28,630 --> 00:00:29,670
Ignore him.

17
00:00:29,670 --> 00:00:31,140
Yeah, sorry about the breakup.

18
00:00:31,140 --> 00:00:32,310
That's okay, I'm fine.

19
00:00:32,310 --> 00:00:33,600
Of course you're fine.

20
00:00:33,600 --> 00:00:36,420
Not every member of a species finds a mate.

21
00:00:36,420 --> 00:00:38,400
Sir Isaac Newton died a virgin.

22
00:00:38,400 --> 00:00:40,670
Look at the contributions he made.

23
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:43,240
I'm not a virgin, Sheldon.

24
00:00:43,240 --> 00:00:45,740
Wha... So now you think you're better than Isaac Newton?

25
00:00:47,350 --> 00:00:49,710
No wonder women don't like you.

26
00:00:50,900 --> 00:00:52,150
You're not being very nice.

27
00:00:52,150 --> 00:00:53,550
What? He said he was fine.

28
00:00:53,550 --> 00:00:56,150
Sometimes people say things they don't mean.

29
00:00:56,150 --> 00:00:57,680
Oh, that's a paradox.

30
00:00:57,680 --> 00:00:59,320
I-If you meant what you just said,

31
00:00:59,320 --> 00:01:02,500
then that means you may not have meant what you just said.

32
00:01:02,500 --> 00:01:04,290
Careful, I saw this on Star Trek.

33
00:01:04,290 --> 00:01:06,960
Smoke's gonna come out of his ears soon.

34
00:01:08,590 --> 00:01:10,040
Hey, boys. How's it going?

35
00:01:10,040 --> 00:01:11,990
Well, I thought we were having a nice conversation,

36
00:01:11,990 --> 00:01:14,680
but it turns out, I was being offensive.

37
00:01:14,680 --> 00:01:16,690
- So, normal. - Yeah--

38
00:01:17,350 --> 00:01:18,900
?Sheldon, what did you do?

39
00:01:18,900 --> 00:01:21,100
We were discussing Raj's recent breakup

40
00:01:21,100 --> 00:01:23,310
and apparently, I was insensitive to him.

41
00:01:23,310 --> 00:01:25,150
It's okay, I'm fine.

42
00:01:25,150 --> 00:01:26,640
You di-- Don't fall for it.

43
00:01:26,640 --> 00:01:28,490
He'll get you to compare him to a dead virgin,

44
00:01:28,490 --> 00:01:30,830
and suddenly you're the bad guy.

45
00:01:31,800 --> 00:01:33,750
Sheldon, when I said I was fine,

46
00:01:33,750 --> 00:01:35,910
I meant I didn't want to talk about it anymore.

47
00:01:35,910 --> 00:01:37,390
Then why didn't you say that?

48
00:01:37,390 --> 00:01:38,960
Because that's not what people do.

49
00:01:38,960 --> 00:01:40,400
Well, I would prefer if people told me

50
00:01:40,400 --> 00:01:42,100
exactly what is on their mind.

51
00:01:42,100 --> 00:01:43,420
No. No, you don't, you really don't.

52
00:01:43,420 --> 00:01:45,870
I actually can't say "Don't" enough.

53
00:01:46,550 --> 00:01:48,430
Well, it certainly would be easier.

54
00:01:48,430 --> 00:01:50,240
You have no idea what it's like

55
00:01:50,240 --> 00:01:53,230
to struggle with recognizing emotional cues.

56
00:01:53,230 --> 00:01:55,100
I'm sure it's extremely frustrating.

57
00:01:55,100 --> 00:01:57,050
- Thank you. - And also a little sad.

58
00:01:57,050 --> 00:01:59,660
O-Okay, now you're just showing off.

59
00:02:00,960 --> 00:02:02,810
You know, I just read that a team at MIT

60
00:02:02,810 --> 00:02:05,730
developed a device that helps people read human emotions.

61
00:02:05,730 --> 00:02:06,960
And you think we can get those guys

62
00:02:06,960 --> 00:02:09,890
to reprogram Sheldon? Cool.

63
00:02:10,450 --> 00:02:13,360
It's supposed to be accurate, like, 85% of the time.

64
00:02:13,360 --> 00:02:14,940
Wow, I find that hard to believe.

65
00:02:14,940 --> 00:02:16,800
That a bunch of awkward scientists

66
00:02:16,800 --> 00:02:19,030
with no social skills would invent a machine

67
00:02:19,030 --> 00:02:20,310
to do it for them?

68
00:02:20,310 --> 00:02:22,280
I take it back. I believe it.

69
00:02:22,880 --> 00:02:25,590
You know, if it's at MIT, I can make some calls.

70
00:02:25,590 --> 00:02:27,900
Maybe we can get Sheldon a prototype.

71
00:02:27,900 --> 00:02:29,450
What do you think?

72
00:02:29,750 --> 00:02:32,760
A machine that reads emotions is intriguing.

73
00:02:32,760 --> 00:02:35,720
It could help me be a more considerate friend.

74
00:02:35,720 --> 00:02:37,170
Wouldn't that be nice.

75
00:02:37,170 --> 00:02:38,870
It could also help me identify my enemies,

76
00:02:38,870 --> 00:02:41,390
discover their fears and then...

77
00:02:42,200 --> 00:02:45,210
I could use those fears to destroy them.

78
00:02:47,100 --> 00:02:49,340
I like the first one.

79
00:03:15,270 --> 00:03:16,580
Now that Sheldon's across the hall,

80
00:03:16,580 --> 00:03:18,900
have you decided what you're doing with his old room?

81
00:03:18,900 --> 00:03:21,960
I was thinking maybe a library or a gaming room.

82
00:03:21,960 --> 00:03:23,950
You could make it a train room.

83
00:03:23,950 --> 00:03:25,370
I don't like trains. You like trains.

84
00:03:25,370 --> 00:03:28,620
I know, and Amy says I can't have a train room.

85
00:03:29,580 --> 00:03:32,100
Sheldon, I just heard from the guys at MIT

86
00:03:32,100 --> 00:03:34,180
about that emotion reader; they're sending a prototype

87
00:03:34,180 --> 00:03:35,410
for you to beta test.

88
00:03:35,970 --> 00:03:37,070
Wonderful.

89
00:03:37,070 --> 00:03:38,280
Although I'm not sure how I feel

90
00:03:38,280 --> 00:03:40,120
about being used as a guinea pig.

91
00:03:40,120 --> 00:03:43,470
Well, when you get the machine, you can find out.

92
00:03:44,220 --> 00:03:45,720
Maybe I could use it

93
00:03:45,720 --> 00:03:47,830
to understand why women keep dumping me.

94
00:03:47,830 --> 00:03:50,450
Oh, you don't need a machine for that, just send a survey card

95
00:03:50,450 --> 00:03:51,790
to all your ex-girlfriends and tell them

96
00:03:51,790 --> 00:03:54,310
if they fill it out they might win a prize.

97
00:03:54,980 --> 00:03:56,390
That's actually not a bad idea.

98
00:03:56,390 --> 00:03:58,190
Maybe I could even get them all together,

99
00:03:58,190 --> 00:04:00,180
sort of like a... a focus group,

100
00:04:00,180 --> 00:04:01,570
to find out what's wrong with me.

101
00:04:01,570 --> 00:04:04,260
No, Raj, that's a terrible idea.

102
00:04:04,260 --> 00:04:06,120
Yeah, I was joking.

103
00:04:06,120 --> 00:04:07,430
You... Really?

104
00:04:07,430 --> 00:04:09,310
Uh, little tip: jokes are often better

105
00:04:09,310 --> 00:04:13,160
when you end them with "Wocka Wocka" or "Ha-cha-cha."

106
00:04:15,670 --> 00:04:18,290
Hey, great news. The TV I want will fit in the gaming room,

107
00:04:18,290 --> 00:04:19,720
and if I leave the curtains open,

108
00:04:19,720 --> 00:04:21,900
I can watch it from work.

109
00:04:23,070 --> 00:04:24,680
Hey, can you hold off redoing the room?

110
00:04:24,680 --> 00:04:26,720
My brother's coming out here in a few weeks.

111
00:04:26,720 --> 00:04:29,170
Oh. Yeah. Okay, sure. What's going on with your brother?

112
00:04:29,170 --> 00:04:32,040
My dad asked if I can get him a job interview at my work.

113
00:04:32,040 --> 00:04:33,600
Is that a good idea?

114
00:04:33,600 --> 00:04:35,440
I mean, you think they'll consider someone

115
00:04:35,440 --> 00:04:37,260
who was in prison for selling drugs?

116
00:04:37,260 --> 00:04:39,440
Well, I sell pharmaceuticals.

117
00:04:39,440 --> 00:04:42,870
That's just a really hard to spell word for drugs.

118
00:04:43,880 --> 00:04:45,300
Well, I'm sure he'll appreciate

119
00:04:45,300 --> 00:04:49,160
carrying his samples in a briefcase instead of his colon.

120
00:04:51,360 --> 00:04:52,970
How long do you think he'll stay?

121
00:04:52,970 --> 00:04:55,180
I-I'm not sure. Maybe a few days.

122
00:04:55,180 --> 00:04:57,270
Unless he gets the job, then who knows?

123
00:04:57,580 --> 00:04:59,390
"Who knows?" That's exciting.

124
00:04:59,390 --> 00:05:00,500
I'll get to wake up every morning

125
00:05:00,500 --> 00:05:02,730
and see if he's still here.

126
00:05:03,710 --> 00:05:05,540
You don't have a problem with this, do you?

127
00:05:05,540 --> 00:05:07,540
Of course not. I mean, he's your brother.

128
00:05:07,540 --> 00:05:09,390
Okay. Thank you, you're the best.

129
00:05:09,670 --> 00:05:11,670
Remember that when the new TV falls off the wall

130
00:05:11,670 --> 00:05:13,630
and crushes us both.

131
00:05:16,650 --> 00:05:17,770
This thing's pretty cool.

132
00:05:17,770 --> 00:05:18,920
It interprets emotions

133
00:05:18,920 --> 00:05:22,000
using a wireless signal to analyze subtle changes

134
00:05:22,000 --> 00:05:23,680
in breathing and heart rate.

135
00:05:23,680 --> 00:05:25,400
It's amazing a machine can do that.

136
00:05:25,400 --> 00:05:26,130
Yes.

137
00:05:26,130 --> 00:05:27,640
Now, when the robots rise up,

138
00:05:27,640 --> 00:05:30,760
they'll know that I've been rooting for them the whole time.

139
00:05:31,980 --> 00:05:34,110
The display is synced to your phone.

140
00:05:34,110 --> 00:05:35,920
Give it a try.

141
00:05:35,920 --> 00:05:36,730
All right.

142
00:05:36,730 --> 00:05:38,080
Now, I'm gonna look at some pictures

143
00:05:38,080 --> 00:05:39,930
to prompt an emotional response, and we'll see

144
00:05:39,930 --> 00:05:42,000
if the machine can identify them accurately.

145
00:05:42,000 --> 00:05:43,630
Okay, remember, it can only detect happy, sad,

146
00:05:43,630 --> 00:05:44,840
angry and excited.

147
00:05:44,840 --> 00:05:46,290
Not other things you're feeling, like,

148
00:05:46,290 --> 00:05:48,570
"What have I done with my life?"

149
00:05:52,040 --> 00:05:55,270
Okay, I'm looking at the first picture.

150
00:05:55,270 --> 00:05:57,790
You are...

151
00:05:58,160 --> 00:05:59,300
happy?

152
00:05:59,300 --> 00:06:01,430
Yes. I'm looking at puppies.

153
00:06:02,290 --> 00:06:04,480
Somebody's ignoring their tiny needle teeth,

154
00:06:04,480 --> 00:06:05,970
but all right.

155
00:06:06,820 --> 00:06:09,460
- Try another one. - Okay.

156
00:06:09,770 --> 00:06:11,790
What does it say I'm feeling?

157
00:06:11,790 --> 00:06:12,970
Sad.

158
00:06:12,970 --> 00:06:15,880
Yes. I'm looking at a picture of my grandma.

159
00:06:15,880 --> 00:06:18,900
Oh, that makes sense, 'cause she's gone and you miss her.

160
00:06:18,900 --> 00:06:19,820
Yes.

161
00:06:19,820 --> 00:06:22,750
And you're worried that turkey neck is in your future.

162
00:06:26,470 --> 00:06:28,350
What, now, see... Now it says you're mad.

163
00:06:28,350 --> 00:06:30,420
Make up your mind.

164
00:06:33,830 --> 00:06:34,840
Okay, Emily.

165
00:06:34,840 --> 00:06:36,210
Yeah, sounds great.

166
00:06:36,570 --> 00:06:37,820
See you then.

167
00:06:37,820 --> 00:06:39,650
Is that Emily your ex-girlfriend?

168
00:06:39,650 --> 00:06:41,810
Yeah. I'm getting all my exes together

169
00:06:41,810 --> 00:06:43,890
in order to discuss why they broke up with me

170
00:06:43,890 --> 00:06:46,200
and how I can be a better boyfriend.

171
00:06:46,200 --> 00:06:47,520
Oh, God. You went through with that?

172
00:06:47,520 --> 00:06:48,890
What is wrong with you?

173
00:06:48,890 --> 00:06:50,930
We are going to find out.

174
00:06:52,600 --> 00:06:54,140
Why would you do that, Raj?

175
00:06:54,140 --> 00:06:56,960
Well, I want information in order to improve myself.

176
00:06:56,960 --> 00:06:58,570
You're not gonna get information,

177
00:06:58,570 --> 00:07:01,480
you're just gonna get criticism that hurts your feelings.

178
00:07:01,480 --> 00:07:03,050
Don't worry, I'm a grown man.

179
00:07:03,050 --> 00:07:04,690
I have a thick skin.

180
00:07:04,690 --> 00:07:05,960
You're so stupid.

181
00:07:05,960 --> 00:07:07,840
Hey!

182
00:07:12,810 --> 00:07:14,590
I'm trying to help him clean it up a little.

183
00:07:14,590 --> 00:07:15,610
Yeah, sure.

184
00:07:17,920 --> 00:07:20,800
He really worked with the Drug Enforcement Agency?

185
00:07:20,800 --> 00:07:23,670
He didn't know it till he was cuffed, but yeah.

186
00:07:25,380 --> 00:07:27,730
Hey, Leonard, if you're happy and you know it,

187
00:07:27,730 --> 00:07:29,100
no need to clap your hands,

188
00:07:29,100 --> 00:07:32,550
because I have an emotion detector.

189
00:07:33,080 --> 00:07:33,970
How's it working out?

190
00:07:33,970 --> 00:07:35,510
Surprisingly well.

191
00:07:35,510 --> 00:07:36,610
That's great, I'm happy for you.

192
00:07:36,610 --> 00:07:38,740
No, wait, uh, hold on.

193
00:07:39,150 --> 00:07:41,890
Oh, what, you are. Aren't you sweet?

194
00:07:42,770 --> 00:07:44,300
What's that? Are you working on your resume?

195
00:07:44,300 --> 00:07:45,440
No, it's my brother's. I'm trying

196
00:07:45,440 --> 00:07:46,890
to help him get a job out here.

197
00:07:47,690 --> 00:07:50,300
And that makes Leonard angry.

198
00:07:51,400 --> 00:07:52,420
No, it doesn't.

199
00:07:52,420 --> 00:07:55,520
What, Leonard, please. I know an angry face when I see it.

200
00:07:55,520 --> 00:07:58,340
It's this red frowny guy on my phone.

201
00:07:59,290 --> 00:08:01,570
What? Are you really upset about Randall coming?

202
00:08:01,570 --> 00:08:03,860
- No. - Yes.

203
00:08:03,860 --> 00:08:07,320
- I said no. - I-It's like you're twins.

204
00:08:07,950 --> 00:08:10,120
Leonard, if you're mad about this, just tell me.

205
00:08:11,040 --> 00:08:11,830
Fine.

206
00:08:11,830 --> 00:08:14,610
You invited your drug dealer brother to stay with us

207
00:08:14,610 --> 00:08:17,780
for God knows how long and didn't bother to ask me first.

208
00:08:17,780 --> 00:08:18,560
He's my brother!

209
00:08:18,560 --> 00:08:20,210
I didn't think I needed your permission.

210
00:08:20,210 --> 00:08:22,580
Well, hey. Now she's angry, too.

211
00:08:22,940 --> 00:08:25,170
This thing works like gangbusters.

212
00:08:29,170 --> 00:08:31,200
I'm not saying you have to ask my permission,

213
00:08:31,200 --> 00:08:32,400
but you could have talked to me about it

214
00:08:32,400 --> 00:08:33,810
before you said it was okay.

215
00:08:33,810 --> 00:08:35,890
Like you talked to me about your gaming room?

216
00:08:35,890 --> 00:08:37,010
Our gaming room!

217
00:08:37,010 --> 00:08:39,720
I was gonna put a scented candle in it.

218
00:08:40,390 --> 00:08:42,300
He's still mad.

219
00:08:42,300 --> 00:08:44,580
Stop enjoying their fight.

220
00:08:45,510 --> 00:08:47,020
You first.

221
00:08:48,160 --> 00:08:49,050
If you were this upset,

222
00:08:49,050 --> 00:08:50,930
why didn't you say so when I told you?

223
00:08:50,930 --> 00:08:52,810
Because I didn't want to sound like a jerk.

224
00:08:52,810 --> 00:08:54,750
Well, you sound like one now. I don't see the big deal

225
00:08:54,750 --> 00:08:56,850
if my brother comes and stays for a while.

226
00:08:56,850 --> 00:08:58,860
If you get him a job, he's gonna live here forever!

227
00:08:58,860 --> 00:09:00,450
He would get his own place.

228
00:09:00,450 --> 00:09:01,950
Has he ever had his own place?

229
00:09:01,950 --> 00:09:02,720
Yes!

230
00:09:02,720 --> 00:09:05,990
Did it have a metal toilet next to the bed?

231
00:09:06,890 --> 00:09:08,400
It still counts.

232
00:09:08,400 --> 00:09:10,110
You know, how is this any different

233
00:09:10,110 --> 00:09:11,860
from you making me live with Sheldon?

234
00:09:11,860 --> 00:09:13,060
You... Hey!

235
00:09:13,060 --> 00:09:16,250
I shared my Honey Nut Cheerios with you.

236
00:09:17,180 --> 00:09:20,130
You gave me a bill at the end of every month.

237
00:09:21,880 --> 00:09:22,700
Stay out of this.

238
00:09:22,700 --> 00:09:25,090
You and your stupid machine started this fight!

239
00:09:25,090 --> 00:09:26,850
You are lucky that this feelings machine

240
00:09:26,850 --> 00:09:29,030
doesn't have feelings.

241
00:09:29,550 --> 00:09:30,950
Come on, Sheldon, let's go.

242
00:09:30,950 --> 00:09:33,270
Gladly. Can we storm out?

243
00:09:33,270 --> 00:09:36,020
I think it loses its impact if we're chatting about it.

244
00:09:36,020 --> 00:09:36,610
Fine.

245
00:09:36,610 --> 00:09:38,310
I'll just give them the finger.

246
00:09:43,020 --> 00:09:45,310
Okay, first off,

247
00:09:45,310 --> 00:09:48,340
I want to thank you all so much for coming.

248
00:09:48,340 --> 00:09:50,490
Howard is here to interpret for Emily,

249
00:09:50,490 --> 00:09:52,420
and to take notes.

250
00:09:54,240 --> 00:09:57,210
No, he doesn't think it's stupid.

251
00:09:57,620 --> 00:10:00,350
Uh, heads up, both of you are named Emily,

252
00:10:00,350 --> 00:10:03,390
so we'll call you "Red-headed Emily"

253
00:10:03,390 --> 00:10:08,030
and you, "Red-headed Emily, Junior."

254
00:10:11,760 --> 00:10:13,640
Hey, you went out with him. I didn't.

255
00:10:15,070 --> 00:10:17,680
Okay, uh, let's get things started.

256
00:10:17,680 --> 00:10:20,290
Um, why don't we go around the room,

257
00:10:20,290 --> 00:10:21,390
say your name,

258
00:10:21,390 --> 00:10:23,350
and why you broke up with me.

259
00:10:23,350 --> 00:10:24,750
Want to kick it off?

260
00:10:24,750 --> 00:10:28,310
Oh, okay. Um... I'm Lucy,

261
00:10:28,310 --> 00:10:30,240
and I broke up with Raj

262
00:10:30,240 --> 00:10:32,500
because I have severe social anxiety,

263
00:10:32,500 --> 00:10:33,660
and he kept trying to force me

264
00:10:33,660 --> 00:10:36,070
into uncomfortable situations.

265
00:10:37,140 --> 00:10:38,780
Like this one?

266
00:10:38,780 --> 00:10:40,420
Yeah.

267
00:10:40,420 --> 00:10:41,820
I did do that.

268
00:10:41,820 --> 00:10:44,430
I can be insensitive to other people's boundaries.

269
00:10:44,430 --> 00:10:45,910
Howard, would you write that down?

270
00:10:45,910 --> 00:10:48,680
Oh... schmuck. Got it.

271
00:10:48,940 --> 00:10:50,390
Uh, next?

272
00:10:50,970 --> 00:10:53,310
Okay. Um...

273
00:10:53,310 --> 00:10:55,000
I'm Claire.

274
00:10:55,000 --> 00:10:56,110
And I guess I broke up with you

275
00:10:56,110 --> 00:10:58,980
because you were just really needy.

276
00:10:59,280 --> 00:11:00,820
Also, you were incredibly vain--

277
00:11:00,820 --> 00:11:01,860
like, all the time you spent

278
00:11:01,860 --> 00:11:02,830
shaping your eyebrows...

279
00:11:02,830 --> 00:11:05,830
Okay, new rule-- everybody only gets one.

280
00:11:06,710 --> 00:11:08,200
Uh, next?

281
00:11:08,790 --> 00:11:10,360
Ooh, I'm not sure I'm comfortable

282
00:11:10,360 --> 00:11:13,010
sharing details about our relationship in front of Howard.

283
00:11:13,590 --> 00:11:15,420
He's here to support me, so anything you have to say

284
00:11:15,420 --> 00:11:16,980
you can say in front of him.

285
00:11:16,980 --> 00:11:19,840
Okay. Well, whenever you and I were in bed...

286
00:11:19,840 --> 00:11:22,140
Howard, get out.

287
00:11:23,240 --> 00:11:24,790
Not a chance.

288
00:11:25,360 --> 00:11:28,990
So, you were telling us how Raj was terrible in bed.

289
00:11:32,030 --> 00:11:34,520
Sheldon, dinner's ready.

290
00:11:34,520 --> 00:11:36,470
I made beef loaf, because I know you're uncomfortable

291
00:11:36,470 --> 00:11:39,450
with the non-specificity of meat loaf.

292
00:11:40,970 --> 00:11:42,140
Sheldon?

293
00:11:46,510 --> 00:11:48,050
Hey, are you okay?

294
00:11:48,050 --> 00:11:49,500
Not really.

295
00:11:49,500 --> 00:11:50,780
What's going on?

296
00:11:50,780 --> 00:11:53,250
I wish I never tried that device.

297
00:11:53,250 --> 00:11:55,470
And I know I said the same thing after the massage chair,

298
00:11:55,470 --> 00:11:57,740
but this time I mean it.

299
00:11:58,590 --> 00:12:01,610
I'm sorry Leonard and Penny hurt your feelings.

300
00:12:01,610 --> 00:12:03,210
It's more than that.

301
00:12:03,210 --> 00:12:04,720
It's me.

302
00:12:04,720 --> 00:12:05,490
I always knew

303
00:12:05,490 --> 00:12:07,820
I had trouble recognizing other people's emotions,

304
00:12:07,820 --> 00:12:11,610
but that machine just made it so real.

305
00:12:11,610 --> 00:12:14,430
Well, everybody has things that they need help with.

306
00:12:14,430 --> 00:12:17,000
Like me-- I can't see without my glasses.

307
00:12:17,000 --> 00:12:19,610
And right now you're just a, a cute, pink smudge wearing

308
00:12:19,610 --> 00:12:22,270
a childish green smudge.

309
00:12:22,920 --> 00:12:26,410
I thought I was getting better at it, but clearly I'm not.

310
00:12:27,080 --> 00:12:29,050
Yes, you are.

311
00:12:29,050 --> 00:12:30,220
There have definitely been days

312
00:12:30,220 --> 00:12:32,610
when I was sad and you could tell.

313
00:12:32,610 --> 00:12:34,880
Yeah, but that's shooting fish in a barrel.

314
00:12:34,880 --> 00:12:37,300
You're kind of a sad sack.

315
00:12:39,500 --> 00:12:41,270
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said that.

316
00:12:41,270 --> 00:12:43,100
I'm just upset.

317
00:12:43,100 --> 00:12:44,650
No, see, right there,

318
00:12:44,650 --> 00:12:46,450
you knew you hurt my feelings.

319
00:12:46,450 --> 00:12:48,020
And I'm proud of you--

320
00:12:48,020 --> 00:12:51,850
for reasons I'm sure have something to do with my father.

321
00:12:53,100 --> 00:12:55,010
And if you don't like

322
00:12:55,010 --> 00:12:57,080
that machine, get rid of it.

323
00:12:57,080 --> 00:13:00,530
Because I love you exactly the way you are.

324
00:13:07,830 --> 00:13:10,330
I feel the same way about you.

325
00:13:11,810 --> 00:13:13,080
Now, put your glasses back on.

326
00:13:13,080 --> 00:13:14,830
You look weird.

327
00:13:18,950 --> 00:13:20,730
I thought you were great,

328
00:13:20,730 --> 00:13:22,750
but, oh, my God, you were

329
00:13:22,750 --> 00:13:25,240
so dominated by your parents.

330
00:13:25,240 --> 00:13:26,910
Oh, yeah, and that used to drive me nuts.

331
00:13:26,910 --> 00:13:28,560
He's kind of a mama's boy.

332
00:13:28,560 --> 00:13:29,440
- Kind of? - Whoa, okay!

333
00:13:29,440 --> 00:13:31,280
That's enough.

334
00:13:31,740 --> 00:13:34,240
Write down "Loving son."

335
00:13:35,410 --> 00:13:37,570
Can I just say something?

336
00:13:37,570 --> 00:13:39,090
Going out with Raj

337
00:13:39,090 --> 00:13:41,680
was one of the best things that ever happened to me.

338
00:13:41,680 --> 00:13:44,160
Yes, I'll take you back.

339
00:13:46,880 --> 00:13:48,610
Let me finish.

340
00:13:48,610 --> 00:13:51,100
It's like I needed to go through that experience

341
00:13:51,100 --> 00:13:54,990
to know what exactly I don't want in a man.

342
00:13:54,990 --> 00:13:58,160
Well, that's hard to hear, but I'll still take you back.

343
00:13:58,990 --> 00:14:01,380
You know, the same thing happened to me.

344
00:14:01,380 --> 00:14:03,830
After I broke up with Raj, I met Gary,

345
00:14:03,830 --> 00:14:05,500
who's just amazing.

346
00:14:05,500 --> 00:14:07,190
Sorry, is that "Gary" with one R or two?

347
00:14:07,190 --> 00:14:09,420
Would you stop writing?!

348
00:14:10,110 --> 00:14:12,320
Just wait. So... did all of you

349
00:14:12,320 --> 00:14:14,520
go on to better relationships after me?

350
00:14:14,520 --> 00:14:15,130
Oh, yeah.

351
00:14:15,130 --> 00:14:15,970
Without question.

352
00:14:15,970 --> 00:14:18,400
Little before, actually.

353
00:14:23,800 --> 00:14:25,700
Don't let him get away.

354
00:14:25,700 --> 00:14:27,470
Wait. What did she say?

355
00:14:27,470 --> 00:14:29,430
Uh, basically, she traded you

356
00:14:29,430 --> 00:14:31,610
for Bruce Wayne.

357
00:14:32,960 --> 00:14:35,580
Okay, maybe we should just end this.

358
00:14:35,580 --> 00:14:37,230
Wait, hang on.

359
00:14:37,230 --> 00:14:39,400
I just want to point out to everyone here,

360
00:14:39,730 --> 00:14:42,980
this is a man who is going to great lengths

361
00:14:42,980 --> 00:14:44,820
to better himself.

362
00:14:44,820 --> 00:14:46,340
Even at the risk of...

363
00:14:46,340 --> 00:14:47,760
being humiliated.

364
00:14:47,760 --> 00:14:50,750
And I, for one, think that's very brave.

365
00:14:50,750 --> 00:14:52,150
Thank you, Howard.

366
00:14:52,150 --> 00:14:56,120
Honestly, I'm surprised you two didn't wind up together.

367
00:14:58,620 --> 00:15:01,400
Well, like you gals, I had to suffer through him

368
00:15:01,400 --> 00:15:03,520
to find Bernadette.

369
00:15:03,790 --> 00:15:06,180
Wish it were you.

370
00:15:09,460 --> 00:15:10,570
Yes?

371
00:15:10,570 --> 00:15:12,780
We owe you an apology.

372
00:15:12,780 --> 00:15:15,210
Oh, it's fine. You needed a suitcase,

373
00:15:15,210 --> 00:15:17,890
I wasn't home, you borrowed a suitcase.

374
00:15:17,890 --> 00:15:21,040
That was six years ago. I'm talking about tonight.

375
00:15:22,630 --> 00:15:25,400
Well, I thought we were going in order.

376
00:15:26,950 --> 00:15:28,200
Look, we got really angry at each other,

377
00:15:28,200 --> 00:15:29,800
and you just got caught in the middle of it.

378
00:15:29,800 --> 00:15:30,500
And...

379
00:15:30,500 --> 00:15:31,930
sorry about the suitcase.

380
00:15:31,930 --> 00:15:32,770
Yeah, well, you should be.

381
00:15:32,770 --> 00:15:34,040
Your socks were still in it.

382
00:15:34,040 --> 00:15:36,010
I had to throw it away.

383
00:15:36,620 --> 00:15:37,250
Anyway,

384
00:15:37,250 --> 00:15:39,600
I, uh, trust that you've resolved your conflict.

385
00:15:39,600 --> 00:15:40,870
Yes, we're fine.

386
00:15:40,870 --> 00:15:42,220
Mm, Penny's gonna call her dad and tell him it's not

387
00:15:42,220 --> 00:15:43,880
a good time for Randall to visit.

388
00:15:43,880 --> 00:15:46,010
Hopefully, he won't be too upset.

389
00:15:46,010 --> 00:15:48,430
Oh, you're his little girl-- he can't stay mad at you.

390
00:15:48,430 --> 00:15:49,690
He won't be mad at me.

391
00:15:49,690 --> 00:15:52,170
I mean, you're the one who doesn't want my brother to come, so...

392
00:15:53,730 --> 00:15:55,750
So you're gonna throw me under the bus?

393
00:15:55,750 --> 00:15:57,250
Oh, I'm gonna throw you so hard,

394
00:15:57,250 --> 00:16:00,390
I might actually win a stuffed animal.

395
00:16:02,840 --> 00:16:05,760
Uh, guys, it sounds like you're getting angry again.

396
00:16:05,760 --> 00:16:06,840
That's because we are.

397
00:16:06,840 --> 00:16:07,880
Yes!

398
00:16:07,880 --> 00:16:09,340
I don't need an emotion machine!

399
00:16:09,340 --> 00:16:11,090
I am one!

400
00:16:14,720 --> 00:16:16,720
Thanks, ladies! This was fun!

401
00:16:16,720 --> 00:16:20,730
Let's not wait so long for another bizarre, awkward night.

402
00:16:21,780 --> 00:16:23,290
Well, that was a waste of time.

403
00:16:23,290 --> 00:16:24,600
I'm such an idiot.

404
00:16:24,600 --> 00:16:25,700
Don't beat yourself up.

405
00:16:25,700 --> 00:16:27,760
That's what I'm here for.

406
00:16:28,130 --> 00:16:28,940
Maybe I won't settle down.

407
00:16:28,940 --> 00:16:30,790
Maybe I'll just play the field.

408
00:16:30,790 --> 00:16:32,190
Yeah, the field was just here.

409
00:16:32,190 --> 00:16:34,270
The field said no.

410
00:16:35,910 --> 00:16:37,540
Dude, come on.

411
00:16:37,790 --> 00:16:39,510
Okay, I'll tell you what.

412
00:16:39,510 --> 00:16:40,170
I'll make you a deal.

413
00:16:40,170 --> 00:16:42,370
30 years from now, if you're still single

414
00:16:42,370 --> 00:16:44,880
and things don't work out with me and Bernadette...

415
00:16:44,880 --> 00:16:47,250
you and I can give it a go.

416
00:16:48,040 --> 00:16:50,280
I appreciate the offer, but if things don't work out with you two,

417
00:16:50,280 --> 00:16:52,920
I'm swooping in on her like a vulture.

418
00:16:53,370 --> 00:16:55,800
Too late. Stuart called dibs.

419
00:16:56,810 --> 00:16:59,000
But theoretically, if you and I

420
00:16:59,000 --> 00:17:01,460
were in a gay relationship,

421
00:17:01,460 --> 00:17:03,090
how would we tell people?

422
00:17:03,090 --> 00:17:05,140
Like, print up announcements?

423
00:17:05,650 --> 00:17:07,470
I don't know. What difference does it make?

424
00:17:07,470 --> 00:17:11,050
Well, I want to make sure we get invited to all the parades.

425
00:17:11,510 --> 00:17:12,830
Those do look fun.

426
00:17:12,830 --> 00:17:15,570
Yeah. Well, if you want to march in a fishnet crop top,

427
00:17:15,570 --> 00:17:17,950
you better lay off that dip.

428
00:17:18,920 --> 00:17:19,610
If you didn't want me to eat it,

429
00:17:19,610 --> 00:17:21,650
- why'd you put it out? - It was for the girls.

430
00:17:21,650 --> 00:17:24,480
They broke up with me-- I don't care if they get fat.

431
00:17:25,330 --> 00:17:26,630
I'm not gonna get fat.

432
00:17:26,630 --> 00:17:30,100
Oh, you want to bet? You never exercise.

433
00:17:30,100 --> 00:17:33,020
Fine. Look, I'll exercise right now.

434
00:17:33,020 --> 00:17:34,120
One...

435
00:17:35,780 --> 00:17:36,850
two...

436
00:17:38,590 --> 00:17:40,450
These are crunches, by the way.

437
00:17:40,450 --> 00:17:41,320
Very mature.

438
00:17:41,320 --> 00:17:42,060
Keep eating like that.

439
00:17:42,060 --> 00:17:43,270
You're gonna have a heart attack.

440
00:17:43,270 --> 00:17:45,710
Okay. How about if I eat like this?

441
00:17:50,050 --> 00:17:51,790
You're such a child.

442
00:17:51,790 --> 00:17:54,220
Hey, is that any way to talk to your future husband?

443
00:17:54,220 --> 00:17:55,800
Hey, I was being hypothetical, okay?

444
00:17:55,800 --> 00:17:57,900
- I would never marry you. - Please.

445
00:17:57,900 --> 00:17:59,720
When you see the ring I pick out, you're gonna melt.

446
00:17:59,720 --> 00:18:01,290
Yeah, right.

447
00:18:01,290 --> 00:18:02,160
Wait, is it rose gold?

448
00:18:02,160 --> 00:18:04,820
Actually, don't tell me. I want to be surprised.

449
00:18:10,670 --> 00:18:12,820
So, did you wind up sending that machine back?

450
00:18:12,820 --> 00:18:15,600
I did. You know, I'm not even sure how accurate it was.

451
00:18:15,600 --> 00:18:19,500
I took it to the train store-- it said everyone was sad.

452
00:18:21,340 --> 00:18:23,430
I finally got Halley to sleep.

453
00:18:23,430 --> 00:18:25,350
You know, I just read a study that suggests

454
00:18:25,350 --> 00:18:27,180
new mothers are better at senseing emotions

455
00:18:27,180 --> 00:18:28,630
for up to two years.

456
00:18:28,630 --> 00:18:29,440
It's ture.

457
00:18:29,440 --> 00:18:31,550
Pregnancy causes physiological change in the brain,

458
00:18:31,550 --> 00:18:33,310
and resulting increase empathetic.

459
00:18:33,310 --> 00:18:36,750
So all we need to do is got Shledon knocked up.

460
00:18:37,650 --> 00:18:41,460
Can't. He's already fixed when I found him at the shelter.

461
00:18:42,150 --> 00:18:44,150
Hey, Bernadette, let's test this theory.

462
00:18:44,150 --> 00:18:46,360
What're you thinking I'm feeling right now?

463
00:18:46,360 --> 00:18:47,650
Let's see.

464
00:18:47,650 --> 00:18:49,090
You're better than us?

465
00:18:49,090 --> 00:18:50,600
A little bit sorry for us?

466
00:18:50,600 --> 00:18:54,810
But mostly gald you don't have to be us.

467
00:18:56,500 --> 00:18:59,160
Keep filling this one with baby, she's good.

