1
00:00:01,250 --> 00:00:03,510
Previously on The Big Bang Theory.

2
00:00:11,390 --> 00:00:12,930
Hello.

3
00:00:13,480 --> 00:00:15,790
I'm looking for Howard Wolowitz.

4
00:00:15,790 --> 00:00:17,390
May I ask what this is about?

5
00:00:17,390 --> 00:00:18,910
No, you may not.

6
00:00:19,310 --> 00:00:20,530
Very well.

7
00:00:23,280 --> 00:00:26,730
Hi, Colonel Williams, how can I help you?

8
00:00:26,730 --> 00:00:30,040
Okay, sure, I can meet with you on Thursday.

9
00:00:30,040 --> 00:00:31,730
Caltech is fine.

10
00:00:31,730 --> 00:00:34,970
Yeah, and may I ask what this is about?

11
00:00:35,640 --> 00:00:37,310
I may not?

12
00:00:37,670 --> 00:00:39,630
That's what he said to me.

13
00:00:42,120 --> 00:00:43,470
Look at this.

14
00:00:43,470 --> 00:00:46,770
Elon Musk has a theory that we're all just characters

15
00:00:46,770 --> 00:00:49,880
in some advanced civilization's video game.

16
00:00:49,880 --> 00:00:51,600
So some alien kid spent his money

17
00:00:51,600 --> 00:00:54,880
on the asthma-and-glasses upgrade for me?

18
00:00:56,550 --> 00:00:59,650
Well, he doesn't say it's a good game.

19
00:01:01,300 --> 00:01:03,530
- All right, we got a problem. - What's up?

20
00:01:03,530 --> 00:01:06,040
The Air Force contacted me about our quantum gyroscope.

21
00:01:06,040 --> 00:01:07,660
- They want to have a meeting. - Really?

22
00:01:07,660 --> 00:01:09,800
Yeah. This military guy showed up at Howard's door.

23
00:01:09,800 --> 00:01:11,330
He was terrifying.

24
00:01:11,330 --> 00:01:12,560
Oh, what did he say?

25
00:01:12,560 --> 00:01:13,790
He gave me his business card

26
00:01:13,790 --> 00:01:17,570
and asked me to please pass it along to Howard.

27
00:01:18,530 --> 00:01:20,680
That doesn't sound terrifying.

28
00:01:20,680 --> 00:01:23,430
To a white guy born here, no.

29
00:01:24,800 --> 00:01:27,170
If you are a brown guy whose name has a lot of syllables in it --

30
00:01:27,170 --> 00:01:29,600
terrifying.

31
00:01:30,400 --> 00:01:33,290
You realize if the military declares our research classified,

32
00:01:33,290 --> 00:01:34,880
they can take the whole thing away from us.

33
00:01:34,880 --> 00:01:35,750
And if that happens,

34
00:01:35,750 --> 00:01:37,350
we'll never be able to sell it commercially.

35
00:01:37,350 --> 00:01:38,350
There goes our big payday.

36
00:01:38,350 --> 00:01:39,560
I was counting on that money--

37
00:01:39,560 --> 00:01:40,940
I need to make as much as my wife

38
00:01:40,940 --> 00:01:43,720
so I don't have to try so hard in bed.

39
00:01:44,520 --> 00:01:45,400
You do that, too?

40
00:01:45,400 --> 00:01:48,100
Oh, yeah. How do you think I stay this thin?

41
00:01:48,860 --> 00:01:51,380
Gentlemen, I think we are losing sight of the real issue.

42
00:01:51,380 --> 00:01:54,700
We are on the precipice of becoming faceless cogs

43
00:01:54,700 --> 00:01:57,040
in the military-industrial complex.

44
00:01:57,040 --> 00:01:59,120
Isn't that exciting?

45
00:01:59,420 --> 00:02:00,610
You're kidding, right?

46
00:02:00,610 --> 00:02:04,300
Not at all. In Star Wars, when the stormtroopers

47
00:02:04,300 --> 00:02:06,130
would march in perfect formation,

48
00:02:06,130 --> 00:02:08,400
harassing civilians, didn't you ever think,

49
00:02:08,400 --> 00:02:10,870
"Hey, that could be me"?

50
00:02:10,870 --> 00:02:12,250
Sheldon, we could be contributing

51
00:02:12,250 --> 00:02:14,990
to a weapons system that oppresses mankind

52
00:02:14,990 --> 00:02:17,500
for the next thousand years.

53
00:02:17,570 --> 00:02:19,880
Okay, Howard's on board. What do you think, Leonard?

54
00:02:45,910 --> 00:02:46,900
I'm worried about Howard.

55
00:02:46,900 --> 00:02:48,630
Ever since that guy from the Air Force showed up,

56
00:02:48,630 --> 00:02:50,210
he's been a nervous wreck.

57
00:02:50,210 --> 00:02:52,120
All right, we work at a giant pharmaceutical company.

58
00:02:52,120 --> 00:02:53,720
Get him some anti-anxiety meds.

59
00:02:53,720 --> 00:02:55,710
He won't take any pills that aren't chewable

60
00:02:55,710 --> 00:02:57,740
and shaped like a Flintstone.

61
00:02:58,810 --> 00:03:00,110
You know, when Leonard's feeling anxious

62
00:03:00,110 --> 00:03:01,680
I make him take a long walk.

63
00:03:01,900 --> 00:03:02,880
Does that help?

64
00:03:02,880 --> 00:03:05,730
Well, for a while. Then he comes back.

65
00:03:07,030 --> 00:03:09,110
- I don't believe this. - What's wrong?

66
00:03:09,670 --> 00:03:13,050
This guy from the office just congratulated me on being pregnant.

67
00:03:13,050 --> 00:03:15,300
You did already know, right?

68
00:03:16,590 --> 00:03:18,280
No one at the office did.

69
00:03:18,280 --> 00:03:19,590
- Did you tell anyone? - No.

70
00:03:19,590 --> 00:03:20,860
You told me not to.

71
00:03:20,860 --> 00:03:23,530
I bet it was Barbara Chen in retrovirus.

72
00:03:23,530 --> 00:03:25,590
She might have heard me throwing up one morning.

73
00:03:25,590 --> 00:03:29,020
Every since she got the hearing aid, she thinks she's so great.

74
00:03:30,900 --> 00:03:32,890
Why don't you want anyone to know?

75
00:03:32,890 --> 00:03:35,080
'Cause I'm up for a major immunotherapy study,

76
00:03:35,080 --> 00:03:36,070
and if they find out I'm pregnant

77
00:03:36,070 --> 00:03:37,670
they might give it to someone else.

78
00:03:37,670 --> 00:03:39,010
Would they really do that?

79
00:03:39,010 --> 00:03:41,220
I know they would-- they did it to Barbara Chen last year

80
00:03:41,220 --> 00:03:43,460
when I told everyone she was pregnant.

81
00:03:46,890 --> 00:03:49,100
Wait till I Snapchat that my friends might be working

82
00:03:49,100 --> 00:03:51,930
on a top secret government project.

83
00:03:53,360 --> 00:03:54,140
Are you crazy?

84
00:03:54,140 --> 00:03:56,140
You can't put that on Snapchat.

85
00:03:56,330 --> 00:03:59,600
Fine, I'll put it on Facebook like a caveman.

86
00:04:02,120 --> 00:04:04,890
You know, maybe before our meeting we should talk to a lawyer.

87
00:04:04,890 --> 00:04:06,210
That's not a bad idea.

88
00:04:06,210 --> 00:04:08,720
Well, you must have someone in your family that's a lawyer.

89
00:04:08,720 --> 00:04:10,770
Why? Because I'm Jewish?

90
00:04:10,770 --> 00:04:12,160
That's like me saying, "Hey, you're Indian.

91
00:04:12,160 --> 00:04:14,980
Doesn't your cousin work in a call center?"

92
00:04:16,570 --> 00:04:19,260
My cousin does work in a call center.

93
00:04:21,170 --> 00:04:23,350
And my cousin's a lawyer.

94
00:04:24,790 --> 00:04:27,000
We don't need Howard's cousin, no.

95
00:04:27,000 --> 00:04:29,110
We have me.

96
00:04:29,780 --> 00:04:31,980
You're not a lawyer, Sheldon, you're just a know-it-all.

97
00:04:31,980 --> 00:04:33,410
I am not a know-it-all.

98
00:04:33,410 --> 00:04:35,960
I'm a person who knows lots of things

99
00:04:35,960 --> 00:04:38,850
and likes to correct other people when they're wrong.

100
00:04:39,490 --> 00:04:41,720
That's the definition of being a know-it-all.

101
00:04:41,720 --> 00:04:45,070
Or in German, a Besserwisser.

102
00:04:47,840 --> 00:04:50,220
How did you think you were gonna hide your pregnancy?

103
00:04:50,220 --> 00:04:52,840
I had a plan-- I kept leaving Dove Bar wrappers around

104
00:04:52,840 --> 00:04:54,920
to explain any weight gain.

105
00:04:55,970 --> 00:04:58,680
Where did you get empty Dove Bar wrappers?

106
00:04:58,680 --> 00:05:01,460
From all the Dove Bars I ate! I'm pregnant!

107
00:05:01,460 --> 00:05:03,240
Try to keep up!

108
00:05:05,310 --> 00:05:08,260
I'm sorry. I-I have to go find out if my boss knows.

109
00:05:08,260 --> 00:05:10,370
Well, whatever happens, we're here for you.

110
00:05:10,370 --> 00:05:11,560
Thanks. You guys are the best.

111
00:05:11,560 --> 00:05:13,230
Yeah, drive safe. We love you. And give us a call...

112
00:05:13,230 --> 00:05:14,310
Oh, my God, it was me, it was me!

113
00:05:14,310 --> 00:05:16,090
I'm the one who blabbed she was pregnant!

114
00:05:16,630 --> 00:05:17,740
- What?! - I didn't mean to.

115
00:05:17,740 --> 00:05:19,570
It just slipped out in front of her assistant one day.

116
00:05:19,570 --> 00:05:20,860
I... I forgot my coat.

117
00:05:20,860 --> 00:05:22,090
Oh! Here's your coat, honey.

118
00:05:22,090 --> 00:05:24,030
That's such a cute jacket.

119
00:05:25,620 --> 00:05:27,890
God, I feel so bad-- I just lied to her.

120
00:05:27,890 --> 00:05:29,450
Oh, but you did it so well.

121
00:05:29,450 --> 00:05:31,090
That's amazing!

122
00:05:32,310 --> 00:05:33,780
It's like watching a sculptor,

123
00:05:33,780 --> 00:05:36,310
but your clay was lies.

124
00:05:37,100 --> 00:05:39,130
Is that really what's important right now?

125
00:05:39,130 --> 00:05:41,550
I mean, seriously, you have got to let me scan your brain

126
00:05:41,550 --> 00:05:44,760
when you're being dishonest so I can see what lights up.

127
00:05:45,270 --> 00:05:46,600
That's super helpful, Amy.

128
00:05:46,600 --> 00:05:48,700
Thanks a lot. I can't wait to do that.

129
00:05:49,070 --> 00:05:51,880
I can see a clump of bitch cells lightin' up from here.

130
00:05:55,810 --> 00:05:58,440
Give me a second to call my cousin.

131
00:05:58,440 --> 00:06:01,550
I don't see how a tax lawyer from Fort Lauderdale

132
00:06:01,550 --> 00:06:03,980
could be helpful regarding intellectual property.

133
00:06:03,980 --> 00:06:06,010
First of all, he's in Boca Raton,

134
00:06:06,010 --> 00:06:08,280
which is better than Fort Lauderdale.

135
00:06:09,120 --> 00:06:10,250
But more importantly,

136
00:06:10,250 --> 00:06:12,230
he lasted two days on Jeopardy,

137
00:06:12,230 --> 00:06:14,340
so he's clearly a smart guy.

138
00:06:18,240 --> 00:06:19,400
Hello.

139
00:06:19,400 --> 00:06:21,960
Hey, Marty. Thanks for talking to us.

140
00:06:21,960 --> 00:06:22,740
Hey, no problem.

141
00:06:22,740 --> 00:06:24,630
Thanks for going to outer space so no matter what I do

142
00:06:24,630 --> 00:06:27,000
my mom will be disappointed in me.

143
00:06:28,380 --> 00:06:31,790
Well, I married a little Catholic girl, so we're even.

144
00:06:32,250 --> 00:06:34,120
Anyway, this is Leonard and Sheldon.

145
00:06:34,120 --> 00:06:36,070
The three of us came up with the guidance system.

146
00:06:36,070 --> 00:06:36,870
- Hi. - Hello.

147
00:06:36,870 --> 00:06:38,090
And this is my friend, Raj.

148
00:06:38,090 --> 00:06:39,570
Oh, I'm not on the patent. I'm just here

149
00:06:39,570 --> 00:06:42,720
because there's a bumblebee in my office.

150
00:06:43,840 --> 00:06:45,660
I saw it. It's big.

151
00:06:47,140 --> 00:06:48,880
Anyway, like I said in the e-mail,

152
00:06:48,880 --> 00:06:50,280
this meeting's on Thursday.

153
00:06:50,280 --> 00:06:52,080
Do you have any advice for us?

154
00:06:52,080 --> 00:06:54,220
Well, I don't know much about patent law.

155
00:06:54,220 --> 00:06:55,980
But, uh, my advice is:

156
00:06:55,980 --> 00:06:58,620
hear them out, offer as little information as possible,

157
00:06:58,620 --> 00:07:01,120
and whatever you do, don't sign anything.

158
00:07:01,120 --> 00:07:03,900
"Don't sign anything"? That's your advice?

159
00:07:03,900 --> 00:07:05,990
Okay, so, uh, if during this meeting,

160
00:07:05,990 --> 00:07:09,020
one of us were to, say, complete an oil painting,

161
00:07:09,020 --> 00:07:12,020
you'd recommend that we leave that unsigned?

162
00:07:12,990 --> 00:07:13,890
That's not what I meant.

163
00:07:13,890 --> 00:07:14,920
That's what you said.

164
00:07:14,920 --> 00:07:16,390
That's not what I meant.

165
00:07:16,700 --> 00:07:18,970
This must be how you practice law in Boca Raton,

166
00:07:18,970 --> 00:07:20,210
by saying things you don't mean

167
00:07:20,210 --> 00:07:21,940
and meaning things you don't say.

168
00:07:21,940 --> 00:07:24,440
Howard, why is he yelling at me?

169
00:07:25,890 --> 00:07:27,310
All right, you were on Jeopardy.

170
00:07:27,310 --> 00:07:28,870
Allow me to Alex Trebek

171
00:07:28,870 --> 00:07:30,520
this and put it in the form of a question:

172
00:07:30,520 --> 00:07:34,000
Who has been a complete waste of our time?

173
00:07:35,460 --> 00:07:36,650
Marty, let me call you back.

174
00:07:36,650 --> 00:07:38,330
Someday, when I'm up on murder charges,

175
00:07:38,330 --> 00:07:40,110
you'll be hearing from me.

176
00:07:41,330 --> 00:07:43,600
You don't need him. I'll represent you.

177
00:07:47,000 --> 00:07:48,870
- Hi. - Hey. What brings you by?

178
00:07:48,870 --> 00:07:51,850
Oh, had to go to a sales seminar on our new sleeping pill.

179
00:07:51,850 --> 00:07:53,470
- Oh. How was it? - Great.

180
00:07:53,470 --> 00:07:55,920
- Fell asleep? - In, like, two minutes. Yeah.

181
00:07:56,660 --> 00:07:58,620
So, how is everything going around here?

182
00:07:58,620 --> 00:08:01,220
Are you still upset about people finding out you're pregnant?

183
00:08:01,220 --> 00:08:03,360
I'm furious.

184
00:08:03,360 --> 00:08:05,040
Sure, sure.

185
00:08:05,670 --> 00:08:07,350
Uh, did you ever figure out who told?

186
00:08:07,350 --> 00:08:10,010
No. I confronted Barbara Chen, but she claimed

187
00:08:10,010 --> 00:08:11,950
she didn't know what I was talking about.

188
00:08:11,950 --> 00:08:14,570
Well, I guess it's just gonna remain a mystery,

189
00:08:14,570 --> 00:08:16,870
you know, like whatever happened in that seminar

190
00:08:16,870 --> 00:08:18,890
after they dimmed the lights.

191
00:08:19,960 --> 00:08:21,340
It had to be Barbara.

192
00:08:21,340 --> 00:08:24,200
I've been trying to figure out a way to get back at her.

193
00:08:24,200 --> 00:08:26,350
Do you think using her work computer to Google

194
00:08:26,350 --> 00:08:29,290
"How to be a prostitute" is over the line?

195
00:08:30,510 --> 00:08:32,250
Uh, you know, when I was in high school,

196
00:08:32,250 --> 00:08:35,150
there was this girl who was talking about me behind my back,

197
00:08:35,150 --> 00:08:36,230
so me and all my friends,

198
00:08:36,230 --> 00:08:39,630
we cornered her in the bathroom and forgave her.

199
00:08:41,230 --> 00:08:42,630
What kind of revenge is that?

200
00:08:42,630 --> 00:08:45,990
This woman screwed with my job. She's got to pay.

201
00:08:45,990 --> 00:08:48,530
Okay, all right, honey, you know what?

202
00:08:49,240 --> 00:08:51,590
There was something I was too scared to tell you yesterday,

203
00:08:51,590 --> 00:08:56,040
a-and now... I'm just balls-out terrified to tell you, but...

204
00:08:56,040 --> 00:08:57,330
the truth is it...

205
00:08:57,530 --> 00:08:59,660
wasn't Barbara Chen, it was me.

206
00:08:59,930 --> 00:09:01,700
I'm the reason everyone knows.

207
00:09:01,700 --> 00:09:02,890
Why did you do that?

208
00:09:02,890 --> 00:09:06,350
Well, it was an accident. I am so sorry I lied.

209
00:09:07,230 --> 00:09:08,550
Get out.

210
00:09:13,720 --> 00:09:17,420
Oh, you know, I also lied about the girl in the bathroom.

211
00:09:17,420 --> 00:09:19,590
Yeah, we actually dumped her retainer in the toilet

212
00:09:19,590 --> 00:09:21,920
and put it back in her mouth.

213
00:09:26,870 --> 00:09:29,570
I don't understand why I can't talk at this meeting.

214
00:09:29,570 --> 00:09:32,220
'Cause when you talk, it enrages people.

215
00:09:34,220 --> 00:09:35,310
Okay.

216
00:09:35,310 --> 00:09:36,440
Quick question.

217
00:09:36,440 --> 00:09:38,760
Am I allowed to exchange pleasantries

218
00:09:38,760 --> 00:09:40,200
upon meeting this colonel?

219
00:09:40,200 --> 00:09:41,320
Yes.

220
00:09:41,320 --> 00:09:42,900
Am I allowed to inform him

221
00:09:42,900 --> 00:09:47,210
that Colonel Sanders was never actually in the military?

222
00:09:47,210 --> 00:09:48,110
I'm getting enraged.

223
00:09:48,110 --> 00:09:49,150
Fine.

224
00:09:50,900 --> 00:09:53,170
Can I use text-to-speech software?

225
00:09:53,170 --> 00:09:55,470
- No! - Don't speak.

226
00:09:56,170 --> 00:09:58,390
Aw, nuts.

227
00:09:58,390 --> 00:09:59,530
Gentlemen!

228
00:09:59,530 --> 00:10:00,810
I'm Colonel Williams.

229
00:10:00,810 --> 00:10:02,340
Thank you for meeting with me.

230
00:10:02,340 --> 00:10:03,600
- Hi. - Hello.

231
00:10:05,900 --> 00:10:09,880
So, which one of you is the brains behind all this?

232
00:10:09,880 --> 00:10:11,670
It's a group effort,

233
00:10:11,670 --> 00:10:16,000
but I guess if we had to pick a main brain, it would be me.

234
00:10:23,990 --> 00:10:25,700
And because of the quantum vortices,

235
00:10:25,700 --> 00:10:26,900
this can run perpetually?

236
00:10:26,900 --> 00:10:27,890
Exactly.

237
00:10:27,890 --> 00:10:29,930
Yeah, you have a good grasp of the physics.

238
00:10:29,930 --> 00:10:32,470
- Well, I'm a scientist by training. - Really?

239
00:10:32,470 --> 00:10:33,430
You're a physicist?

240
00:10:33,430 --> 00:10:35,770
Better. I'm an engineer.

241
00:10:41,540 --> 00:10:43,020
Where did you go to school?

242
00:10:43,020 --> 00:10:44,050
MIT.

243
00:10:44,050 --> 00:10:45,900
Oh. Well, hey, me, too.

244
00:10:45,900 --> 00:10:46,680
I should have known.

245
00:10:46,680 --> 00:10:49,880
Behind every great invention is an MIT mind.

246
00:10:53,460 --> 00:10:55,060
I'll cut to the chase.

247
00:10:55,060 --> 00:10:58,530
The Air Force believes there's an application for this technology,

248
00:10:58,530 --> 00:11:01,510
and we're interested in funding your research.

249
00:11:01,510 --> 00:11:03,470
Well, thanks, but you should know

250
00:11:03,470 --> 00:11:07,200
we're a little concerned about this being used in weapons.

251
00:11:07,200 --> 00:11:09,320
Oh, well, let me put your mind at ease.

252
00:11:09,320 --> 00:11:12,410
What we use it for is none of your business.

253
00:11:15,250 --> 00:11:17,500
I don't know how I feel about this.

254
00:11:17,500 --> 00:11:19,640
Look, guys, it's just a guidance system.

255
00:11:19,640 --> 00:11:21,300
It's not like you're handing us

256
00:11:21,300 --> 00:11:23,820
the Death Star from Star Trek.

257
00:11:28,940 --> 00:11:30,540
All you need to worry about is,

258
00:11:30,540 --> 00:11:32,910
right now, it's this big,

259
00:11:32,910 --> 00:11:36,730
and we need it to be... this big.

260
00:11:36,730 --> 00:11:39,680
That's a lot less big.

261
00:11:39,680 --> 00:11:43,920
Yes, it's... this much less big.

262
00:11:44,200 --> 00:11:46,640
I'm not even sure that's possible.

263
00:11:46,640 --> 00:11:48,630
Well, I ran it by some colleagues at MIT,

264
00:11:48,630 --> 00:11:51,240
and they thought they could get it done in four months.

265
00:11:51,240 --> 00:11:54,200
- Four months? - Yeah, we'll do it in two!

266
00:11:54,700 --> 00:11:56,160
Hi. I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.

267
00:11:56,160 --> 00:11:58,410
I'm the actual brains behind this project.

268
00:11:58,410 --> 00:12:00,480
Also, engineers aren't real scientists,

269
00:12:00,480 --> 00:12:01,910
MIT's a trade school,

270
00:12:01,910 --> 00:12:05,530
and the Death Star is from Star Wars, not Star Trek!

271
00:12:06,060 --> 00:12:07,150
But otherwise,

272
00:12:07,150 --> 00:12:09,460
thank you for your service.

273
00:12:16,510 --> 00:12:19,120
Howard told me you were working late, so I brought dinner.

274
00:12:19,120 --> 00:12:21,620
Oh, thanks. You know, I just wanted to get some work done

275
00:12:21,620 --> 00:12:24,550
without people congratulating me about the baby every five minutes.

276
00:12:24,550 --> 00:12:26,010
I spent my day alone in the lab

277
00:12:26,010 --> 00:12:28,700
waiting for a rat to die of anthrax.

278
00:12:29,900 --> 00:12:32,560
Did you come here to bring me dinner or to gloat?

279
00:12:33,770 --> 00:12:35,620
Well, I came to see how you were feeling,

280
00:12:35,620 --> 00:12:38,140
but I'm guessing still angry?

281
00:12:38,140 --> 00:12:39,050
I'm sorry.

282
00:12:39,050 --> 00:12:41,730
My boss wants to meet with me, and I'm stressing.

283
00:12:41,730 --> 00:12:44,150
You really think they're gonna start treating you differently?

284
00:12:44,150 --> 00:12:45,350
Are you kidding?

285
00:12:45,350 --> 00:12:47,420
I've always been treated differently!

286
00:12:47,420 --> 00:12:49,670
Look at me! Listen to me!

287
00:12:49,670 --> 00:12:52,060
I mean, the first thought when you see me isn't,

288
00:12:52,060 --> 00:12:53,320
"That's a scientist."

289
00:12:53,320 --> 00:12:56,820
It's, "I wonder if her mommy knows where she is."

290
00:12:58,730 --> 00:13:01,830
I am really regretting that I got you a Happy Meal.

291
00:13:05,250 --> 00:13:07,250
I've worked so hard to get where I am,

292
00:13:07,250 --> 00:13:09,290
and I don't want to get sent back to square one

293
00:13:09,290 --> 00:13:11,150
because I'm pregnant.

294
00:13:11,150 --> 00:13:13,070
I understand how you feel.

295
00:13:13,070 --> 00:13:14,540
Thank you.

296
00:13:14,540 --> 00:13:17,060
I wish there were some way I could make it better.

297
00:13:17,060 --> 00:13:20,120
Well, you brought me French fries. That's a start.

298
00:13:20,120 --> 00:13:24,370
Uh, actually, I got you apple slices 'cause you're pregnant.

299
00:13:25,500 --> 00:13:27,330
Apple slices?

300
00:13:27,330 --> 00:13:30,600
What kind of lunatic goes to McDonald's and gets fruit?!

301
00:13:30,600 --> 00:13:31,710
I'll be right back.

302
00:13:33,290 --> 00:13:34,770
And a chocolate shake!

303
00:13:42,940 --> 00:13:43,920
What are you doing?

304
00:13:43,920 --> 00:13:47,710
Oh, Leonard's mad at me, so I'm making him lemon bars.

305
00:13:48,710 --> 00:13:50,560
Does he even like lemon bars?

306
00:13:50,560 --> 00:13:52,400
Not really.

307
00:13:52,800 --> 00:13:56,280
But I'm mad at him, too, so lemon bars it is.

308
00:13:57,080 --> 00:13:58,750
Something happen at the meeting?

309
00:13:58,750 --> 00:14:01,120
They made me promise I wouldn't talk.

310
00:14:01,120 --> 00:14:02,820
- And you talked? - Well, now, see?

311
00:14:02,820 --> 00:14:03,970
You knew what was gonna happen.

312
00:14:03,970 --> 00:14:05,550
Why didn't they?

313
00:14:06,250 --> 00:14:08,200
Anyway, now we're committed to completing this project

314
00:14:08,200 --> 00:14:09,890
in a ridiculously short time frame,

315
00:14:09,890 --> 00:14:11,990
and everyone's upset with me.

316
00:14:11,990 --> 00:14:13,280
Well, if it makes you feel any better,

317
00:14:13,280 --> 00:14:15,610
Bernadette's mad at me, too.

318
00:14:15,610 --> 00:14:17,570
If it makes you feel any better,

319
00:14:17,570 --> 00:14:20,520
a parasitoid wasp known as Oobius depressus

320
00:14:20,520 --> 00:14:25,420
has been rediscovered after 101 years of presumed extinction.

321
00:14:26,490 --> 00:14:28,310
Why would that make me feel better?

322
00:14:28,310 --> 00:14:31,820
Why would your Bernadette thing make me feel better?

323
00:14:31,820 --> 00:14:33,740
At least mine was educational.

324
00:14:33,740 --> 00:14:35,330
Okay. Never mind.

325
00:14:35,330 --> 00:14:36,990
Look, I'm sorry.

326
00:14:36,990 --> 00:14:40,150
Tell me why Bernadette is upset with you.

327
00:14:40,150 --> 00:14:42,460
Well, I told people at work that she's pregnant.

328
00:14:42,460 --> 00:14:44,660
She wasn't ready for them to know.

329
00:14:44,660 --> 00:14:45,680
Why would you do that?

330
00:14:45,680 --> 00:14:47,870
Well, it just slipped out. I feel terrible.

331
00:14:47,870 --> 00:14:50,030
See, that's exactly what happened to me,

332
00:14:50,030 --> 00:14:53,320
except that I said it on purpose, and I have no regrets.

333
00:14:55,770 --> 00:14:57,980
Is it even possible to get this done in two months?

334
00:14:57,980 --> 00:14:59,130
Well, maybe. I don't know.

335
00:14:59,130 --> 00:15:01,770
We'll have to work 12 hours a day, seven days a week.

336
00:15:01,770 --> 00:15:04,190
Which means I won't be able to make Penny breakfast every day,

337
00:15:04,190 --> 00:15:06,120
and she'll realize my brioche French toast

338
00:15:06,120 --> 00:15:08,700
was the only thing keeping her in the marriage.

339
00:15:09,590 --> 00:15:10,740
I love your French toast.

340
00:15:10,740 --> 00:15:12,210
Oh, thanks, man.

341
00:15:13,410 --> 00:15:16,090
So, why did you guys even agree to the deadline?

342
00:15:16,090 --> 00:15:17,730
We didn't. Sheldon did.

343
00:15:17,730 --> 00:15:18,650
And you just let him?

344
00:15:18,650 --> 00:15:21,300
Well, the colonel said it was for the good of the country,

345
00:15:21,300 --> 00:15:22,840
and the funding is substantial.

346
00:15:22,840 --> 00:15:24,520
No, but mostly, there was an awkward pause,

347
00:15:24,520 --> 00:15:27,780
and I broke it by saying, "Okay."

348
00:15:28,840 --> 00:15:31,820
So I guess I won't be seeing you guys for a while.

349
00:15:31,820 --> 00:15:33,270
Oh, looks like it. Wow.

350
00:15:33,270 --> 00:15:36,890
You're going off to work with the military, leaving me behind.

351
00:15:36,890 --> 00:15:40,340
Now I know how all those army wives feel.

352
00:15:41,680 --> 00:15:42,390
Would you stop?

353
00:15:42,390 --> 00:15:44,210
We're just gonna be on the other side of campus.

354
00:15:44,210 --> 00:15:46,830
And right here.

355
00:15:48,220 --> 00:15:51,280
You are a deeply silly man.

356
00:15:52,720 --> 00:15:55,030
He is so afraid of his feelings.

357
00:16:01,890 --> 00:16:02,950
Got a minute?

358
00:16:02,950 --> 00:16:05,110
Yeah, come on in.

359
00:16:07,130 --> 00:16:08,990
I just wanted to apologize.

360
00:16:08,990 --> 00:16:11,150
I know what you did was an accident.

361
00:16:11,650 --> 00:16:14,370
Oh, thank you, and I'm sorry I lied about it.

362
00:16:14,370 --> 00:16:16,390
For what it's worth, you're a great liar.

363
00:16:16,390 --> 00:16:19,220
Oh, that's what Amy said.

364
00:16:20,330 --> 00:16:21,870
So what's going on with the research project?

365
00:16:21,870 --> 00:16:23,400
Are they gonna let you run it?

366
00:16:23,630 --> 00:16:25,390
Well, my boss said he hadn't decided yet,

367
00:16:25,390 --> 00:16:26,710
so I gently reminded him

368
00:16:26,710 --> 00:16:28,370
that he's an old rich white guy,

369
00:16:28,370 --> 00:16:29,780
and I'm a sweet little pregnant lady

370
00:16:29,780 --> 00:16:32,590
who's not afraid to cry in front of a jury.

371
00:16:34,070 --> 00:16:35,800
You threatened to sue?

372
00:16:35,800 --> 00:16:38,610
Hey, I learned a long time ago, when you're four feet eleven

373
00:16:38,610 --> 00:16:40,490
and eye level with every guy's crotch,

374
00:16:40,490 --> 00:16:42,750
that's where you punch.

375
00:16:44,010 --> 00:16:45,050
That's funny.

376
00:16:45,050 --> 00:16:47,560
I learned something totally different.

377
00:16:49,790 --> 00:16:50,360
Do you know what?

378
00:16:50,360 --> 00:16:52,290
It's just a research project.

379
00:16:52,290 --> 00:16:53,750
The most important job in the world

380
00:16:53,750 --> 00:16:55,490
is gonna be raising this child.

381
00:16:55,490 --> 00:16:57,450
It's all I need to give my life meaning.

382
00:16:57,450 --> 00:16:59,670
Oh, that's so beautiful.

383
00:16:59,670 --> 00:17:01,330
You believe me? Oh, good.

384
00:17:01,330 --> 00:17:02,840
11 more chumps like you,

385
00:17:02,840 --> 00:17:05,090
I'll have the jury eating out of my hand.

386
00:17:07,500 --> 00:17:10,700
I never realized this building was classified.

387
00:17:10,700 --> 00:17:13,830
Maybe that's because it's classified.

388
00:17:16,240 --> 00:17:18,920
Wish we weren't so far from my parking space.

389
00:17:18,920 --> 00:17:20,470
The way you put away those lemon bars,

390
00:17:20,470 --> 00:17:22,640
perhaps that's a good thing.

391
00:17:23,560 --> 00:17:26,060
I'd like to reinstate the you-not-talking rule.

392
00:17:26,060 --> 00:17:29,140
Why? It clearly doesn't work.

393
00:17:31,030 --> 00:17:32,730
I guess this is it.

394
00:17:32,730 --> 00:17:34,650
Is that a retinal scanner?

395
00:17:34,650 --> 00:17:36,670
Let's find out.

396
00:17:37,400 --> 00:17:40,150
Howard Wolowitz-- access granted.

397
00:17:40,150 --> 00:17:41,680
- No way! - Impressive!

398
00:17:41,680 --> 00:17:43,100
Oh, my turn! My turn!

399
00:17:43,960 --> 00:17:46,290
Leonard Hofstadter-- access granted.

400
00:17:46,290 --> 00:17:48,970
I didn't even have to take my glasses off!

401
00:17:53,370 --> 00:17:55,100
Access denied.

402
00:17:55,100 --> 00:17:57,120
It knows!

403
00:18:01,330 --> 00:18:03,750
Oh, oh, oh, oh, guys, hold me upside down!

404
00:18:11,620 --> 00:18:14,040
Howard Wolowitz, access granted.

