1
00:03:01,440 --> 00:03:06,440
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:03:01,440 --> 00:03:06,440
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:03:01,440 --> 00:03:06,440
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:03:01,940 --> 00:03:06,440
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

5
00:03:01,940 --> 00:03:06,440
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

6
00:03:01,940 --> 00:03:06,440
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

7
00:03:01,940 --> 00:03:06,440
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

8
00:00:01,160 --> 00:00:02,710
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...

9
00:00:02,710 --> 00:00:05,460
My father thinks the reason I can't make a relationship work

10
00:00:05,460 --> 00:00:06,850
is because I'm spoiled.

11
00:00:06,850 --> 00:00:09,330
All right, how much, exactly, does he pay for?

12
00:00:11,090 --> 00:00:12,360
Okay, I'll tell you,

13
00:00:12,360 --> 00:00:14,140
but please don't judge me.

14
00:00:14,140 --> 00:00:19,010
He pays for my car, my rent, and my credit cards.

15
00:00:20,610 --> 00:00:23,920
I'm trying, but I'm judging.

16
00:00:25,180 --> 00:00:26,340
Maybe your dad's right.

17
00:00:26,340 --> 00:00:29,110
Yeah, women do like a man that can support himself.

18
00:00:29,110 --> 00:00:31,040
I have come to an important decision.

19
00:00:31,040 --> 00:00:33,370
I will not be accepting your money anymore.

20
00:00:33,370 --> 00:00:34,480
That's wonderful.

21
00:00:34,480 --> 00:00:35,670
Yes, that is wonderful.

22
00:00:35,670 --> 00:00:38,350
You will no longer be able to accuse me of being spoiled.

23
00:00:38,350 --> 00:00:40,040
I'm so proud of you.

24
00:00:40,040 --> 00:00:41,230
Dad, I'm trying to tell you off,

25
00:00:41,230 --> 00:00:44,710
and you're ruining it with your delight and relief.

26
00:00:52,180 --> 00:00:54,010
Interesting.

27
00:00:56,600 --> 00:00:57,890
Okay.

28
00:00:57,890 --> 00:00:59,010
How bad is it?

29
00:00:59,010 --> 00:00:59,880
Let me put it this way--

30
00:00:59,880 --> 00:01:04,600
do you own a barrel and suspenders?

31
00:01:04,600 --> 00:01:05,770
Are you serious?

32
00:01:05,770 --> 00:01:09,440
I'm not wearing this visor to play women's golf.

33
00:01:11,960 --> 00:01:12,910
Oh, let me guess.

34
00:01:12,910 --> 00:01:17,550
You guys are drafting your fantasy accounting firms.

35
00:01:17,560 --> 00:01:19,580
We're helping Raj figure out his finances.

36
00:01:19,580 --> 00:01:21,620
Well, he has a job. How bad can it be?

37
00:01:21,620 --> 00:01:24,300
Well, his rent and car lease are exceedingly high.

38
00:01:24,300 --> 00:01:26,870
You couple that with his penchant for dining out and shopping...

39
00:01:26,870 --> 00:01:28,560
Wait, wait, not shopping for clothes, right?

40
00:01:28,560 --> 00:01:31,070
Because look.

41
00:01:32,130 --> 00:01:34,570
He also has a remarkable amount of credit card debt.

42
00:01:34,570 --> 00:01:36,750
I thought your dad paid your cards.

43
00:01:36,750 --> 00:01:39,650
I have a card for emergencies that I pay for myself.

44
00:01:39,650 --> 00:01:41,930
What emergency happened at the L.A. Zoo?

45
00:01:41,930 --> 00:01:44,700
That's a penguin I sponsor.

46
00:01:45,330 --> 00:01:47,020
They're losing their homes to global warming,

47
00:01:47,020 --> 00:01:48,820
and my car gets, like, seven miles a gallon,

48
00:01:48,820 --> 00:01:51,130
so I felt bad.

49
00:01:51,130 --> 00:01:53,170
What is Pink Cheeks?

50
00:01:53,170 --> 00:01:56,470
It's intimate waxing. Quit looking at that!

51
00:01:57,720 --> 00:01:59,270
Maybe you should find someone

52
00:01:59,270 --> 00:02:01,650
to help you get your finances under control.

53
00:02:01,650 --> 00:02:02,780
Like a business manager?

54
00:02:02,780 --> 00:02:04,310
No, absolutely not.

55
00:02:04,310 --> 00:02:05,760
You can't afford to hire someone

56
00:02:05,760 --> 00:02:08,620
who'll forbid you from spending your money on foolish expenses.

57
00:02:08,620 --> 00:02:11,750
That is a foolish expense, and I forbid it.

58
00:02:13,560 --> 00:02:16,420
What if there's someone who just likes controlling

59
00:02:16,420 --> 00:02:19,870
other people and stealing joy from their lives?

60
00:02:19,870 --> 00:02:22,870
He sounds like a sociopath.

61
00:02:23,230 --> 00:02:26,920
We don't know, his mother never had him tested.

62
00:02:28,990 --> 00:02:32,130
You're talking about me. Very funny.

63
00:02:32,130 --> 00:02:36,080
Although I would enjoy drawing up a budget

64
00:02:36,080 --> 00:02:37,930
and forcing Raj to adhere to it

65
00:02:37,930 --> 00:02:39,380
without an ounce of compassion.

66
00:02:39,380 --> 00:02:42,820
Wait, wait, who's gonna break it to the penguin?

67
00:02:44,050 --> 00:02:45,380
Okay, Sheldon.

68
00:02:45,380 --> 00:02:47,310
Yeah, I'm putting you in charge of my finances.

69
00:02:47,310 --> 00:02:50,140
I will not spend another penny that you don't authorize.

70
00:02:50,140 --> 00:02:51,240
Very well.

71
00:02:51,240 --> 00:02:53,670
Hey, Comic-Con tickets go on sale this Friday.

72
00:02:53,670 --> 00:02:55,650
You can't buy one.

73
00:02:57,100 --> 00:03:00,280
Oh, better luck next time, Pink Cheeks.

74
00:03:26,830 --> 00:03:29,040
You're actually going to Comic-Con?

75
00:03:29,040 --> 00:03:31,080
Well, Leonard wants me to do more stuff like that with him,

76
00:03:31,080 --> 00:03:33,060
so I thought maybe this year I'd tag along.

77
00:03:33,060 --> 00:03:35,140
Well, that's sweet. I bet you'll have fun.

78
00:03:35,140 --> 00:03:36,640
So, do you want to come?

79
00:03:36,850 --> 00:03:37,610
No, thanks.

80
00:03:37,610 --> 00:03:41,180
I already live in a place all the nerds come to.

81
00:03:41,640 --> 00:03:45,290
Please? I went to your boring thing last month.

82
00:03:45,290 --> 00:03:48,420
My aunt's funeral?

83
00:03:48,700 --> 00:03:52,540
Come on, even you checked your e-mail during the eulogy.

84
00:03:52,540 --> 00:03:54,110
Well, I'm not going,

85
00:03:54,110 --> 00:03:56,650
but I do think it's nice you want to.

86
00:03:56,650 --> 00:03:58,070
It's not that I want to go,

87
00:03:58,070 --> 00:03:59,800
I just think it'll make Leonard happy.

88
00:03:59,800 --> 00:04:01,810
And if I have to watch him squeeze into an Ewok costume,

89
00:04:01,810 --> 00:04:04,210
so be it.

90
00:04:04,270 --> 00:04:06,210
Look at you, going to Comic-Con,

91
00:04:06,210 --> 00:04:07,350
talking about Ewoks.

92
00:04:07,350 --> 00:04:10,490
I really have become the cool one around here.

93
00:04:12,720 --> 00:04:15,280
You actually think Penny will have fun at Comic-Con?

94
00:04:15,280 --> 00:04:17,950
No. Which will make me miserable,

95
00:04:17,950 --> 00:04:20,600
which is usually Sheldon's job.

96
00:04:21,950 --> 00:04:24,380
She's gonna hate waiting in line for the panels.

97
00:04:24,380 --> 00:04:25,900
She's gonna hate all the crowds at the panels.

98
00:04:25,900 --> 00:04:28,090
She's gonna hate the panels.

99
00:04:28,760 --> 00:04:32,580
She's gonna hate how often we say the word "Panels."

100
00:04:32,580 --> 00:04:34,170
Why don't you just tell her not to come?

101
00:04:34,170 --> 00:04:36,690
Well, she's so excited, I can't do that to her.

102
00:04:36,690 --> 00:04:38,470
What if you make it sound so bad

103
00:04:38,470 --> 00:04:40,260
she won't want to go?

104
00:04:40,260 --> 00:04:42,950
That I would do to her.

105
00:04:43,830 --> 00:04:45,330
I can't believe Penny's gonna get to go,

106
00:04:45,330 --> 00:04:46,510
and I'm not.

107
00:04:46,510 --> 00:04:48,570
You can always watch the panels online.

108
00:04:48,570 --> 00:04:51,830
Oh, boy, we do say that a lot.

109
00:04:51,830 --> 00:04:54,450
Panels.

110
00:04:57,500 --> 00:05:00,310
Just wanted to be included.

111
00:05:01,860 --> 00:05:03,850
Come on, Sheldon, it's Comic-Con.

112
00:05:03,850 --> 00:05:05,060
Just let me have the money for this,

113
00:05:05,060 --> 00:05:06,520
and I won't ask for anything else.

114
00:05:06,520 --> 00:05:08,600
You put me in charge of your finances.

115
00:05:08,600 --> 00:05:11,030
If you wanted someone weak and spineless you could walk all over,

116
00:05:11,030 --> 00:05:13,640
you should have asked Leonard.

117
00:05:13,640 --> 00:05:16,070
See? Miserable.

118
00:05:16,070 --> 00:05:18,910
Okay, you're right, I got myself into this,

119
00:05:18,910 --> 00:05:20,880
but I've never missed a Comic-Con with you guys.

120
00:05:20,880 --> 00:05:23,070
Your father may have spoiled you, but I won't.

121
00:05:23,070 --> 00:05:24,560
If you want a ticket to Comic-Con,

122
00:05:24,560 --> 00:05:26,930
I suggest you figure out a way to earn the money yourself.

123
00:05:26,930 --> 00:05:29,650
Yeah, you're a grown man who's highly educated.

124
00:05:29,650 --> 00:05:33,590
You could charge people money to punch you.

125
00:05:35,020 --> 00:05:36,900
Go ahead, make jokes. I don't know why you think

126
00:05:36,900 --> 00:05:39,480
you're going to Comic-Con-- you just had a baby.

127
00:05:39,480 --> 00:05:40,810
- So? - Well, so?

128
00:05:40,810 --> 00:05:42,510
So you think Bernadette's just gonna let you

129
00:05:42,510 --> 00:05:44,610
jet down to San Diego for five days

130
00:05:44,610 --> 00:05:46,180
and leave her alone?

131
00:05:46,180 --> 00:05:47,110
Hang-hang on.

132
00:05:47,110 --> 00:05:49,720
So I have to bring Penny, you can't afford it,

133
00:05:49,720 --> 00:05:50,810
Howard's gonna get in trouble,

134
00:05:50,810 --> 00:05:53,390
and this guy gets to have a great time.

135
00:05:54,470 --> 00:05:57,340
I'm gonna go as Dumbledore.

136
00:06:01,550 --> 00:06:03,020
How's my favorite girl?

137
00:06:03,020 --> 00:06:04,410
Okay.

138
00:06:04,410 --> 00:06:06,490
- What you doing? - Making lasagna.

139
00:06:06,490 --> 00:06:09,430
Oh, she's sexy, she can cook.

140
00:06:09,430 --> 00:06:11,200
I'm such a lucky guy.

141
00:06:11,200 --> 00:06:15,140
You want something stupid, or you did something stupid?

142
00:06:15,590 --> 00:06:19,020
No. I just walked in here, saw how beautiful you are

143
00:06:19,020 --> 00:06:20,310
and had to tell you.

144
00:06:20,310 --> 00:06:23,800
Oh, dear God, you're cheating on me with Raj.

145
00:06:25,640 --> 00:06:27,430
Never gets old.

146
00:06:29,430 --> 00:06:31,270
Okay, there is something I want,

147
00:06:31,270 --> 00:06:33,590
but it's not a big deal.

148
00:06:33,590 --> 00:06:34,570
What is it?

149
00:06:34,570 --> 00:06:36,340
Well, Comic-Con tickets go on sale this Friday,

150
00:06:36,340 --> 00:06:37,620
and I was hoping I could go with the guys.

151
00:06:37,620 --> 00:06:39,860
But before you say anything, I'll make up for being gone

152
00:06:39,860 --> 00:06:42,500
by doing everything around here-- I mean everything.

153
00:06:42,500 --> 00:06:43,830
I'm even gonna answer for you.

154
00:06:43,830 --> 00:06:46,770
"Yes, Howard, you can go."

155
00:06:47,080 --> 00:06:49,440
It's so hard to say no to you.

156
00:06:49,440 --> 00:06:50,730
Thank you.

157
00:06:51,690 --> 00:06:53,730
So I'll say maybe.

158
00:06:54,870 --> 00:06:56,520
What? Why?

159
00:06:56,520 --> 00:06:59,250
You said tickets don't go on sale till Friday, right?

160
00:06:59,250 --> 00:07:00,290
Yeah.

161
00:07:00,290 --> 00:07:03,100
You said you were gonna do all this stuff for me, right?

162
00:07:03,690 --> 00:07:05,380
Yeah.

163
00:07:07,360 --> 00:07:09,770
See where I'm going with this?

164
00:07:11,770 --> 00:07:13,830
Yeah.

165
00:07:15,560 --> 00:07:19,710
If you don't know how to make lasagna, Google does.

166
00:07:21,910 --> 00:07:25,580
Okay, so this is the main Comic-Con floor.

167
00:07:25,580 --> 00:07:28,160
It's where all the vendors and exhibits are.

168
00:07:28,160 --> 00:07:30,820
Wow, that is a lot of people jammed in there.

169
00:07:30,820 --> 00:07:33,970
I know. Sometimes Howard wears a striped shirt

170
00:07:33,970 --> 00:07:37,190
so we can play "Where's Wolowitz?"

171
00:07:39,320 --> 00:07:42,270
Okay, now, th-this is us camping out in line

172
00:07:42,270 --> 00:07:43,730
for the Avengers panel.

173
00:07:43,730 --> 00:07:46,820
Oh, you really sleep on the sidewalk, huh?

174
00:07:46,820 --> 00:07:48,930
Yeah. It can get chilly,

175
00:07:48,930 --> 00:07:51,410
but Raj figured out that if you pee in a bottle

176
00:07:51,410 --> 00:07:52,340
and put it in your sleeping bag,

177
00:07:52,340 --> 00:07:55,240
it helps keep you warm.

178
00:07:56,510 --> 00:07:58,640
Here's the hotel room we all share.

179
00:07:58,640 --> 00:08:01,050
Well, you and I would get our own room, right?

180
00:08:01,050 --> 00:08:02,940
Every hotel is booked.

181
00:08:02,940 --> 00:08:04,890
But, yeah, see this space here

182
00:08:04,890 --> 00:08:06,370
between Sheldon's feet and my head?

183
00:08:06,370 --> 00:08:09,010
That's where you go.

184
00:08:09,010 --> 00:08:10,650
Well, it's no different than when Sheldon

185
00:08:10,650 --> 00:08:14,830
used to climb in bed with us during a thunderstorm.

186
00:08:14,830 --> 00:08:17,390
Don't worry, we won't be doing much sleeping anyway.

187
00:08:17,390 --> 00:08:18,870
It's like an all-night party.

188
00:08:18,870 --> 00:08:22,730
There's trivia contests and Dungeons & Dragons.

189
00:08:22,730 --> 00:08:26,890
As we like to say, it's "Off the chain mail."

190
00:08:27,410 --> 00:08:29,710
I even said "Off the chain mail,"

191
00:08:29,710 --> 00:08:32,530
and she still wants to go.

192
00:08:32,530 --> 00:08:34,390
That's probably my fault.

193
00:08:34,390 --> 00:08:37,970
She may have heard about my cool Dumbledore costume.

194
00:08:38,610 --> 00:08:41,430
Okay, I can give you 20 bucks for the whole box.

195
00:08:41,430 --> 00:08:44,060
But you charged me hundreds for this stuff.

196
00:08:44,060 --> 00:08:47,750
I know. And I did it with a straight face.

197
00:08:48,790 --> 00:08:50,240
But I need to earn enough money

198
00:08:50,240 --> 00:08:52,520
so I can go to Comic-Con.

199
00:08:54,230 --> 00:08:55,670
Well... all right.

200
00:08:55,670 --> 00:08:57,630
I'll give you 25 bucks.

201
00:08:57,630 --> 00:08:59,610
That's my best offer.

202
00:08:59,610 --> 00:09:01,230
I have no choice.

203
00:09:01,230 --> 00:09:02,740
You know, if you want to make extra money,

204
00:09:02,740 --> 00:09:04,430
I-I could throw some work your way.

205
00:09:04,430 --> 00:09:05,520
Really? I'll do anything.

206
00:09:05,520 --> 00:09:06,560
Great, you're hired.

207
00:09:06,560 --> 00:09:08,740
First thing you can do is put price tags on these.

208
00:09:08,740 --> 00:09:11,920
Start the little ones at $50.

209
00:09:14,480 --> 00:09:15,470
You know, it's no big deal.

210
00:09:15,470 --> 00:09:17,650
I can put up with anything for three days.

211
00:09:17,650 --> 00:09:18,780
Comic-Con's five days.

212
00:09:18,780 --> 00:09:21,310
Are you kidding me?

213
00:09:22,860 --> 00:09:24,730
Why don't you just tell him you don't want to go?

214
00:09:24,730 --> 00:09:26,790
I can't, it'll break his heart.

215
00:09:26,790 --> 00:09:27,850
You know, he's always making an effort

216
00:09:27,850 --> 00:09:29,720
to do things with me he doesn't enjoy,

217
00:09:29,720 --> 00:09:32,310
like going outside.

218
00:09:32,700 --> 00:09:35,120
He is an indoor cat.

219
00:09:35,530 --> 00:09:37,110
You know, maybe it won't be that bad.

220
00:09:37,110 --> 00:09:39,220
Leonard says it's really mainstream now.

221
00:09:39,220 --> 00:09:42,680
Comic books aren't just for sad nerds anymore.

222
00:09:57,460 --> 00:10:01,090
I mean, it is still a key part of their demographic.

223
00:10:07,850 --> 00:10:09,810
Howie, can you get that?

224
00:10:09,810 --> 00:10:11,790
Kind of busy.

225
00:10:11,790 --> 00:10:13,490
Busy like I'll be with the baby

226
00:10:13,490 --> 00:10:16,190
if you go to San Diego?

227
00:10:21,390 --> 00:10:22,360
What's with the gloves?

228
00:10:22,360 --> 00:10:25,450
They complete my ensemble. What do you want?

229
00:10:26,560 --> 00:10:28,020
I'm looking to make extra money

230
00:10:28,020 --> 00:10:30,600
and was wondering if you had any chores I could do.

231
00:10:30,600 --> 00:10:31,890
Hang on.

232
00:10:31,890 --> 00:10:37,380
Bernie, can I outsource my chores to an Indian guy?

233
00:10:38,900 --> 00:10:40,590
No.

234
00:10:40,590 --> 00:10:42,830
I tried.

235
00:10:45,670 --> 00:10:46,820
Hey, I was thinking,

236
00:10:46,820 --> 00:10:48,880
if you want to do a couples costume,

237
00:10:48,880 --> 00:10:51,720
we could paint ourselves green and be Hulk and She-Hulk.

238
00:10:51,720 --> 00:10:53,760
Or we could paint ourselves blue

239
00:10:53,760 --> 00:10:56,870
and go as Nightcrawler and Mystique.

240
00:10:57,460 --> 00:11:00,950
Is there any scenario where we're not in full body paint?

241
00:11:00,950 --> 00:11:04,270
Yeah, if you want us to look like losers.

242
00:11:04,270 --> 00:11:07,460
Hey, um, are you sure the guys are okay with me coming?

243
00:11:07,460 --> 00:11:09,510
Yeah, of course, why?

244
00:11:09,510 --> 00:11:11,430
This is just something you usually do together,

245
00:11:11,430 --> 00:11:13,970
and if I'm screwing it up, I don't have to go.

246
00:11:13,970 --> 00:11:18,300
Oh, why? Do you not want to go?

247
00:11:18,680 --> 00:11:22,260
Why? Do you not want me to go?

248
00:11:22,260 --> 00:11:25,230
No, I want you to go.

249
00:11:26,180 --> 00:11:31,400
Okay, good, 'cause that's what I want, too.

250
00:11:34,300 --> 00:11:38,840
Now we're going as Hulk and She-Hulk.

251
00:11:39,260 --> 00:11:42,180
I don't want to take my shirt off at Comic-Con.

252
00:11:42,180 --> 00:11:46,350
If I may speak for Comic-Con, we don't want that either.

253
00:11:46,840 --> 00:11:47,900
Is that nice?

254
00:11:47,900 --> 00:11:50,210
No, but it's honest, and it sounds like you could use

255
00:11:50,210 --> 00:11:52,490
a little more honesty in your relationship.

256
00:11:52,490 --> 00:11:54,790
Uh, I-it's more complicated than that.

257
00:11:54,790 --> 00:11:56,360
I'm always honest with Amy.

258
00:11:56,360 --> 00:11:58,480
The other day she said she was self-conscious

259
00:11:58,480 --> 00:12:00,520
about the beauty mark on her shoulder,

260
00:12:00,520 --> 00:12:02,890
and I said, "You know, you can call that a beauty mark all you want.

261
00:12:02,890 --> 00:12:06,460
When there's hair growing out of it, that's a mole."

262
00:12:07,740 --> 00:12:09,830
Do you think she's as honest with you?

263
00:12:09,830 --> 00:12:11,120
I should hope so.

264
00:12:11,120 --> 00:12:12,910
When she called me an insensitive jerk,

265
00:12:12,910 --> 00:12:15,510
I'd like to think she meant it.

266
00:12:18,000 --> 00:12:20,970
There's got to be other ways you can make a quick buck.

267
00:12:20,970 --> 00:12:22,390
Yeah, you'd think.

268
00:12:22,390 --> 00:12:26,190
Ooh, maybe I could sell my blood and sperm.

269
00:12:28,490 --> 00:12:30,200
I really should wear a bell around my neck

270
00:12:30,200 --> 00:12:32,350
so you guys can hear me coming.

271
00:12:32,350 --> 00:12:34,100
Here, let me help you.

272
00:12:34,100 --> 00:12:35,390
Thank you.

273
00:12:35,390 --> 00:12:37,020
Oh, Double Stuf Oreos,

274
00:12:37,020 --> 00:12:40,020
I remember when I could afford you.

275
00:12:40,560 --> 00:12:41,620
There she goes.

276
00:12:41,620 --> 00:12:43,420
Stay, I'll get her.

277
00:12:43,420 --> 00:12:45,070
- Appreciate it. - That's fine.

278
00:12:45,070 --> 00:12:48,110
She and I can cry together.

279
00:12:48,300 --> 00:12:50,010
He's such a sweetie.

280
00:12:50,010 --> 00:12:53,480
I know, I wish there was some way we could help him.

281
00:12:53,480 --> 00:12:54,980
If he could find a girl with a good job,

282
00:12:54,980 --> 00:12:56,480
all his problems would be over.

283
00:12:56,480 --> 00:12:59,940
Yeah, that's working out great for me.

284
00:13:02,750 --> 00:13:04,690
Penny says they're ready to go.

285
00:13:04,980 --> 00:13:06,210
Very well.

286
00:13:06,210 --> 00:13:09,530
Prepare for a long night of deceit.

287
00:13:09,530 --> 00:13:15,090
Sheldon, women can wear makeup, it's not lying.

288
00:13:15,090 --> 00:13:17,040
I was talking about Leonard.

289
00:13:17,040 --> 00:13:18,700
And if makeup is so truthful,

290
00:13:18,700 --> 00:13:21,460
why is it called "Concealer"?

291
00:13:22,060 --> 00:13:24,180
Wait, wait, wait, what's Leonard lying about?

292
00:13:24,180 --> 00:13:26,040
He doesn't really want Penny to go to Comic-Con.

293
00:13:26,040 --> 00:13:28,310
He's just doing it to make her happy.

294
00:13:28,310 --> 00:13:29,720
Really?

295
00:13:29,720 --> 00:13:31,520
Because she doesn't actually want to go.

296
00:13:31,520 --> 00:13:34,060
She's just doing it to make him happy.

297
00:13:34,060 --> 00:13:36,090
So they're both trying to make each other happy,

298
00:13:36,090 --> 00:13:39,730
and the end result is they make each other sad?

299
00:13:39,730 --> 00:13:42,560
That's hilarious.

300
00:13:43,730 --> 00:13:46,030
I can't wait to tell them.

301
00:13:46,190 --> 00:13:47,750
No, you're not gonna tell them anything.

302
00:13:47,750 --> 00:13:49,460
You're gonna stay out of it.

303
00:13:49,460 --> 00:13:50,260
Why?

304
00:13:50,260 --> 00:13:52,270
Because it's between them.

305
00:13:52,270 --> 00:13:53,220
Well, if you haven't noticed,

306
00:13:53,220 --> 00:13:56,810
I've been between them for the last ten years.

307
00:14:00,050 --> 00:14:00,940
Hey, babe, you want to drive?

308
00:14:00,940 --> 00:14:02,160
Sure, or you can.

309
00:14:02,160 --> 00:14:04,580
No, it's fine, I know you don't like the way I drive.

310
00:14:04,580 --> 00:14:06,920
I don't have a problem with your driving.

311
00:14:06,920 --> 00:14:08,050
Are you listening to this?

312
00:14:08,050 --> 00:14:11,000
They deceive each other about everything.

313
00:14:13,570 --> 00:14:17,270
Just so you know, that guy in the parking lot hit me.

314
00:14:17,270 --> 00:14:20,440
He wasn't in a car, but okay.

315
00:14:21,600 --> 00:14:23,110
Just say you want to drive.

316
00:14:23,110 --> 00:14:25,520
I honestly don't.

317
00:14:28,200 --> 00:14:30,800
Amy, do us a favor, please drive.

318
00:14:30,800 --> 00:14:32,400
Sure, happy to.

319
00:14:32,400 --> 00:14:33,680
If you want to drive, just drive.

320
00:14:33,680 --> 00:14:35,480
I don't see why this has to be so complicated.

321
00:14:35,480 --> 00:14:37,620
It's not complicated. Amy's driving, that's it!

322
00:14:37,620 --> 00:14:39,850
That's not it because you're clearly upset.

323
00:14:39,850 --> 00:14:41,470
You're the one who seems upset.

324
00:14:41,470 --> 00:14:42,490
Why would I be upset?

325
00:14:42,490 --> 00:14:45,620
Because you don't want her to go to Comic-Con!

326
00:14:47,720 --> 00:14:51,720
This is an interesting way to stay out of it.

327
00:14:52,340 --> 00:14:54,220
Wait, you don't want me to go?

328
00:14:54,220 --> 00:14:57,550
Well, I just don't think you're gonna have a good time.

329
00:14:57,550 --> 00:14:58,510
Yeah, well, get this:

330
00:14:58,510 --> 00:14:59,500
neither does Penny,

331
00:14:59,500 --> 00:15:02,180
that's why she doesn't want to go.

332
00:15:03,000 --> 00:15:06,490
You set 'em up, I knock 'em down, good job.

333
00:15:06,490 --> 00:15:09,140
Why would you say you wanted to go if you didn't?

334
00:15:09,140 --> 00:15:11,060
I just thought it would make you happy.

335
00:15:11,060 --> 00:15:14,660
O-O-O-Okay, hold on, so if you don't want to go

336
00:15:14,660 --> 00:15:16,740
and I don't need to bring you,

337
00:15:16,740 --> 00:15:18,670
is everything good?

338
00:15:18,670 --> 00:15:22,170
Hold on, I'm trying to decide if I'm mad at you.

339
00:15:23,160 --> 00:15:25,470
No, I'm happy I don't have to go.

340
00:15:26,450 --> 00:15:27,570
All right, problem solved.

341
00:15:27,570 --> 00:15:28,620
- Okay. - Yeah.

342
00:15:28,620 --> 00:15:30,870
Not entirely, the fight over who's going to drive is still...

343
00:15:30,880 --> 00:15:33,440
Oh, my God, stop talking!

344
00:15:35,470 --> 00:15:36,700
The place looks great.

345
00:15:36,700 --> 00:15:38,240
Did you guys get a maid?

346
00:15:38,240 --> 00:15:40,500
Kind of.

347
00:15:41,130 --> 00:15:42,450
Dinner's almost ready.

348
00:15:42,450 --> 00:15:45,630
If you like meatloaf, I'm sure you'll like its cousin,

349
00:15:45,630 --> 00:15:47,980
bowl of meat.

350
00:15:49,260 --> 00:15:51,060
Hey, if you're still looking to make money,

351
00:15:51,060 --> 00:15:53,880
I will pay you to burn that jacket.

352
00:15:55,940 --> 00:15:57,820
Thank you, but it doesn't look like

353
00:15:57,820 --> 00:15:59,810
I'm going to Comic-Con this year.

354
00:15:59,810 --> 00:16:01,280
Well, with as much debt as you have,

355
00:16:01,280 --> 00:16:03,840
probably not next year either.

356
00:16:05,090 --> 00:16:06,790
- Howie? - Sure.

357
00:16:06,790 --> 00:16:09,900
This is for you.

358
00:16:10,340 --> 00:16:11,350
What's this?

359
00:16:11,350 --> 00:16:13,360
It's back pay for all the babysitting

360
00:16:13,360 --> 00:16:15,150
and taking care of Halley you've done.

361
00:16:15,150 --> 00:16:18,540
There's more than enough in there to cover Comic-Con.

362
00:16:18,540 --> 00:16:22,390
Um, I also take care of Halley.

363
00:16:23,510 --> 00:16:25,530
And you live here for free.

364
00:16:25,530 --> 00:16:27,970
I do, ma'am, thank you, ma'am.

365
00:16:28,790 --> 00:16:30,780
This is so generous of you,

366
00:16:30,780 --> 00:16:32,450
I-I, um, I don't know what to say.

367
00:16:32,450 --> 00:16:33,650
Now you can come with us.

368
00:16:33,650 --> 00:16:36,840
Yeah, there's room in the bed by Sheldon's feet.

369
00:16:38,430 --> 00:16:39,810
As much as I appreciate this,

370
00:16:39,810 --> 00:16:40,980
I can't accept it.

371
00:16:40,980 --> 00:16:41,650
Okay?

372
00:16:41,650 --> 00:16:42,730
Halley's my goddaughter,

373
00:16:42,730 --> 00:16:44,390
I don't take care of her for money.

374
00:16:44,390 --> 00:16:46,240
I would.

375
00:16:49,310 --> 00:16:50,890
Keep it. Consider it a gift.

376
00:16:51,570 --> 00:16:54,040
Hold on. Is it back pay or is it a gift?

377
00:16:54,040 --> 00:16:55,230
What's the difference?

378
00:16:55,230 --> 00:16:57,100
When the IRS questions us in separate rooms,

379
00:16:57,100 --> 00:16:59,630
we need to have our stories straight.

380
00:16:59,630 --> 00:17:02,010
It doesn't matter. I'm not keeping this.

381
00:17:02,010 --> 00:17:04,210
I'm trying to pay my own way and be responsible.

382
00:17:04,210 --> 00:17:06,140
Taking handouts won't help that.

383
00:17:06,140 --> 00:17:08,120
So you're not going to Comic-Con?

384
00:17:08,800 --> 00:17:10,580
I've been plenty of times.

385
00:17:10,580 --> 00:17:13,690
If I miss one, it's fine. I'm a big boy.

386
00:17:13,690 --> 00:17:15,500
I'm a big boy, and if I missed one,

387
00:17:15,500 --> 00:17:18,340
I'd throw a big-boy tantrum.

388
00:17:19,520 --> 00:17:22,510
You know what? I've gone 12 times.

389
00:17:22,510 --> 00:17:24,020
Maybe I'll sit out this year, too.

390
00:17:24,020 --> 00:17:25,460
- Really? - Yeah.

391
00:17:25,460 --> 00:17:27,680
Maybe you and I can do something fun that weekend.

392
00:17:27,680 --> 00:17:30,250
Ooh, how about white-water rafting?

393
00:17:30,250 --> 00:17:32,120
Oh... how about we compromise

394
00:17:32,120 --> 00:17:35,910
and go on the Small World ride at Disneyland?

395
00:17:37,150 --> 00:17:39,790
You know what, I'm not gonna go either.

396
00:17:39,790 --> 00:17:40,930
I'm a father now.

397
00:17:40,930 --> 00:17:44,400
I'd rather spend time with my family.

398
00:17:44,400 --> 00:17:45,970
You just don't want to go alone with Sheldon.

399
00:17:45,970 --> 00:17:47,600
I'm gonna go check on dinner.

400
00:17:50,410 --> 00:17:52,490
Sounds like everyone's staying home.

401
00:17:52,490 --> 00:17:54,400
What do you say?

402
00:17:54,400 --> 00:17:57,790
Nuts to that, I'm going to Comic-Con!

403
00:17:57,790 --> 00:17:59,280
By yourself?

404
00:17:59,280 --> 00:18:00,720
Not necessarily.

405
00:18:00,720 --> 00:18:03,260
I have four months to find some new friends.

406
00:18:03,260 --> 00:18:04,730
I'll go with you.

407
00:18:04,730 --> 00:18:06,620
That's very kind of you, Stuart.

408
00:18:06,620 --> 00:18:09,660
Check back in with me in July.

409
00:18:15,590 --> 00:18:19,170
There's my pretty girlfriend.

410
00:18:20,630 --> 00:18:23,320
I'm not going with you to Comic-Con.

411
00:18:23,320 --> 00:18:26,910
What? Can't a man just be happy to see his woman

412
00:18:26,910 --> 00:18:29,000
and pat her on her second most erogenous

413
00:18:29,000 --> 00:18:31,350
ball-and-socket joint?

414
00:18:33,890 --> 00:18:37,310
He can, but it's still not changing my mind.

415
00:18:38,190 --> 00:18:41,840
Well, maybe what's in my pants will change your mind.

416
00:18:45,900 --> 00:18:48,790
It's a list of this year's panelists.

417
00:18:52,780 --> 00:18:55,820
It's long, isn't it?

