1
00:00:00,890 --> 00:00:02,700
Previously on The Big Bang Theory.

2
00:00:02,700 --> 00:00:04,720
Dad, this is Sheldon's mother, Mary.

3
00:00:04,720 --> 00:00:05,430
How do you do?

4
00:00:05,430 --> 00:00:06,370
Nice to meet you.

5
00:00:06,370 --> 00:00:07,490
And, of course, Mom.

6
00:00:07,490 --> 00:00:10,130
Hello, my hateful shrew.

7
00:00:10,130 --> 00:00:13,450
Hello to you, you wrinkled old bastard.

8
00:00:15,570 --> 00:00:19,240
Hey, I just got an e-mail from the U.S. Air Force.

9
00:00:19,240 --> 00:00:21,430
I'm just afraid if I respond,

10
00:00:21,430 --> 00:00:22,950
then they'll know I got it.

11
00:00:22,950 --> 00:00:23,580
Oh, dude.

12
00:00:23,580 --> 00:00:24,940
The minute you opened that e-mail,

13
00:00:24,940 --> 00:00:25,910
they knew you got it.

14
00:00:25,910 --> 00:00:26,890
I mean, they're probably looking at you

15
00:00:26,890 --> 00:00:28,750
through the camera right now.

16
00:00:30,430 --> 00:00:31,830
Oh, God.

17
00:00:31,830 --> 00:00:33,900
I think someone's following us.

18
00:00:35,380 --> 00:00:37,550
Uh, turn left here and see if he turns with us.

19
00:00:37,550 --> 00:00:39,670
Why is he turning here? The restaurant's the other way.

20
00:00:39,670 --> 00:00:41,710
I don't know. He uses that traffic app.

21
00:00:41,710 --> 00:00:43,170
Maybe there's an accident.

22
00:00:43,170 --> 00:00:44,920
Oh, so follow him.

23
00:00:45,440 --> 00:00:47,780
Oh, no!

24
00:00:48,230 --> 00:00:49,180
Leonard, if you don't mind,

25
00:00:49,180 --> 00:00:50,870
I think I'm a little tired.

26
00:00:50,870 --> 00:00:52,230
I'm gonna call it a night.

27
00:00:52,230 --> 00:00:53,130
Sure, Dad.

28
00:00:53,130 --> 00:00:54,680
I'm a little tuckered out myself.

29
00:00:54,680 --> 00:00:57,390
Well, I will see you all in the morning.

30
00:00:58,230 --> 00:00:59,270
Would you like to share a cab?

31
00:00:59,270 --> 00:01:00,490
That would be fine.

32
00:01:00,490 --> 00:01:02,170
- Where are you staying? - I'm at the Westin.

33
00:01:02,170 --> 00:01:03,460
Well, so am I.

34
00:01:03,460 --> 00:01:04,820
Could I interest you in a nightcap?

35
00:01:04,820 --> 00:01:06,920
I think that you could.

36
00:01:11,470 --> 00:01:12,410
Leonard?

37
00:01:15,070 --> 00:01:16,600
Leonard?

38
00:01:17,150 --> 00:01:18,250
What?

39
00:01:18,250 --> 00:01:21,340
You realize you and I could become brothers.

40
00:01:22,820 --> 00:01:24,230
We're not gonna be brothers.

41
00:01:24,230 --> 00:01:25,830
We're not gonna be stepbrothers.

42
00:01:25,830 --> 00:01:27,660
Go to sleep.

43
00:01:27,660 --> 00:01:29,340
I hope you're right.

44
00:01:29,340 --> 00:01:31,330
'Cause a grown man living with his brother

45
00:01:31,330 --> 00:01:34,670
and his brother's wife is weird.

46
00:01:35,120 --> 00:01:36,880
Go to sleep.

47
00:01:36,880 --> 00:01:38,410
Okay.

48
00:01:41,680 --> 00:01:43,590
Do you think your father's doing unspeakable things

49
00:01:43,590 --> 00:01:45,380
to my mother?

50
00:01:46,320 --> 00:01:47,850
No.

51
00:01:48,180 --> 00:01:48,880
Are you saying that

52
00:01:48,880 --> 00:01:51,150
because the things are unspeakable?

53
00:01:51,150 --> 00:01:52,170
Your parents are old.

54
00:01:52,170 --> 00:01:54,280
Anything unspeakable was finished by 9:30.

55
00:01:54,280 --> 00:01:55,860
Go to sleep.

56
00:01:57,240 --> 00:01:58,930
Very well.

57
00:02:00,690 --> 00:02:03,930
I'm sorry if this stuff is gonna make the ceremony awkward.

58
00:02:03,930 --> 00:02:05,610
God, I thought my brother fresh out of jail

59
00:02:05,610 --> 00:02:06,990
was gonna make everyone uncomfortable,

60
00:02:06,990 --> 00:02:07,770
but now this...

61
00:02:07,770 --> 00:02:08,490
Hey, if you want me to sleep

62
00:02:08,490 --> 00:02:11,140
you're gonna have to stop talking.

63
00:02:35,940 --> 00:02:37,450
Okay, I'm gonna go pick up my family.

64
00:02:37,450 --> 00:02:39,740
Like an hour and half, two hours, depending on traffic.

65
00:02:39,740 --> 00:02:40,620
Yeah, drive safe.

66
00:02:40,620 --> 00:02:42,180
Oh, hey, and do yourself a favor, all right?

67
00:02:42,180 --> 00:02:45,270
When Beverly gets here, do not bring up last night.

68
00:02:45,270 --> 00:02:47,080
All right? As far as you're concerned,

69
00:02:47,080 --> 00:02:48,650
you don't know anything,

70
00:02:48,650 --> 00:02:49,810
you didn't see anything.

71
00:02:49,810 --> 00:02:53,240
I want you just to play dumb.

72
00:02:54,330 --> 00:02:57,340
It was nice of her to show us playing dumb with an example.

73
00:02:57,340 --> 00:02:58,420
What?

74
00:03:00,270 --> 00:03:02,570
Hi. Okay, hey there, I got-- I'm sorry, I got to go now.

75
00:03:02,570 --> 00:03:04,890
- Penny, wait. - Why?

76
00:03:06,220 --> 00:03:08,610
I wanted to thank you for going through all the trouble

77
00:03:08,610 --> 00:03:11,740
of planning a second wedding ceremony for me,

78
00:03:11,740 --> 00:03:14,150
but unfortunately I cannot attend.

79
00:03:14,150 --> 00:03:15,920
Well, why? What's wrong?

80
00:03:15,920 --> 00:03:17,510
Wha-- are we still doing the dumb thing?

81
00:03:17,510 --> 00:03:19,710
Okay, why, what's wrong?

82
00:03:19,930 --> 00:03:21,290
I just cannot stay here

83
00:03:21,290 --> 00:03:23,840
while your father goes out of his way to humiliate me.

84
00:03:23,840 --> 00:03:27,000
Oh, golly, however did he humiliate you?

85
00:03:27,370 --> 00:03:29,150
Stop it, Sheldon.

86
00:03:29,150 --> 00:03:31,810
Do I say "stop what?" or just throw in the towel?

87
00:03:32,460 --> 00:03:34,550
I don't see why I should have to watch your father

88
00:03:34,550 --> 00:03:37,450
parade around with some Bible-thumping bumpkin.

89
00:03:37,450 --> 00:03:40,380
Oh, excuse me, that is my mother you're talking about,

90
00:03:40,380 --> 00:03:42,120
however accurately.

91
00:03:42,800 --> 00:03:43,460
Okay, Beverly,

92
00:03:43,460 --> 00:03:44,740
aren't you overreacting a little?

93
00:03:44,740 --> 00:03:47,100
All we know is they shared a cab and had a nightcap.

94
00:03:47,100 --> 00:03:48,400
And turned their phones off.

95
00:03:48,400 --> 00:03:49,850
Not helping, buddy.

96
00:03:51,670 --> 00:03:54,060
Mother, Penny and I really want you to be part of this.

97
00:03:54,060 --> 00:03:55,040
Please stay.

98
00:03:55,040 --> 00:03:56,080
Yeah, plus if you leave,

99
00:03:56,080 --> 00:03:58,760
Alfred will know he got under your skin.

100
00:04:01,800 --> 00:04:03,630
Well, we can't have that.

101
00:04:05,070 --> 00:04:06,480
You know, also, if they did have coitus,

102
00:04:06,480 --> 00:04:09,090
we'll all be needing a skilled psychiatrist.

103
00:04:12,750 --> 00:04:14,540
It is funny when you think about it.

104
00:04:14,540 --> 00:04:15,490
Maybe to you.

105
00:04:15,490 --> 00:04:17,990
You didn't get a $500 traffic ticket.

106
00:04:18,320 --> 00:04:20,830
Because you were driving like a lunatic.

107
00:04:20,830 --> 00:04:22,920
Hey, if thinking secret government agents

108
00:04:22,920 --> 00:04:25,300
are chasing you makes you a lunatic, then...

109
00:04:25,300 --> 00:04:26,990
yeah, okay.

110
00:04:29,440 --> 00:04:31,060
Oh, I'll get it.

111
00:04:32,140 --> 00:04:33,870
It didn't help that you couldn't walk a straight line

112
00:04:33,870 --> 00:04:35,890
when the cop pulled you over.

113
00:04:37,220 --> 00:04:39,590
I have performance anxiety.

114
00:04:41,100 --> 00:04:43,320
You of all people should know that.

115
00:04:53,570 --> 00:04:55,140
Hello.

116
00:04:55,670 --> 00:04:58,380
I'm looking for Howard Wolowitz.

117
00:04:58,620 --> 00:05:01,180
Howard Wolowitz?

118
00:05:01,820 --> 00:05:04,510
I have the right address, don't I?

119
00:05:04,990 --> 00:05:06,650
Address?

120
00:05:07,110 --> 00:05:08,720
Is he here?

121
00:05:08,720 --> 00:05:11,800
Um... no.

122
00:05:12,590 --> 00:05:14,660
Do you know where I can find him?

123
00:05:14,660 --> 00:05:16,190
May I ask what this is about?

124
00:05:16,190 --> 00:05:17,620
No, you may not.

125
00:05:18,210 --> 00:05:19,220
Very well.

126
00:05:24,580 --> 00:05:25,770
Have him call me.

127
00:05:26,230 --> 00:05:27,170
Okay.

128
00:05:27,660 --> 00:05:30,010
Raj, who's at the door?

129
00:05:32,520 --> 00:05:34,470
That's not him.

130
00:05:37,240 --> 00:05:39,140
Oh, I can't wait for you to meet everyone.

131
00:05:39,140 --> 00:05:41,270
I told them all about you.

132
00:05:41,270 --> 00:05:42,540
Like what?

133
00:05:42,540 --> 00:05:44,070
Do they know about your brother?

134
00:05:44,070 --> 00:05:48,320
Uh, not everything, just, like, the jail and drugs part.

135
00:05:48,640 --> 00:05:50,460
- Why would you do that? - What?

136
00:05:50,460 --> 00:05:52,400
The world doesn't need to know our problems.

137
00:05:52,400 --> 00:05:53,240
Well, Mom, I'm sorry, but...

138
00:05:53,240 --> 00:05:57,170
Hey, look, they got Walgreens here, too.

139
00:05:57,950 --> 00:06:00,570
You really think it's helpful to change the subject, Wyatt?

140
00:06:00,570 --> 00:06:02,680
Just trying to make this a happy trip, dear.

141
00:06:02,680 --> 00:06:04,290
Well, quit it!

142
00:06:07,030 --> 00:06:09,290
So, uh, Randall, can't believe after all these years

143
00:06:09,290 --> 00:06:11,430
you finally get to visit me in California.

144
00:06:11,430 --> 00:06:13,560
Well, good thing I was a nonviolent offender,

145
00:06:13,560 --> 00:06:15,910
otherwise I couldn't have left the state.

146
00:06:17,230 --> 00:06:19,790
All right, that's enough jail talk.

147
00:06:19,790 --> 00:06:23,020
Penny knows where I was; she sent me cigarettes.

148
00:06:23,020 --> 00:06:24,770
You sent your brother cigarettes?

149
00:06:24,770 --> 00:06:27,190
He was cooking and selling crystal meth, Susan,

150
00:06:27,190 --> 00:06:30,250
I think we can let the cigarettes slide.

151
00:06:30,740 --> 00:06:32,200
Stop trying to be the cool dad;

152
00:06:32,200 --> 00:06:35,360
you have a shirt with our cat's picture on it.

153
00:06:36,700 --> 00:06:39,160
Anyway, we're here, slugger.

154
00:06:41,390 --> 00:06:44,160
That's great, now they know where I live.

155
00:06:44,160 --> 00:06:45,150
What are you talking about?

156
00:06:45,150 --> 00:06:46,620
They've always known where you live.

157
00:06:46,620 --> 00:06:47,660
Yeah, if you want to go off the grid,

158
00:06:47,660 --> 00:06:50,020
you have to move out of your mother's house.

159
00:06:51,480 --> 00:06:53,530
Can we take a moment to discuss

160
00:06:53,530 --> 00:06:56,000
that I just lied to the government for you?

161
00:06:56,000 --> 00:06:57,120
Yeah.

162
00:06:57,120 --> 00:06:59,590
I would not have done that for you.

163
00:07:00,390 --> 00:07:02,840
Howard, please just call the man, see what he wants.

164
00:07:02,840 --> 00:07:05,200
All right, all right.

165
00:07:05,630 --> 00:07:06,940
Hey, make sure you tell him that

166
00:07:06,940 --> 00:07:08,770
you weren't home when he came by

167
00:07:08,770 --> 00:07:10,500
and that your Indian friend gave you the message

168
00:07:10,500 --> 00:07:13,390
the moment you stepped through the door.

169
00:07:13,490 --> 00:07:15,520
Yes, hello.

170
00:07:15,520 --> 00:07:18,040
Uh, this is Howard Wolowitz

171
00:07:18,040 --> 00:07:19,730
for Colonel Richard Williams.

172
00:07:19,730 --> 00:07:21,110
Oh, I take it back, don't mention me.

173
00:07:21,110 --> 00:07:24,600
Hi, Colonel Williams, how can I help you?

174
00:07:24,900 --> 00:07:28,520
What? Oh, uh, yes, he is from India.

175
00:07:29,770 --> 00:07:33,470
No, I don't know his immigration status.

176
00:07:35,840 --> 00:07:38,200
Relax, I'm still on hold!

177
00:07:40,810 --> 00:07:42,300
Speaking.

178
00:07:43,230 --> 00:07:46,480
Okay, sure, I can meet with you on Thursday.

179
00:07:46,480 --> 00:07:48,200
Caltech is fine.

180
00:07:48,200 --> 00:07:50,910
Yeah, and may I ask what this is about?

181
00:07:52,120 --> 00:07:53,450
I may not?

182
00:07:54,050 --> 00:07:56,300
That's what he said to me.

183
00:07:58,200 --> 00:07:59,120
Here you are, Mother.

184
00:07:59,120 --> 00:08:00,450
Thank you.

185
00:08:00,890 --> 00:08:02,640
I'm glad you decided to stay.

186
00:08:03,050 --> 00:08:05,860
It's gonna be special for Penny and me to share this with you.

187
00:08:05,860 --> 00:08:08,390
I can't wait for this day to be over.

188
00:08:10,610 --> 00:08:13,110
Yeah, special, like that.

189
00:08:14,670 --> 00:08:15,830
That's them.

190
00:08:16,200 --> 00:08:19,500
Please don't make things any more awkward than they already are.

191
00:08:19,500 --> 00:08:22,760
All right, so less or equally awkward, got it.

192
00:08:24,440 --> 00:08:25,860
Hey, guys, come on in.

193
00:08:25,860 --> 00:08:27,450
- Oh, thank you. - Good morning.

194
00:08:27,450 --> 00:08:28,420
- Morning. - Hello.

195
00:08:28,420 --> 00:08:30,370
How is everyone today?

196
00:08:30,370 --> 00:08:31,530
Good, and you?

197
00:08:31,530 --> 00:08:33,530
- Good, good. - Good.

198
00:08:33,530 --> 00:08:34,800
I'm good, too.

199
00:08:34,800 --> 00:08:36,040
Good.

200
00:08:39,750 --> 00:08:42,170
So, did you defile my mother or not?

201
00:08:43,410 --> 00:08:45,390
Sheldon!

202
00:08:45,390 --> 00:08:47,070
You're being rude.

203
00:08:47,070 --> 00:08:48,740
If I may, I can assure you,

204
00:08:48,740 --> 00:08:50,200
your mother and I did nothing more

205
00:08:50,200 --> 00:08:52,970
than share a cab and a conversation.

206
00:08:53,160 --> 00:08:54,760
Did that conversation include the phrase

207
00:08:54,760 --> 00:08:56,870
"Your genitals are a joy to behold"?

208
00:08:56,870 --> 00:08:59,060
That's enough!

209
00:08:59,380 --> 00:09:00,700
Look, I promise you, neither I,

210
00:09:00,700 --> 00:09:03,470
nor anyone, has ever said that.

211
00:09:04,940 --> 00:09:07,370
You don't know his girlfriend very well.

212
00:09:08,610 --> 00:09:11,560
Or what a joy it is to behold my genitals.

213
00:09:14,230 --> 00:09:16,230
All right, you guys, uh, get settled in,

214
00:09:16,230 --> 00:09:18,300
then we'll go across the hall and say hi to everyone.

215
00:09:18,300 --> 00:09:20,870
You know, It's hard to believe I've never met Leonard.

216
00:09:20,870 --> 00:09:23,350
Well, he probably buys his illegal drugs

217
00:09:23,350 --> 00:09:25,360
from a local vendor.

218
00:09:26,340 --> 00:09:27,760
Not funny, Wyatt.

219
00:09:27,760 --> 00:09:30,120
- I thought it was really funny. - Thanks.

220
00:09:30,660 --> 00:09:33,550
Well, fine, if everyone wants to make jokes about our problems,

221
00:09:33,550 --> 00:09:35,020
then I can, too.

222
00:09:35,020 --> 00:09:36,810
Knock, knock. Who's there?

223
00:09:36,810 --> 00:09:39,760
Our family is an embarrassment.

224
00:09:39,950 --> 00:09:41,930
- That's not much of a joke. - Okay.

225
00:09:42,470 --> 00:09:44,360
Listen, Mom, I know you're nervous, but I promise you,

226
00:09:44,360 --> 00:09:46,710
no one is gonna judge you or this family.

227
00:09:46,710 --> 00:09:48,350
Oh, I'm sorry.

228
00:09:48,350 --> 00:09:50,770
It's just we're meeting Leonard's parents for the first time,

229
00:09:50,770 --> 00:09:54,080
and-and they're academics and-and intellectuals,

230
00:09:54,080 --> 00:09:56,890
and I don't want them thinking we're white trash.

231
00:09:58,010 --> 00:10:00,790
Well, what color trash do you think they'll believe?

232
00:10:03,500 --> 00:10:05,020
How could you think that I would spend the night

233
00:10:05,020 --> 00:10:07,190
with a man I just met?

234
00:10:07,190 --> 00:10:08,520
A man named Jesus

235
00:10:08,520 --> 00:10:10,240
convinced you to build a church in Africa.

236
00:10:10,240 --> 00:10:12,040
You're kind of a sucker.

237
00:10:13,770 --> 00:10:15,770
Well, nothing happened, right?

238
00:10:15,770 --> 00:10:16,920
I-It's over.

239
00:10:16,920 --> 00:10:18,110
Until we get married a third time,

240
00:10:18,110 --> 00:10:20,370
you guys will never have to see each other again.

241
00:10:20,900 --> 00:10:22,720
Well, you know, actually that's not the case.

242
00:10:22,720 --> 00:10:24,770
Mary may visit me in New York.

243
00:10:25,100 --> 00:10:27,080
And he's never been to Texas.

244
00:10:27,080 --> 00:10:28,760
Maybe we meet halfway.

245
00:10:28,760 --> 00:10:32,530
What? In the Chattahoochee National Forest in Georgia?

246
00:10:33,900 --> 00:10:37,110
I can't be the only one that knows that's halfway.

247
00:10:38,390 --> 00:10:40,320
You're not seriously going to visit each other.

248
00:10:40,320 --> 00:10:41,410
And why wouldn't we?

249
00:10:41,410 --> 00:10:43,610
Oh, please, you're just saying this to antagonize me.

250
00:10:43,610 --> 00:10:44,730
Not at all.

251
00:10:44,730 --> 00:10:46,570
Mary happens to be a wonderful woman.

252
00:10:46,570 --> 00:10:49,320
And if it antagonizes you, tothat's just a bonus.

253
00:10:51,130 --> 00:10:53,300
Mary, I'm sorry you're in the middle of this.

254
00:10:53,300 --> 00:10:55,310
No, no, nothing to be sorry about.

255
00:10:55,310 --> 00:10:57,600
I genuinely like your father.

256
00:10:57,600 --> 00:11:00,500
What? But he's a mediocre academic.

257
00:11:00,500 --> 00:11:04,580
And according to Beverly, his sexual prowess is subpar.

258
00:11:05,180 --> 00:11:07,980
He's basically Leonard with a bigger prostate.

259
00:11:10,770 --> 00:11:14,140
Are you saying that my dad's not good enough for your mom?

260
00:11:14,140 --> 00:11:16,260
Yes, while also getting in a solid dig at you.

261
00:11:16,260 --> 00:11:17,860
Pretty efficient, huh?

262
00:11:18,840 --> 00:11:21,910
This is ridiculous. I-I'm going across the hall.

263
00:11:21,910 --> 00:11:23,360
But why should you get to go

264
00:11:23,360 --> 00:11:24,830
and leave me here with your bickering parents?

265
00:11:24,830 --> 00:11:25,900
Fine, then you go!

266
00:11:25,900 --> 00:11:28,400
Well, I don't want to stay here with her. I'll go.

267
00:11:28,400 --> 00:11:29,030
I'll go with you.

268
00:11:29,030 --> 00:11:30,390
That still leaves me here with him.

269
00:11:30,390 --> 00:11:31,940
Hang on, hang on!

270
00:11:31,940 --> 00:11:33,550
We're smart, we can figure this out.

271
00:11:33,550 --> 00:11:37,080
Okay, so...Mary and Beverly can't be together.

272
00:11:37,420 --> 00:11:40,000
Uh, Alfred and Beverly can't be together.

273
00:11:40,000 --> 00:11:42,510
Leonard and I can't be together.

274
00:11:42,510 --> 00:11:45,030
Now, I could be with Alfred...

275
00:11:45,030 --> 00:11:47,100
but I don't like his face.

276
00:11:48,560 --> 00:11:49,820
Oh, here! I've got it!

277
00:11:49,820 --> 00:11:51,750
Who's ready for a wedding?

278
00:11:51,750 --> 00:11:53,670
Great, now I have to start all over.

279
00:11:57,810 --> 00:12:00,160
So how's the world of pharmaceuticals treating you?

280
00:12:00,160 --> 00:12:01,540
Pretty good. I actually just got assigned

281
00:12:01,540 --> 00:12:03,340
a much better territory.

282
00:12:03,340 --> 00:12:05,710
See what happens when you work hard?

283
00:12:05,710 --> 00:12:09,130
Hey, she just sells drugs. I had to make 'em.

284
00:12:10,070 --> 00:12:11,640
Okay, that's enough.

285
00:12:11,640 --> 00:12:14,400
No more drug talk for the rest of this trip.

286
00:12:14,400 --> 00:12:16,410
I'll drink to that.

287
00:12:16,550 --> 00:12:17,880
Haven't you had enough?

288
00:12:17,880 --> 00:12:19,250
Penny drinks more than I do.

289
00:12:19,250 --> 00:12:21,720
Well, I learned from the best.

290
00:12:24,880 --> 00:12:26,160
Very nice, Wyatt.

291
00:12:26,160 --> 00:12:28,930
And you wonder why this one turned out the way he did.

292
00:12:28,930 --> 00:12:30,930
You see what I've gotta put up with!

293
00:12:30,930 --> 00:12:33,000
What you've gotta put up with?

294
00:12:33,000 --> 00:12:34,670
Why did you have to go to jail?

295
00:12:34,670 --> 00:12:38,040
It's called getting caught, Mother!

296
00:12:38,770 --> 00:12:39,650
Hello!

297
00:12:39,650 --> 00:12:40,980
Hey, there he is! Hey!

298
00:12:40,980 --> 00:12:44,230
Oh, Leonard! It's so nice to see you again!

299
00:12:44,230 --> 00:12:44,970
Oh, you, too!

300
00:12:44,970 --> 00:12:47,330
Hey, everyone, this is my mother, Beverly.

301
00:12:47,330 --> 00:12:48,750
- Hello.- Hi.

302
00:12:48,750 --> 00:12:51,710
We are not white trash!

303
00:12:56,050 --> 00:12:58,350
Are you excited to see your son walk down the aisle?

304
00:12:58,350 --> 00:12:59,750
Yes, I am.

305
00:12:59,750 --> 00:13:00,950
I'm just feeling a little guilty

306
00:13:00,950 --> 00:13:02,450
about all the trouble I've caused.

307
00:13:02,450 --> 00:13:03,960
Oh, so am I.

308
00:13:03,960 --> 00:13:07,200
You made God sad today, Mom.

309
00:13:14,510 --> 00:13:16,210
Sheldon, they haven't done anything wrong.

310
00:13:16,210 --> 00:13:18,150
I think it's nice they're hitting it off.

311
00:13:18,150 --> 00:13:20,370
Well, that's still no reason to rush into anything.

312
00:13:20,370 --> 00:13:21,350
Look at us.

313
00:13:21,350 --> 00:13:23,130
We took things remarkably slow.

314
00:13:23,130 --> 00:13:26,220
You and I, we didn't even hold hands for two years.

315
00:13:27,500 --> 00:13:29,490
It was a lot hotter than it sounds.

316
00:13:30,560 --> 00:13:32,010
You're a patient young lady.

317
00:13:32,010 --> 00:13:33,000
Hey, hey! She's mine!

318
00:13:33,000 --> 00:13:35,180
Take a cold shower, grandpa!

319
00:13:38,870 --> 00:13:41,070
Why wouldn't that colonel say what the meeting's about?

320
00:13:41,070 --> 00:13:42,300
It has to be bad news.

321
00:13:42,550 --> 00:13:45,110
Calm down, okay? Try not to think about it.

322
00:13:45,110 --> 00:13:47,750
That's really stupid advice.

323
00:13:47,750 --> 00:13:49,810
You know that hurts my feelings.

324
00:13:50,140 --> 00:13:52,200
Calm down, try not to think about it.

325
00:13:53,470 --> 00:13:54,560
Okay.

326
00:13:56,760 --> 00:13:58,210
Why do I bother talking to you?

327
00:13:58,210 --> 00:14:00,990
Oh, come on. What's the worst that could come of this meeting?

328
00:14:00,990 --> 00:14:03,110
I don't know. They take the invention away,

329
00:14:03,110 --> 00:14:04,310
and I get nothing?

330
00:14:04,590 --> 00:14:06,320
Okay, that's not so bad.

331
00:14:06,320 --> 00:14:07,810
You know what happened to the scientists

332
00:14:07,810 --> 00:14:09,350
that worked on the Manhattan Project?

333
00:14:09,350 --> 00:14:11,470
The government forced them to move to the desert.

334
00:14:11,470 --> 00:14:13,130
They had to live in secret,

335
00:14:13,130 --> 00:14:14,420
and when Oppenheimer objected

336
00:14:14,420 --> 00:14:15,650
to what they made him do,

337
00:14:15,650 --> 00:14:18,170
they destroyed his reputation.

338
00:14:18,680 --> 00:14:21,410
What's the point of that story?

339
00:14:23,080 --> 00:14:24,840
I just read a book about Oppenheimer,

340
00:14:24,840 --> 00:14:27,800
seemed like a chance to show off.

341
00:14:30,420 --> 00:14:31,940
There he is!

342
00:14:31,940 --> 00:14:34,600
There's my happy Hebraic homeboy.

343
00:14:35,290 --> 00:14:36,710
Yeah, that's the smile I'm gonna remember

344
00:14:36,710 --> 00:14:40,220
when you're living in the desert and I'm living with your wife.

345
00:14:44,150 --> 00:14:46,510
So, what do you do for a living?

346
00:14:46,890 --> 00:14:49,210
Mommy, you want to take this one?

347
00:14:49,970 --> 00:14:52,850
Um, Randall's in between jobs.

348
00:14:52,850 --> 00:14:55,280
And court appearances.

349
00:14:56,240 --> 00:14:57,170
It's nice to meet the woman

350
00:14:57,170 --> 00:14:59,240
who raised this fine young man.

351
00:14:59,240 --> 00:15:01,230
I'm looking forward to meeting his father.

352
00:15:01,230 --> 00:15:03,580
Prepare to be disappointed.

353
00:15:04,420 --> 00:15:05,610
And he can't wait to meet you, too.

354
00:15:05,610 --> 00:15:07,000
Can I get anyone a drink?

355
00:15:07,000 --> 00:15:08,360
Well, I could use another beer.

356
00:15:08,360 --> 00:15:09,820
You're done.

357
00:15:11,710 --> 00:15:13,210
He's done.

358
00:15:14,580 --> 00:15:17,320
Hey! Is everyone getting to know each other?

359
00:15:17,320 --> 00:15:18,880
Not at all!

360
00:15:29,770 --> 00:15:31,430
Nice to see you again, Dr. Hofstadter.

361
00:15:31,430 --> 00:15:33,470
I'm, uh, Leonard's friend, Stuart.

362
00:15:33,470 --> 00:15:35,460
Nice to see you, too.

363
00:15:35,760 --> 00:15:36,870
Hi, I'm Stuart.

364
00:15:36,870 --> 00:15:39,580
Ooh, I'm Alfred. Leonard's father.

365
00:15:39,580 --> 00:15:40,950
Oh! Oh, hi.

366
00:15:40,950 --> 00:15:42,960
Uh, I'm sorry, did you two want to sit together?

367
00:15:42,960 --> 00:15:44,840
- No. - No.

368
00:15:47,310 --> 00:15:50,980
I was wondering why the front row was available.

369
00:15:51,940 --> 00:15:53,860
Okay, I think we're ready.

370
00:16:01,330 --> 00:16:03,400
Why do people cry at weddings?

371
00:16:03,400 --> 00:16:06,270
They're practicing for what's coming later.

372
00:16:11,250 --> 00:16:14,520
Thank you for cleaning yourself up for your sister's wedding.

373
00:16:14,520 --> 00:16:17,230
Thank you for my new teeth.

374
00:16:21,890 --> 00:16:23,420
Welcome to the family, Leonard.

375
00:16:23,420 --> 00:16:25,690
Don't lend your new brother-in-law money.

376
00:16:30,830 --> 00:16:33,620
We're here today to celebrate love.

377
00:16:36,510 --> 00:16:39,370
Sigh louder, no one heard you.

378
00:16:40,800 --> 00:16:42,660
Really, I can move.

379
00:16:43,550 --> 00:16:45,240
Not just Leonard and Penny's love,

380
00:16:45,240 --> 00:16:48,310
but the love we have for them, as well as each other.

381
00:16:48,310 --> 00:16:50,000
Speaking of love,

382
00:16:50,000 --> 00:16:53,450
STDs among the elderly are skyrocketing.

383
00:16:55,420 --> 00:16:56,660
Love is patient,

384
00:16:56,660 --> 00:16:58,450
but it's not gonna put up with all the side chatter,

385
00:16:58,450 --> 00:17:00,270
so let's knock it off!

386
00:17:02,340 --> 00:17:04,060
At least she's yelling at someone else for a change.

387
00:17:04,060 --> 00:17:05,480
Howard!

388
00:17:09,810 --> 00:17:11,660
Okay, I understand everyone's a little tense today,

389
00:17:11,660 --> 00:17:14,160
so I am just gonna get to the important stuff.

390
00:17:14,650 --> 00:17:17,520
Leonard, standing here with you

391
00:17:17,520 --> 00:17:19,860
in front of our family and friends

392
00:17:19,860 --> 00:17:22,280
is bringing up a lot of feelings.

393
00:17:22,280 --> 00:17:25,940
Like what a good idea it was to elope the first time.

394
00:17:27,620 --> 00:17:31,550
But also how incredibly happy you make me.

395
00:17:32,210 --> 00:17:34,070
Thank you for marrying me.

396
00:17:34,070 --> 00:17:36,170
Hopefully for the last time.

397
00:17:38,980 --> 00:17:39,900
Penny...

398
00:17:41,060 --> 00:17:42,250
as a scientist,

399
00:17:42,250 --> 00:17:44,560
my job is to figure out why things happen.

400
00:17:44,560 --> 00:17:47,520
But I don't think I'll ever understand

401
00:17:47,520 --> 00:17:48,840
how someone like me

402
00:17:48,840 --> 00:17:52,800
could get to be with someone like you.

403
00:17:52,800 --> 00:17:56,150
You know... maybe... I don't need to understand it,

404
00:17:56,150 --> 00:17:57,320
I just need to be grateful.

405
00:17:57,320 --> 00:17:58,630
I love you, Penny.

406
00:18:02,150 --> 00:18:05,070
Anybody have anything snarky to say about that?

407
00:18:07,140 --> 00:18:08,750
Didn't think so.

408
00:18:10,040 --> 00:18:11,740
I'd like to say something.

409
00:18:12,640 --> 00:18:13,680
Beverly,

410
00:18:14,030 --> 00:18:16,840
I know that we don't bring out the best in each other.

411
00:18:17,090 --> 00:18:20,800
But something wonderful did come from our relationship:

412
00:18:20,800 --> 00:18:23,270
that young man right there.

413
00:18:23,620 --> 00:18:25,620
I couldn't agree more.

414
00:18:27,830 --> 00:18:29,350
That's beautiful.

415
00:18:31,820 --> 00:18:34,360
Thank you. All right, let's continue.

416
00:18:34,360 --> 00:18:37,790
Yeah, excuse me, I need to say something

417
00:18:37,790 --> 00:18:40,730
to someone pretty special, and...

418
00:18:40,730 --> 00:18:43,180
I just can't wait any longer.

419
00:18:43,720 --> 00:18:44,870
It's happening.

420
00:18:44,950 --> 00:18:46,300
Leonard...

421
00:18:50,290 --> 00:18:52,850
You and I have our ups and downs.

422
00:18:52,850 --> 00:18:56,940
But I have always considered you my family.

423
00:18:56,940 --> 00:19:00,050
Even before the recent threat of our parents fornicating

424
00:19:00,050 --> 00:19:02,500
like wrinkly old rabbits.

425
00:19:06,870 --> 00:19:08,820
I don't always show it,

426
00:19:08,820 --> 00:19:11,640
but you are of great importance to me.

427
00:19:13,230 --> 00:19:14,510
Both of you.

428
00:19:15,610 --> 00:19:17,150
Thank you.

429
00:19:17,150 --> 00:19:18,780
Okay.

430
00:19:19,070 --> 00:19:22,300
I now pronounce you husband and wife.

431
00:19:23,050 --> 00:19:26,330
And weird other husband who came with the apartment.

432
00:19:33,000 --> 00:19:34,910
Thank you for taking us to the airport.

433
00:19:34,910 --> 00:19:38,240
Hey, I'm just thrilled we're all getting along for a minute.

434
00:19:38,240 --> 00:19:39,570
Yeah, me, too.

435
00:19:39,570 --> 00:19:42,000
Beverly, I'm sorry if I upset you.

436
00:19:42,000 --> 00:19:43,920
Water under the bridge, Alfred.

437
00:19:44,910 --> 00:19:47,050
Leonard, why don't you get into the carpool lane?

438
00:19:47,050 --> 00:19:49,020
Well, that's a solid line. He can't cross it.

439
00:19:49,020 --> 00:19:50,420
That's okay. I can make it over.

440
00:19:50,480 --> 00:19:51,890
No, no, let's plod along.

441
00:19:51,890 --> 00:19:54,620
It'll make your father feel more comfortable.

442
00:19:55,540 --> 00:19:57,400
What makes me comfortable is knowing I don't have to

443
00:19:57,400 --> 00:20:01,430
wake up tomorrow morning and see your sour face.

444
00:20:01,980 --> 00:20:05,110
Do the world a favor and don't wake up tomorrow morning.

445
00:20:08,080 --> 00:20:10,200
That was almost a minute.

446
00:20:12,470 --> 00:20:15,110
There's a lot of traffic. Are we gonna be okay?

447
00:20:15,110 --> 00:20:16,900
You'll be at the airport an hour before your flight.

448
00:20:16,900 --> 00:20:17,970
Good. Thank you.

449
00:20:17,970 --> 00:20:22,230
Plenty of time for you to meet another geriatric boy toy.

450
00:20:23,520 --> 00:20:26,480
Hey. I will not have you be disrespectful to me.

451
00:20:26,480 --> 00:20:27,980
Yes, ma'am.

452
00:20:27,980 --> 00:20:29,990
Sheldon, your mother's an attractive woman.

453
00:20:29,990 --> 00:20:31,160
You need to get used to the fact

454
00:20:31,160 --> 00:20:33,130
that men are gonna be interested in her.

455
00:20:33,130 --> 00:20:36,760
And you need to drive the car and mind your business.

456
00:20:37,210 --> 00:20:39,340
I will not have you be disrespectful to me.

457
00:20:39,340 --> 00:20:40,320
What-- you're not my mother.

458
00:20:40,320 --> 00:20:41,860
Don't you be disrespectful to her!

459
00:20:41,860 --> 00:20:43,530
Yes, ma'am.

460
00:20:44,790 --> 00:20:48,290
You'll get there, you've just got to put some zing on it.

461
00:20:51,670 --> 00:20:54,190
Penny, I don't know what I was worried about.

462
00:20:54,190 --> 00:20:55,760
Your friends are just lovely.

463
00:20:55,760 --> 00:20:57,360
Oh, thanks, Mom.

464
00:20:57,360 --> 00:21:01,260
Although that Sheldon is a bit peculiar.

465
00:21:01,900 --> 00:21:05,000
Is he? I never noticed.

466
00:21:05,450 --> 00:21:07,290
He reminds me of that turkey we had

467
00:21:07,290 --> 00:21:09,490
who drowned looking up at the rain.

468
00:21:12,340 --> 00:21:14,270
Cops, cops, be cool!

